<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<profdata>
	<profile>
		<id>119</id>
		<name>Zubaid Ahmad</name>
		<firstname>Zubaid</firstname>
		<lastname>Ahmad</lastname>
		<title1>Vice Chairman</title1>
		<title2>Institutional Clients Group</title2>
		<title3>Global Head, Public Sector and Sovereign Wealth Funds</title3>
		<title4/>
		<smallImg>ahmad.jpg</smallImg>
		<speaker/>
		<boardDir/>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>yes</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>no</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>no</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>no</sec16exec>
		<sec16link/>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<p>Zubaid Ahmad is a Vice Chairman of Citi's Institutional Clients Group and a member of its Senior Strategic Advisory Group.  His responsibilities include serving as (a) Global Head of the Public Sector Group, where he helps strategically deliver Citi's product offerings, across Banking, Markets and Global Transaction Services, to the firm's government clients, such as Central Banks and Ministries of Finance, among others; and (b) Global Head of Sovereign Wealth and Government Investment Funds. Mr. Ahmad also serves on Citi's Business Development Committee.</p>
			<p>During his 25-year global corporate- and investment-banking experience, Zubaid has completed a large number of transactions, for both the U.S. as well as emerging markets clients spanning mergers and acquisitions, leveraged buyouts, debt and equity capital markets, privatizations and project financings. Zubaid's client relationships have included leading corporations, as well as private equity and sovereign wealth funds.</p>
			<p>Prior to joining Citi in June 2010, Zubaid served as a Vice Chairman and Head of Corporate Finance - Americas for Standard Chartered Bank. Until June 2008, he held various senior positions at J.P. Morgan, including Vice Chairman and Chief Operating Officer of Americas Investment Banking and Vice Chairman of the Financial Sponsors Group, where he was responsible for a number of the firm's relationships with leading global private equity firms. Previously, Zubaid served as a Managing Director in both the Global Corporate Finance and Financial Sponsor groups at Credit Suisse, Head of Wasserstein Perella Capital Markets and a member of the investment banking department at Drexel Burnham & Lambert.</p>
			<p>Zubaid received his B.S.B.A., <i>magna cum laude</i>, from Georgetown University and his M.B.A., with distinction, from the Harvard Business School. He has also served on a number of private and public company boards over the years.</p>
			]]></bio>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>1</id>
		<name>Raul Anaya</name>
		<firstname>Raul</firstname>
		<lastname>Anaya</lastname>
		<title1>Chief Executive Officer</title1>
		<title2>Central America and the Caribbean</title2>
		<title3/>
		<title4/>
		<smallImg>anaya.jpg</smallImg>
		<speaker/>
		<boardDir/>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>no</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>no</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>no</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>no</sec16exec>
		<profilelink>anaya/index.htm</profilelink>
		<sec16link/>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<p>Raul Anaya has a 20-year professional track at Citi, where he has had a challenging career across various regions and businesses. Currently, Raul Anaya is responsible for all Citi's businesses in Central America and the Caribbean, as Chief Executive Officer, a role he assumed in July 2008. His geographic leadership extends across the Global Consumer Group (Retail Banking, Cards, and Consumer Finance); Institutional Clients Group, (Fixed Income, Currencies and Commodities, Equities, Investment Banking, Corporate and Commercial Banking, and Transaction Services) and Global Wealth Management, within this region. Appointed in January 2008, Raul also acts as member of the Board of Directors of Banco de Chile.</p>
			<p>Previous to this, Raul Anaya was the Chief Executive Officer of Latin America, Citigroup Global Consumer Group. He was responsible for Consumer Operations - Retail Banking, Cards, and Consumer Finance. Mr. Anaya was named to his position in December 2005. He had served as Retail Head for Latin America from February 2005.</p>
			<p>Earlier, Mr. Anaya was Executive Director in Charge of Consumer Assets at Banamex in Mexico, where he was responsible for Mortgages, Personal Loans, and Auto Financing from August 2003 to January 2005. Prior to this position, he was the Divisional Director in Charge of the Center Metropolitan Retail Banking Division at Banamex.</p>
			<p>From May 1999 to January 2002 Mr. Anaya was Chairman and CEO of Banco Bansud S.A. (formerly a wholly owned subsidiary of Banamex) in Argentina.</p>
			<p>Mr. Anaya joined the organization at the Banamex New York Agency in October 1987, and subsequently held the positions of General Manager of Banamex Los Angeles Agency, Executive VP of the Corporate and International Banking Division at California Commerce Bank, General Manager of Banamex Houston Agency, and General Manager of Banamex New York Agency - responsible for the U.S. and Canada offices.</p>
			<p>Mr. Anaya was Member of the Board of Directors of California Commerce Bank from 1996 to 2001.</p>
			]]></bio>
	</profile>
</profdata>
