<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<profdata>

	<profile>
		<id>119</id>
		<name>Zubaid Ahmad</name>
		<firstname>Zubaid</firstname>
		<lastname>Ahmad</lastname>
		<title1>Vice Chairman</title1>
		<title2>Institutional Clients Group</title2>
		<title3>Global Head, Public Sector and Sovereign Wealth Funds</title3>
		<title4/>
		<smallImg>ahmad.jpg</smallImg>
		<speaker/>
		<boardDir/>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>yes</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>no</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>no</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>no</sec16exec>
		<sec16link/>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<p>Zubaid Ahmad is a Vice Chairman of Citi's Institutional Clients Group and a member of its Senior Strategic Advisory Group.  His responsibilities include serving as (a) Global Head of the Public Sector Group, where he helps strategically deliver Citi's product offerings, across Banking, Markets and Global Transaction Services, to the firm's government clients, such as Central Banks and Ministries of Finance, among others; and (b) Global Head of Sovereign Wealth and Government Investment Funds. Mr. Ahmad also serves on Citi's Business Development Committee.</p>
			<p>During his 25-year global corporate- and investment-banking experience, Zubaid has completed a large number of transactions, for both the U.S. as well as emerging markets clients spanning mergers and acquisitions, leveraged buyouts, debt and equity capital markets, privatizations and project financings. Zubaid's client relationships have included leading corporations, as well as private equity and sovereign wealth funds.</p>
			<p>Prior to joining Citi in June 2010, Zubaid served as a Vice Chairman and Head of Corporate Finance - Americas for Standard Chartered Bank. Until June 2008, he held various senior positions at J.P. Morgan, including Vice Chairman and Chief Operating Officer of Americas Investment Banking and Vice Chairman of the Financial Sponsors Group, where he was responsible for a number of the firm's relationships with leading global private equity firms. Previously, Zubaid served as a Managing Director in both the Global Corporate Finance and Financial Sponsor groups at Credit Suisse, Head of Wasserstein Perella Capital Markets and a member of the investment banking department at Drexel Burnham & Lambert.</p>
			<p>Zubaid received his B.S.B.A., <i>magna cum laude</i>, from Georgetown University and his M.B.A., with distinction, from the Harvard Business School. He has also served on a number of private and public company boards over the years.</p>
			]]></bio>
	</profile>

</profdata>
