<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<profdata>
	
	<profile>
		<id>119</id>
		<name>Zubaid Ahmad</name>
		<firstname>Zubaid</firstname>
		<lastname>Ahmad</lastname>
		<title1>Vice Chairman</title1>
		<title2>Institutional Clients Group</title2>
		<title3>Global Head, Public Sector and Sovereign Wealth Funds</title3>
		<title4/>
		<smallImg>ahmad.jpg</smallImg>
		<speaker/>
		<boardDir/>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>yes</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>no</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>no</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>no</sec16exec>
		<sec16link/>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<p>Zubaid Ahmad is a Vice Chairman of Citi's Institutional Clients Group and a member of its Senior Strategic Advisory Group.  His responsibilities include serving as (a) Global Head of the Public Sector Group, where he helps strategically deliver Citi's product offerings, across Banking, Markets and Global Transaction Services, to the firm's government clients, such as Central Banks and Ministries of Finance, among others; and (b) Global Head of Sovereign Wealth and Government Investment Funds. Mr. Ahmad also serves on Citi's Business Development Committee.</p>
			<p>During his 25-year global corporate- and investment-banking experience, Zubaid has completed a large number of transactions, for both the U.S. as well as emerging markets clients spanning mergers and acquisitions, leveraged buyouts, debt and equity capital markets, privatizations and project financings. Zubaid's client relationships have included leading corporations, as well as private equity and sovereign wealth funds.</p>
			<p>Prior to joining Citi in June 2010, Zubaid served as a Vice Chairman and Head of Corporate Finance - Americas for Standard Chartered Bank. Until June 2008, he held various senior positions at J.P. Morgan, including Vice Chairman and Chief Operating Officer of Americas Investment Banking and Vice Chairman of the Financial Sponsors Group, where he was responsible for a number of the firm's relationships with leading global private equity firms. Previously, Zubaid served as a Managing Director in both the Global Corporate Finance and Financial Sponsor groups at Credit Suisse, Head of Wasserstein Perella Capital Markets and a member of the investment banking department at Drexel Burnham & Lambert.</p>
			<p>Zubaid received his B.S.B.A., <i>magna cum laude</i>, from Georgetown University and his M.B.A., with distinction, from the Harvard Business School. He has also served on a number of private and public company boards over the years.</p>
			]]></bio>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>1</id>
		<name>Raul Anaya</name>
		<firstname>Raul</firstname>
		<lastname>Anaya</lastname>
		<title1>Chief Executive Officer</title1>
		<title2>Central America and the Caribbean</title2>
		<title3/>
		<title4/>
		<smallImg>anaya.jpg</smallImg>
		<speaker/>
		<boardDir/>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>no</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>no</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>no</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>no</sec16exec>
		<profilelink>anaya/index.htm</profilelink>
		<sec16link/>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<p>Raul Anaya has a 20-year professional track at Citi, where he has had a challenging career across various regions and businesses. Currently, Raul Anaya is responsible for all Citi's businesses in Central America and the Caribbean, as Chief Executive Officer, a role he assumed in July 2008. His geographic leadership extends across the Global Consumer Group (Retail Banking, Cards, and Consumer Finance); Institutional Clients Group, (Fixed Income, Currencies and Commodities, Equities, Investment Banking, Corporate and Commercial Banking, and Transaction Services) and Global Wealth Management, within this region. Appointed in January 2008, Raul also acts as member of the Board of Directors of Banco de Chile.</p>
			<p>Previous to this, Raul Anaya was the Chief Executive Officer of Latin America, Citigroup Global Consumer Group. He was responsible for Consumer Operations - Retail Banking, Cards, and Consumer Finance. Mr. Anaya was named to his position in December 2005. He had served as Retail Head for Latin America from February 2005.</p>
			<p>Earlier, Mr. Anaya was Executive Director in Charge of Consumer Assets at Banamex in Mexico, where he was responsible for Mortgages, Personal Loans, and Auto Financing from August 2003 to January 2005. Prior to this position, he was the Divisional Director in Charge of the Center Metropolitan Retail Banking Division at Banamex.</p>
			<p>From May 1999 to January 2002 Mr. Anaya was Chairman and CEO of Banco Bansud S.A. (formerly a wholly owned subsidiary of Banamex) in Argentina.</p>
			<p>Mr. Anaya joined the organization at the Banamex New York Agency in October 1987, and subsequently held the positions of General Manager of Banamex Los Angeles Agency, Executive VP of the Corporate and International Banking Division at California Commerce Bank, General Manager of Banamex Houston Agency, and General Manager of Banamex New York Agency - responsible for the U.S. and Canada offices.</p>
			<p>Mr. Anaya was Member of the Board of Directors of California Commerce Bank from 1996 to 2001.</p>
			]]></bio>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>91</id>
		<name>Robert A. Annibale</name>
		<firstname>Robert A.</firstname>
		<lastname>Annibale</lastname>
		<title1>Global Director</title1>
		<title2>Citi Community Development and Microfinance</title2>
		<smallImg>annibale.jpg</smallImg>
		<speaker>yes</speaker>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>no</bdc>
		<speakerInfo>
			<highlights>
				<link/>
			</highlights>
			<categories>
				<category>Corporate Citizenship and Governance</category>
				<category>Market Insights</category>
			</categories>
			<topic>
				<topicname>How Microfinance Weathered the Economic Downturn</topicname>
				<topicname>Financial Inclusion</topicname>
			</topic>
			<travels>
				<place>New York</place>
				<place>London</place>
			</travels>
		</speakerInfo>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<p>As Global Director of Citi Community Development (CCD), Bob manages Citi's partnerships with global, national and local organizations to support community development. CCD's work focuses on responsible finance through financial capability and asset building; neighborhood preservation and revitalization; access to college education; and small business and microenterprise development.  Working with Citi businesses and community partners, Citi strives to develop appropriate, innovative and sustainable products and services that contribute to expanding access to financial services.</p>
			<p>Bob also directs Citi Microfinance, which is globally responsible for Citi's commercial relationships with microfinance institutions, networks and investors working across businesses and geographies to expand access to financial services in underserved communities.  </p>
			<p>Since joining Citi in 1982, Bob has held a number of senior treasury, risk and corporate positions in Athens, Bahrain, Kenya, London and New York.  He has served on many external boards and councils, including the Board of Advisors for the United Nations Commission on Legal Empowerment of the Poor.  He currently is a member of the Advisory Council of the Institute of Commonwealth Studies at the University of London and the Policy Committee of the Centre for the Study of African Economies at the University of Oxford.  He represents Citi on the Board of the Microfinance Information Exchange, the Council of Microfinance Equity Funds, the Small Enterprise Education and Promotion (SEEP) Network, the Microfinance Network and the Executive Committee of CGAP (World Bank).  </p>
			<p>Bob completed his BA degrees in History and Political Science at Vassar College, in New York, and his Masters Degree in African Studies (History) at the University of London, School of Oriental and African Studies.  </p>
			]]></bio>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>2</id>
		<name>Shirish Apte</name>
		<firstname>Shirish</firstname>
		<lastname>Apte</lastname>
		<title1>Co-Chairman</title1>
		<title2>Asia Pacific Banking</title2>
		<title3/>
		<title4/>
		<smallImg>apte.jpg</smallImg>
		<speaker>yes</speaker>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>yes</bdc>		
		<executivecommittee>none</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>no</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>yes</sec16exec>
		<profilelink>apte/index.htm</profilelink>
		<sec16link>apte/holdings.htm</sec16link>
		<speakerInfo>
			<highlights>
				<link/>
			</highlights>
			<categories>
				<category>The Global Economic Landscape</category>
				<category>Market Insights</category>
			</categories>
			<topic>
				<topicname>Asia: The Next Growth Region</topicname>
				<topicname>India Emergence</topicname>
			</topic>
			<travels>
				<place>Singapore</place>
			</travels>
		</speakerInfo>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<p>Shirish Apte is Co-Chairman of Asia Pacific Banking. From 2009-2011, he was Chief Executive Officer of Citi Asia Pacific with direct responsibility for South Asia, including Australia, India and ASEAN countries.</p>
			<p>Prior to that, Mr. Apte served as CEO of Citi's Central & Eastern European Region, which includes some of the fastest-growing emerging markets.</p>
			<p>Previously, Mr. Apte was CEO of Central & Eastern Europe, Middle East & Africa (CEEMEA), Citi Markets & Banking, and before that, he was Country Manager and Deputy President of Citibank Handlowy, Poland. Mr. Apte was instrumental in Citigroup acquiring Bank Handlowy, Poland in 2000 and led the merger of Bank Handlowy into Citigroup.</p> 
			<p>Mr. Apte has more than 28 years experience with Citi, starting as Relationship Manager with Citibank India. He held various assignments in Corporate Banking, Risk Management and Corporate Finance Investment Banking before becoming Markets & Banking Head in India. Mr. Apte moved to London in 1993 as one of the senior Risk Managers for the group before becoming Corporate Finance Head for CEEMEA, including India.</p> 
			<p>Mr. Apte is a Chartered Accountant from the Institute of Chartered Accountants in England and has an MBA from London Business School. He is Citi's Senior Statesman at the London Business School.</p>
			]]></bio>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>96</id>
		<name>Francisco Aristeguieta</name>
		<firstname>Francisco</firstname>
		<lastname>Aristeguieta</lastname>
		<title1>Chief Executive Officer</title1>
		<title2>Latin America </title2>
		<title3/>
		<smallImg>aristeguieta.jpg</smallImg>
		<speaker>yes</speaker>
		<opc>yes</opc>
		<bdc>no</bdc>		
		<speakerInfo>
			<highlights>
				<link/>
			</highlights>
			<categories>
				<category>Market Insights</category>
				<category>The Future of Banking</category>
			</categories>
			<topic>
				<topicname>Business Opportunities in Latin America</topicname>
				<topicname>Innovation in Latin America</topicname>
			</topic>
			<travels>
				<place>Bogota</place>
			</travels>
		</speakerInfo>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<p>Francisco A. Aristeguieta is the Chief Executive Officer of Citi Latin America, responsible for all businesses and products in the region, excluding Mexico. </p>
			<p>Previously, Mr. Aristeguieta was Latin America and Mexico Region Head of Global Transaction Services (GTS). Before holding this role, he served as CEO of Colombia and the Andean Region Cluster, which consists of Venezuela, Peru, Ecuador and Bolivia.  Prior to that, Mr. Aristeguieta was the Citi Country Officer for the firm in Venezuela and before that, in Ecuador. </p>
			<p>Mr. Aristeguieta joined Citi Venezuela in 1994 as Vice President and Senior Relationship Manager for the Corporate Bank. In 1997 he became Head for the Corporate Bank, Financial Institutions and Public Sector for Citi Venezuela.</p>
			<p>Mr. Aristeguieta is a member of GTS' Executive Committee and of the Institutional Clients Group (ICG) Global Management Committee. He is a member of the ICG Latin America Executive Committee and the Comité de Direccion of Banco Nacional de Mexico (Banamex). In addition, he serves on the Board of Directors of Junior Achievement Americas and served in the past on several other boards, including the Banking Associations and American Chambers of Commerce of Ecuador, Colombia and Venezuela, and the Consejo de Empresas Americanas de Colombia (CEA). He was also Chairman of the Board of Colfondos in Colombia.</p>
			<p>Before joining Citi, Mr. Aristeguieta worked for Vestcor Partners where he was responsible for capital markets origination in Venezuela, Colombia and Brazil. Before that, he worked for Petroleos de Venezuela in its Project Finance Group. </p>
			<p>Mr. Aristeguieta holds an M.B.A. from Brunel University in London under a British Council scholarship, and both a graduate degree in finance and banking and an undergraduate degree in business administration, from the Universidad Metropolitana in Caracas, Venezuela.</p>

			]]></bio>
	</profile>
	
	<profile>
		<id>4</id>
		<name>C. Michael Armstrong</name>
		<firstname>C. Michael</firstname>
		<lastname>Armstrong</lastname>
		<title1>Chairman - Board of Trustees, Johns Hopkins Medicine, Health System Corporation and Hospital</title1>
		<title2/>
		<title3/>
		<title4/>
		<boardDir>no</boardDir>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>no</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>no</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>no</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>no</sec16exec>
		<profilelink/>
		<sec16link/>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>116</id>
		<name>Javier Arrigunaga</name>
		<firstname>Javier</firstname>
		<lastname>Arrigunaga</lastname>
		<title1>Chief Executive Officer</title1>
		<title2>Mexico</title2>
		<title3/>
		<smallImg>arrigunaga.jpg</smallImg>
		<speaker>yes</speaker>
		<opc>yes</opc>
		<bdc>no</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>no</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>no</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>no</sec16exec>
		<speakerInfo>
			<highlights>
				<link/>
			</highlights>
			<categories>
				<category>Market Insights</category>
			</categories>
			<topic>
				<topicname>Financial Regulation in Mexico &amp; Latin America</topicname>
				<topicname>The Evolution of Banking in Mexico &amp; Latin America</topicname>
			</topic>
			<travels>
				<place>Mexico</place>
			</travels>
		</speakerInfo>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<p>Javier Arrigunaga was named Chief Executive Officer of Mexico for Citi following service as CEO of Grupo Financiero Banamex.</p> 
			<p>Javier is a member of the Banamex Executive Commission. He is director of the board of Grupo Financiero Banamex and Banco Nacional de Mexico, Acciones y Valores Banamex (Brokerage House), Aeromexico (Mexico’s flagship airline) and the Universidad Iberoamericana.</p> 
			<p>Before joining Citi/Banamex in 2002, Javier Arrigunaga was the Ambassador of Mexico to the OECD in Paris. He previously worked for 15 years at Banco de Mexico (Mexico’s Central Bank) where he held different positions. Javier was part of the team responsible for the negotiation of the international assistance to support Mexico during the macroeconomic crisis during 1995 and from 1997 he was CEO of the Deposit Insurance Agency responsible for managing the Mexican Banking Crisis.</p> 
			<p>He holds a law degree from the Universidad Iberoamericana and a master's in law and finance from Columbia University.</p> 


			]]></bio>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>5</id>
		<name>George Awad</name>
		<firstname>George</firstname>
		<lastname>Awad</lastname>
		<title1>Chief Executive Officer</title1>
		<title2>Consumer Finance for Citi Holdings</title2>
		<title3/>
		<title4/>
		<smallImg>awad.jpg</smallImg>
		<opc>no</opc><bdc>no</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>no</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>no</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>no</sec16exec>
		<profilelink>awad/index.htm</profilelink>
		<sec16link/>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<p>George Awad is Chief Executive Officer, Consumer Finance for Citi Holdings.  His responsibilities include: Retail and Private Label Cards, The Student Loan Corporation and the Auto Finance business in North America as well as the European Consumer Banks. He is also a member of Citi's Senior Leadership Committee.</p>
			<p>He previously held the positions of Chief Executive Officer, North America Cards and Chief Executive Officer of Citi's Global Consumer Group in Europe, Middle East and Africa (EMEA). George brings strong growth and turnaround leadership.  In North America, the cards businesses are delivering record revenues while the strong focus on risk management is delivering billions of dollars in lower credit losses.  In EMEA, George managed the German Retail Bank through the successful divesture resulting in a multi billion dollar gain. Also in EMEA, George and his team delivered record organic earnings growth by divesting seven subscale platforms and turning around six others; the region ended the fourth quarter 2007 with its highest revenue ever.</p>
			<p>George joined Citi after an 18-year career at General Electric Company, where he was Senior Vice President of Sales and Marketing at GE Money. During this time, he helped lead GE Money to double-digit organic growth for seven consecutive years and drive net income growth from US$700 million in 2000 to over US$3 billion in 2005. His previous positions at General Electric included general management, business development, and sales roles throughout the U.S., China, France, Japan, Singapore, and the U.K.</p>
			<p>George holds a B.S. in civil engineering from the American University of Beirut and an M.B.A. from the University of Pittsburgh, Katz Graduate School of Business. He has more than 20 years of consumer product and financial services experience in Europe, Asia, and the U.S.</p>
			]]></bio>
	</profile>
	
	<profile>
		<id>6</id>
		<name>Suneel Bakhshi</name>
		<firstname>Suneel</firstname>
		<lastname>Bakhshi</lastname>
		<title1>Chief Risk Officer, Commercial Bank</title1>
		<title2/>
		<title3/>
		<title4/>
		<smallImg>bakhshi.jpg</smallImg>
		<speaker>yes</speaker>
		<opc>no</opc><bdc>no</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>no</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>no</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>no</sec16exec>
		<profilelink>bakhshi/index.htm</profilelink>
		<sec16link/>
		<speakerInfo>
			<highlights>
				<link/>
			</highlights>
			<categories>
				<category>Market Insights</category>
			</categories>
			<topic>
				<topicname/>
			</topic>
			<travels>
				<place>London</place>
			</travels>
		</speakerInfo>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<p>Suneel Bakhshi is responsible for Risk Management for the Commercial Bank. Prior to this role, Suneel was Chief Risk Officer of the Global Consumer Group and Citibank N.A.</p>
			<p>In the five years before being appointed to Risk in 2008, Suneel has held several senior Banking roles, heading Citi's Global Commercial Bank, the Emerging Markets Corporate Bank, as well as Emerging Markets Local Finance for Citigroup International.</p>
			<p>Prior to his Banking assignments, over a twenty year international Trading career, Suneel led Sales and Trading for CEEMEA (Central and Eastern Europe, Middle East and Africa), Derivatives Trading for both Citibank and Citigroup in Western Europe, Derivatives for Citibank in Japan, and Risk Treasury for Citibank in the Middle East.</p>
			<p>Suneel has represented Citibank on the Board of the International Swaps and Derivatives Association as well as on the Derivatives Consultative Committee of the Bank of England. Since 2002 he has continued to serve on the Board of the RamaKrishna Mission Hospital in Haridwar, India, a non-denominational charity hospital.</p>
			<p>Educational qualifications include an MBA from Queen's University in Canada, and a B.Comm (Honours) degree from Shri Ram College of Commerce, Delhi University, India.</p>
			]]></bio>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>7</id>
		<name>Ajay Banga</name>
		<firstname>Ajay</firstname>
		<lastname>Banga</lastname>
		<title1>Chief Executive Officer</title1>
		<title2>Asia Pacific</title2>
		<title3>Citi</title3>
		<title4/>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>no</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>no</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>no</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>no</sec16exec>
		<profilelink/>
		<sec16link/>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>8</id>
		<name>Alain J.P. Belda</name>
		<firstname>Alain J.P.</firstname>
		<lastname>Belda</lastname>
		<title1>Managing Director, Warburg Pincus</title1>
		<title2/>
		<title3/>
		<title4/>
		<smallImg>belda.jpg</smallImg>
		<boardDir>yes</boardDir>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>no</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>no</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>yes</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>no</sec16exec>
		<profilelink/>
		<sec16link>belda/holdings.htm</sec16link>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<ul class="list" style="width: 355px;">
				<li>Managing Director, Warburg Pincus - August 2009 to present</li>
				<li>Chairman, Alcoa Inc. - 2001 to 2010</li>
				<li>Chief Executive Officer - 1999 to 2008</li>
				<li>President - 1997 to 2001</li>
				<li>Chief Operating Officer - 1997 to 1999</li>
				<li>Vice Chairman - 1995 to 1997</li>
				<li>Executive Vice President - 1994 to 1995</li>
				<li>President, Alcoa (Latin America) - 1991 to 1994</li>
				<li>Vice President - 1982 to 1991</li>
				<li>President, Alcoa Aluminio SA (Brazil) - 1979 to 1994</li>
				<li>Director of Citigroup (or predecessor) since 1997</li>
				<li>Other Directorships: IBM Corporation and Renault</li>
				<li>Previous Directorships within the last five years: E.I. du Pont de Nemours and Company and Alcoa Inc.</li>
				<li>Other Activities: Brazil Project Advisory Board (Co-Chair) at The Woodrow Wilson International Center for Scholars, The Business Council (member), Business Roundtable (member), World Business Council for Sustainable Development (member), and World Economic Forum - International Business Council (member)</li>
			</ul>
			]]></bio>		
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>9</id>
		<name>Hamid Biglari</name>
		<firstname>Hamid</firstname>
		<lastname>Biglari</lastname>
		<title1>Head of Emerging Markets and Content</title1>
		<title2>Vice Chairman</title2>
		<title3>Citicorp</title3>
		<title4/>
		<smallImg>biglari.jpg</smallImg>
		<speaker>yes</speaker>
		<opc>yes</opc>
		<bdc>no</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>none</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>no</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>no</sec16exec>
		<profilelink>biglari/index.htm</profilelink>
		<sec16link/>
		<speakerInfo>
			<highlights>
				<link/>
			</highlights>
			<categories>
				<category>The Global Economic Landscape</category>
			</categories>
			<topic>
				<topicname>Evolution of the Global Financial Services Landscape</topicname>
				<topicname>Impact of Globalization on Financial Services</topicname>
			</topic>
			<travels>
				<place>New York</place>
			</travels>
		</speakerInfo>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<p>Hamid Biglari is Vice Chairman of Citicorp, the strategic operating arm of Citigroup. He has two executive responsibilities. As Head of Emerging Markets, he has responsibility for prioritization, resource allocation and portfolio optimization globally across emerging markets countries, working closely with Citi's regional CEOs. As Head of Content, he has responsibility for driving and leading Citigroup's intellectual content generation, including its various Research departments.</p>
			<p>Prior to that role, Mr. Biglari held a number of senior roles within the organization, including Chief Operating Officer of Citigroup's Institutional Clients Group, which represents the global investment banking and trading and sales arm of Citigroup/Citicorp.</p>
			<p>Prior to joining Citigroup, Mr. Biglari was a Partner at McKinsey & Company, the international management consulting firm, where he co-led the Firm's investment banking consulting practice. His experience base spans the entire spectrum of consumer and wholesale financial services.</p>
			<p>Prior to that, he was a theoretical research physicist at Princeton University's Plasma Physics Laboratory, the nation's leading center for controlled thermonuclear fusion research.</p>
			<p>He is a member of the Council on Foreign Relations and a member of the Board of Trustees of the Asia Society. In 2009, Mr. Biglari was awarded the Ellis Island Medal of Honor, given for outstanding contributions by immigrants to the United States.</p>
			<p>Dr. Biglari holds Ph.D. and M.S. degrees in astrophysical sciences from Princeton University. Prior to that, he received a B.S. in applied physics and a B.A. in mathematics from Cornell University, both with Distinction.</p>
			]]></bio>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>10</id>
		<name>Stephen Bird</name>
		<firstname>Stephen</firstname>
		<lastname>Bird</lastname>
		<title1>Chief Executive Officer</title1>
		<title2>Asia Pacific</title2>
		<title3/>
		<title4/>
		<smallImg>bird.jpg</smallImg>
		<speaker>yes</speaker>
		<opc>yes</opc>
		<bdc>no</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>none</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>no</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>yes</sec16exec>
		<profilelink>bird/index.htm</profilelink>
		<sec16link>bird/holdings.htm</sec16link>
		<speakerInfo>
			<highlights>
				<link/>
			</highlights>
			<categories>
				<category>The Global Economic Landscape</category>
				<category>Market Insights</category>
			</categories>
			<topic>
				<topicname>Asia: The Next Growth Region</topicname>
				<topicname>China Rising</topicname>
			</topic>
			<travels>
				<place>Hong Kong</place>
			</travels>
		</speakerInfo>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<p>Stephen Bird is Chief Executive Officer of Citi Asia Pacific, responsible for all the company’s business lines across 17 markets in the region from Korea in the North to Australia in the South including China and India. He is a member of the Citi Global Operating Committee.</p>
			<p>Mr. Bird was previously joint CEO of Citi Asia Pacific with responsibility for North Asia. From 2006 to 2008, he was Head of Consumer Banking in Asia Pacific, responsible for the Retail Banking, Credit Cards and Consumer Lending businesses with over 30 million customer accounts across the region.  
			<p>Prior to that, he served four years in Citi Japan as CEO of Credit Cards and Consumer Finance. Earlier, he was Head of Operations & Technology for Citi Latin America, covering all of Citi’s businesses in 23 countries.</p> 
			<p>Mr. Bird joined Citi in 1998 in Singapore as the Asia Pacific Head for Operations & Technology. He successfully built Citi’s technological and operational capability to deliver outstanding customer service and market-leading internet and mobile capability. Citi’s award-winning e-commerce capabilities continue to win customer and industry recognition. He relocated to Latin America in 2001.</p>
			<p>Prior to Citi, Mr. Bird held senior management positions in GE Capital and British Steel in the United Kingdom. At GE Capital, Mr. Bird launched its 6 Sigma program and established a client focus and continual improvement culture in GE Capital Fleet Services before becoming its Director of U.K. Operations. He is a recipient of GE’s “Pinnacle Award” for pioneering work in establishing joint commercial ventures between GE Capital’s different businesses serving the financial needs of the U.K. automotive sector. </p>
			<p>Mr. Bird is an alumnus of Citi’s Chairman’s Executive Forum and GE’s European Advanced Leadership program. He is a graduate of University College Cardiff with an M.B.A. in economics & finance.</p>
			]]></bio>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>92</id>
		<name>Willem Buiter</name>
		<firstname>Willem</firstname>
		<lastname>Buiter</lastname>
		<title1>Citi Chief Economist</title1>
		<smallImg>buiter.jpg</smallImg>
		<speaker/>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>no</bdc>
		<speakerInfo>
			<highlights>
				<link/>
			</highlights>
			<categories>
				<category>The Global Economic Landscape</category>
			</categories>
			<topic>
				<topicname/>
			</topic>
			<travels>
				<place/>
			</travels>
		</speakerInfo>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<p>Willem Buiter CBE, FBA, is Chief Economist of Citi since January 2010.  His previous appointment was Professor of Political Economy at the LSE.  He has a BA from Cambridge and a Ph. D. from Yale. He has held academic appointments at Princeton, the University of Bristol, the LSE, Yale and Cambridge.</p>
			<p>He has published on macroeconomics, monetary and exchange rate management, financial markets and institutions, fiscal policy, social security reform, economic development, emerging markets and transition economics.</p>
			<p>He was a member of the Monetary Policy Committee of the Bank of England from 1997 till 2000 and Chief Economist and Special Counselor to the President at the EBRD from 2000 till 2005.</p>
			<p>He has been an advisor to the IMF, the World Bank, other multilateral institutions, national governments and central banks. He has been a Senior Advisor to Goldman Sachs International and a member of the Academic Advisory Board of APG Investments.  He wrote <a href="http://blogs.ft.com/maverecon/" target="_blank">Maverecon</a>, an economics blog, for The Financial Times.</p>
			]]></bio>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>88</id>
		<name>Andrew Butcher</name>
		<firstname>Andrew</firstname>
		<lastname>Butcher</lastname>
		<title1>Managing Director</title1>
		<title2>Regional Head of Operations and Technology</title2>
		<title3>Citi Asia Pacific</title3>
		<smallImg>butcher.jpg</smallImg>
		<speaker>yes</speaker>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>no</bdc>
		<speakerInfo>
			<highlights>
				<link/>
			</highlights>
			<categories>
				<category>The Future of Banking</category>
			</categories>
			<topic>
				<topicname>Innovation in Banking</topicname>
			</topic>
			<travels>
				<place>Hong Kong</place>
			</travels>
		</speakerInfo>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<p>Andrew Butcher is Head of Operations and Technology for Citi in Asia Pacific and is a member of Citi's Asia Pacific Executive Committee.</p>
			<p>In this role, he is responsible for Citi's operations, technology and shared services in the region, supporting all of Citi's businesses: Consumer Banking, Global Cards, Global Transaction Services, Markets and Global Wealth Management.</p>
			<p>Prior to his current appointment in June 2008, Mr. Butcher was Head of Operations and Technology for Citi's Institutional Clients Group in Asia Pacific, responsible for corporate and investment banking operations in 16 countries, regional processing centers in Penang, Kuala Lumpur, Shanghai, Singapore and Sydney and Technology development in Singapore, Hong Kong, Australia and India.</p>
			<p>Mr. Butcher joined Salomon Brothers, a predecessor company of Citi, in London in 1988. He held various positions in the firm's Operations and Strategic Planning divisions in London and Tokyo before relocating to Hong Kong in 1992. He was responsible for establishing many of the firm's regional operations, including Beijing, Bangkok, Delhi, Kuala Lumpur and Jakarta.</p>
			<p>He was appointed Director, Business Planning and Administration in 1997, Chief Administrative Officer in 1999 and Managing Director in 2000, responsible for regional management of Salomon Smith Barney Asia Pacific infrastructure, including Finance, Operations, Technology, Human Resources, Corporate Services and Public Affairs.</p>
			]]></bio>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>13</id>
		<name>Don Callahan</name>
		<firstname>Don</firstname>
		<lastname>Callahan</lastname>
		<title1>Chief Administrative Officer</title1>
		<title2>Chief Operations &amp; Technology Officer</title2>
		<title3>Citigroup</title3>
		<title4/>
		<smallImg>callahan.jpg</smallImg>
		<speaker/>
		<opc>yes</opc>
		<bdc>no</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>none</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>no</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>yes</sec16exec>
		<profilelink>callahan/index.htm</profilelink>
		<sec16link>callahan/holdings.htm</sec16link>
		<speakerInfo>
			<highlights>
				<link/>
			</highlights>
			<categories>
				<category>The Future of Banking</category>
			</categories>
			<topic>
				<topicname>No Topic Listed</topicname>
			</topic>
			<travels>
				<place>New York</place>
			</travels>
		</speakerInfo>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<p>Don Callahan is the Chief Administrative Officer and Chief Operations & Technology Officer for Citi. Mr. Callahan also oversees Corporate Branding and Shared Services. He joined Citi in October 2007.</p>
			<p>Prior to joining Citi, Mr. Callahan was a Managing Director and Head of Marketing Strategy for the Investment Banking Division at Credit Suisse. He was a member of the Investment Banking Management Committee, the Investment Banking Management Council, and the Chairman's Board.</p>
			<p>From 1993 to 2006, Mr. Callahan worked at Morgan Stanley, where he initially served in numerous roles in strategy, business development, and client technology in the Equities Division. Mr. Callahan became Head of Business Management for the Institutional Clients Group.</p>
			<p>Prior to joining Morgan Stanley, Mr. Callahan held a number of management positions at International Business Machines Corporation (IBM). His last position there was Director of Strategy for IBM Japan.</p>
			<p>He serves on the boards of Manhattanville College, the Salisbury School, the American Red Cross of Greater New York and the New York Hall of Science.</p>
			<p>Mr. Callahan received a B.A. in history from Manhattanville College and, as a post-graduate, attended Oxford University, where he read history.</p>
			]]></bio>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>112</id>
		<name>Lisa M. Caputo</name>
		<firstname>Lisa</firstname>
		<lastname>Caputo</lastname>
		<title1>Managing Director and Senior Banker, Public Sector Group, Citi</title1>
		<title2>Founder and Chairman, Women &amp; Co., Citi</title2>
		<title3/>
		<smallImg>caputo.jpg</smallImg>
		<speaker/>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>no</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>no</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>no</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>no</sec16exec>
		<speakerInfo>
			<highlights>
				<link/>
			</highlights>
			<categories>
				<category>Client Trends and Insights</category>
			</categories>
			<topic>
				<topicname>Women's Economic Trends</topicname>
				<topicname>Women's Financial Needs</topicname>
			</topic>
			<travels>
				<place>New York</place>
			</travels>
		</speakerInfo>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<p>Lisa Caputo assumed her current role as Managing Director and Senior Banker of the Public Sector Group of Citi's Investment Bank in September 2010. Most recently, Lisa was Executive Vice President, Global Marketing and Corporate Affairs since 2007.  Lisa founded Citi's leading women's financial services business, Women & Co., and is currently its Chairman after serving as CEO from 2000-2010.  She is the Co-Head of Women4Citi, Citi's women's initiative program.</p>
  			<p>As Citi's Executive Vice President, Global Marketing and Corporate Affairs, Lisa directed and managed a global integrated marketing, corporate communications/public affairs and community relations strategy for Citi while also serving as the company's Global Chief Marketing Officer. She oversaw the marketing, advertising, branding, consumer insights, media, online marketing, sponsorships, external and internal communications, media relations, issues management, executive communications and community relations operations globally at Citi.  </p>
			<p>Lisa started Women & Co. when she first joined Citi.  Women & Co. helps women build their financial knowledge and create financial strategies through access to financial education, resources and tools, and a community of financially-minded women.  </p>
			<p>Lisa was Chief Marketing and Community Relations Officer for all of Citi's consumer businesses globally from 2005-2007.  From 2003-2005, Lisa was Senior Managing Director, Business Operations and Planning, Citi's Global Consumer Group.  Before joining Citi, Lisa held senior executive marketing and communications positions with The Walt Disney Company and The CBS Corporation. </p>
			<p>Lisa also spent over a decade in the public sector.  She served as Deputy Assistant to the President and Press Secretary to First Lady Hillary Rodham Clinton at the White House during President William J. Clinton's first term.  She held the same job through the 1992 Clinton-Gore campaign and the presidential transition.  Prior to that, Lisa ran Al Gore's media operations at the 1992 Democratic National Convention and was the Press Secretary to U.S. Senator Tim Wirth and to U.S. Representative Bob Traxler.  She also was the National Issues Press Secretary for the 1988 Dukakis-Bentsen presidential campaign.</p>
			<p>Lisa has received several recognitions for accomplishments in marketing and communications.  She is also a member of the Board of Directors of Best Buy Co., Inc., The Sesame Workshop, WNET Channel 13, New Visions for Public Schools, and the Creative Coalition.  She sits on the International Steering Committee of FINCA International, Women@NBCU Advisory Board, the Advisory Council on Media Relations for Brown University, and The New York Presbyterian Sloane Hospital Advisory Committee.</p>
			<p>Lisa graduated magna cum laude from Brown University (A.B. political science and French) and received a Master's degree in Journalism with highest distinction from Northwestern University.</p>
			]]></bio>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>98</id>
		<name>Jonathan Clements</name>
		<firstname>Jonathan</firstname>
		<lastname>Clements</lastname>
		<title1>Director of Financial Education</title1>
		<title2>Citi Personal Wealth Management</title2>
		<smallImg>clements.jpg</smallImg>
		<speaker>yes</speaker>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>no</bdc>
		<speakerInfo>
			<highlights>
				<link/>
			</highlights>
			<categories>
				<category>Client Trends and Insights</category>
			</categories>
			<topic>
				<topicname>Consumer &amp; Investor Financial Insights</topicname>
				<topicname>Personal Finance</topicname>
			</topic>
			<travels>
				<place>New York</place>
			</travels>
		</speakerInfo>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<p>Jonathan Clements is Director of Financial Education for Citi Personal Wealth Management.</p>
			<p>Born in London, England, Jonathan is a graduate of Emmanuel College, Cambridge University. Before joining Citi in 2008, he spent 18 years at <i>The Wall Street Journal</i>, where he was the newspaper's personal-finance columnist.</p>
			<p>Jonathan has written four books, the latest of which is "The Little Book of Main Street Money," published in 2009 by John Wiley & Sons.</p>
			]]></bio>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>80</id>
		<name>Timothy C. Collins</name>
		<firstname>Timothy C.</firstname>
		<lastname>Collins</lastname>
		<title1>Chairman of Investment Committee, Ripplewood Holdings LLC</title1>
		<title2/>
		<title3/>
		<title4/>
		<smallImg>collins.jpg</smallImg>
		<boardDir>yes</boardDir>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>no</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>no</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>yes</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>no</sec16exec>
		<profilelink/>
		<sec16link>collins/holdings.htm</sec16link>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<ul class="list" style="width: 355px;">
				<li>Chairman of Investment Committee, Ripplewood Holdings L.L.C. - 2010 to present</li>
				<li>CEO and Senior Managing Director, Ripplewood Holdings L.L.C. - 1995 to 2010</li>
				<li>Chairman of the Investment & Strategy Committee of RHJ International S.A. - 2009 to present</li>
				<li>Co-CEO & Senior Managing Director, RHJ International SA - 2007 to 2009</li>
				<li>CEO & Senior Managing Director, RHJ International S.A. - 2005 to 2007</li>
				<li>Managing Director, Onex Corporation - 1990 to 1995</li>
				<li>Vice President, Lazard Freres & Co., L.L.C. - 1984 to 1990</li>
				<li>Associate, Booz, Allen & Hamilton, Inc. - 1981 to 1984</li>
				<li>Financial Planning Manager, Cummins Engine Company - 1974 to 1975 and 1978 to 1980</li>
				<li>Director of Citigroup since 2009</li>
				<li>Director of Citibank, N.A. - since 2009 </li>
				<li>Other Directorships: RHJ International S.A., Weather Investments S.p.A., and AEG Power Solutions</li>
				<li>Previous Directorships within the last five years: Readers Digest Association, RSC Holdings Inc., WRC Media Inc., Asbury Automotive Group Inc., Shinsei Bank, Ltd. and Commercial International Bank of Egypt</li>
				<li>Other Activities: Trilateral Commission (member), Yale Divinity School Advisory Board (member), Yale School of Organization and Management Board of Advisors (member), Overseers of the Weill Cornell Medical College (member) , Council on Foreign Relations (member), Tony Blair Faith Foundation (member), Belfer Center for Science and International Affairs (member) and Hotel Carlyle Owners Corporation (member of the Board)</li>
			</ul>
			]]></bio>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>76</id>
		<name>Fernando Concha</name>
		<firstname>Fernando</firstname>
		<lastname>Concha</lastname>
		<title1>Chief Executive Officer</title1>
		<title2>South America Cluster</title2>
		<title3/>
		<title4/>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>no</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>no</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>no</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>no</sec16exec>
		<profilelink/>
		<sec16link/>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>109</id>
		<name>Richard Cookson</name>
		<firstname>Richard</firstname>
		<lastname>Richard Cookson</lastname>
		<title1>Global Chief Investment Officer</title1>
		<title2>Citi Private Bank</title2>
		<title3/>
		<smallImg>cookson.jpg</smallImg>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>no</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>no</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>no</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>no</sec16exec>
		<speaker>yes</speaker>
		<speakerInfo>
			<highlights>
				<link/>
			</highlights>
			<categories>
				<category>The Global Economic Landscape</category>
				<category>Market Insights</category>
				<category>Client Trends and Insights</category>
			</categories>
			<topic>
				<topicname>Global Investment Strategy</topicname>
				<topicname>Emerging Markets</topicname>
			</topic>
			<travels>
				<place>London</place>
			</travels>
		</speakerInfo>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<p>Richard Cookson is the Global Chief Investment Officer of Citi Private Bank, and was appointed in 2010. </p>
			<p>For many years Richard straddled the worlds of journalism and finance. </p>
			<p>He started his career as a bond trader for a Japanese bank before moving to journalism, including a total of almost ten years at The Economist, for which he spent three years as its Japan correspondent and was, before he left for the second time, the paper's international finance editor and founder of the Buttonwood column. </p>
			<p>Between these two stints, he was a global credit strategist at CSFB. </p>
			<p>Before joining Citi Private Bank, Richard was a managing director and global head of asset allocation research for HSBC.</p>
			<p>Richard was educated at New College, Oxford, where he read Philosophy, Politics & Economics.</p>
			]]></bio>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>15</id>
		<name>Michael L. Corbat</name>
		<firstname>Michael L.</firstname>
		<lastname>Corbat</lastname>
		<title1>Chief Executive Officer</title1>
		<title2>Citi Holdings</title2>
		<title3/>
		<title4/>
		<smallImg>corbat.jpg</smallImg>
		<speaker>yes</speaker>
		<opc>yes</opc>
		<bdc>no</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>none</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>no</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>yes</sec16exec>
		<profilelink>corbat/index.htm</profilelink>
		<sec16link>corbat/holdings.htm</sec16link>
		<speakerInfo>
			<highlights>
				<link/>
			</highlights>
			<categories>
				<category>Market Insights</category>
			</categories>
			<topic>
				<topicname/>
			</topic>
			<travels>
				<place>New York</place>
			</travels>
		</speakerInfo>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<p>Michael L. Corbat is CEO of Citi Holdings, and incoming CEO of Europe, Middle East and Africa, beginning in January 2012.</p>
			<p>Mr. Corbat most recently served as the CEO of Citi's Global Wealth Management unit, which comprised Smith Barney and the Citi Private Bank. Prior to this, he was a Managing Director and Head of the Global Corporate Bank and Global Commercial Bank at Citi, a role in which he led the firm's efforts to provide best-in-class financial services to top-tier multi-national corporations and financial institutions around the world.</p>

			<p>Previously, Mr. Corbat was Head of Global Emerging Markets in Markets and Banking, responsible for the origination, trading, and sales of emerging markets fixed income debt. He joined Salomon Brothers, a Citi legacy firm, in 1983 in the Fixed Income Sales Department in Atlanta and has worked in New York City and London.</p>
			<p>In his various advisory and structuring roles, Mr. Corbat has successfully guided clients grappling with significant challenges, such as the bankruptcy of Orange County, California, to sovereign debt restructurings in Ecuador and Uruguay, to being actively involved with many of the activities surrounding the world's largest companies. </p>
			<p>He currently serves on the Board of Directors of EMI, the BritishAmerican Business, Inc. and the Swedish American Chamber of Commerce. </p>
			<p>Born in Bristol, Connecticut, Mr. Corbat earned a bachelor's in economics from Harvard University in 1983.</p>
			]]></bio>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>104</id>
		<name>Sanjiv Das</name>
		<firstname>Sanjiv</firstname>
		<lastname>Das</lastname>
		<title1>President and Chief Executive Officer</title1>
		<title2>CitiMortgage</title2>
		<smallImg>das.jpg</smallImg>
		<speaker>yes</speaker>
		<opc>yes</opc>
		<bdc>no</bdc>
		<speakerInfo>
			<highlights>
				<link/>
			</highlights>
			<categories>
				<category>Market Insights</category>
			</categories>
			<topic>
				<topicname>Foreclosure Prevention Efforts in the U.S.</topicname>
			</topic>
			<travels>
				<place>New York</place>
				<place>St. Louis</place>
			</travels>
		</speakerInfo>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<p>Sanjiv Das is president and chief executive officer of CitiMortgage. After an eight-year tenure with Citi in the 1990s, Mr. Das returned to Citi in July 2008 in this role as head of CitiMortgage.</p> 
			<p>Prior to rejoining Citi, Mr. Das was a managing director in Morgan Stanley's Institutional Securities Group, where he built a best-in-class organization that delivered proprietary content based on fundamental analytics across equity research, trading and investment banking.</p>  
			<p>In his first tenure at Citi, his roles included head of Citi's Global Mortgage Product Group and managing director of Marketing and Product Development for CitiMortgage. He was also general manager of Citibank's Consumer Mortgage Group in Australia and spent time in Citi's Cards operation. </p> 
			<p>Additional experience includes time at Bank One (First USA) as executive vice president in the Mortgage and Home Equity division.</p> 
			<p>Mr. Das holds a B.S. in mathematics from the University of Delhi and an M.B.A. in marketing and finance from the Indian Institute of Management &#150; Ahmedabad.</p>]]></bio>
	</profile>	
	<profile>
		<id>16</id>
		<name>James C. Cowles</name>
		<firstname>James C.</firstname>
		<lastname>Cowles</lastname>
		<title1>Head of EMEA Markets</title1>
		<title2>Institutional Clients Group</title2>
		<title3/>
		<title4/>
		<smallImg>cowles.jpg</smallImg>
		<speaker/>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>no</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>no</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>no</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>no</sec16exec>
		<profilelink>cowles/index.htm</profilelink>
		<sec16link/>
		<speakerInfo>
			<highlights>
				<link/>
			</highlights>
			<categories>
				<category>Market Insights</category>
			</categories>
			<topic>
				<topicname>EMEA Markets Outlook</topicname>
			</topic>
			<travels>
				<place>London</place>
			</travels>
		</speakerInfo>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<p>James C. Cowles is Head of EMEA (Europe, Middle East, Africa) Markets and a Managing Director at Citi. He is also a member of Citi's Senior Leadership Committee.</p>
			<p>Prior to assuming his current position, Jim was Head of Global Equities Products, following a stint as Head of Equities, EMEA for four years. Previous to that he was Head of Global Equity Capital Markets (new issue product) for seven years.</p>
			<p>Jim joined Smith Barney in 1979.  Prior to joining the Equities Division in 1997, Jim's past positions included: Deputy Head of Investment Banking, Head of Real Estate Investment Banking and Commercial Mortgage Trading, Head of Debt Capital Markets and Head of Direct Investments.</p>
			<p>He is a member of EMEA's CitiDifference Steering Committee, which provides management leadership and accountability in the development and execution of EMEA's objectives in diversity.</p>
			<p>Jim graduated Phi Beta Kappa from Denison University in 1977 with a BA in Economics.  He graduated with an MBA from The Wharton School, University of Pennsylvania in 1979.</p>
			]]></bio>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>120</id>
		<name>Alberto Cribiore</name>
		<firstname>Alberto</firstname>
		<lastname>Cribiore</lastname>
		<title1>Vice Chairman</title1> 
		<title2>Institutional Clients Group</title2>
		<title3/>
		<title4/>
		<smallImg>cribiore.jpg</smallImg>
		<speaker/>
		<boardDir/>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>yes</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>no</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>no</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>no</sec16exec>
		<sec16link/>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<p>Alberto Cribiore serves as Vice Chairman of Citi's Institutional Clients Group, which includes the investment and corporate bank as well as all capital market and alternative investment activities.</p>
			<p>Prior to joining Citi, Alberto Cribiore had formed Brera Capital Partners, a global private equity investment firm in 1997. Previously, he was Co-President and Partner at Clayton, Dubilier & Rice, Inc., which he joined in 1985 as one of three equal principal shareholders. Before then, he had been a Senior Vice President at Warner Communications, where he was responsible for mergers, acquisitions and divestitures. Prior to Warner Communication, he was Vice President at IFI International, the international holding company controlled by the Agnelli family. </p>
			<p>Mr. Cribiore is a <i>cum laude</i> graduate of Bocconi University in Milan, Italy and holds degrees in business administration and economics. He has served on the Board of Directors of Merrill Lynch where he served as non executive Chairman, and currently serves as a Director of GAB Robins and various other Brera controlled companies. </p>
			<p>Mr. Cribiore is also an Advisory Director of the Metropolitan Opera Association and Founder and Honorary Chairman of the New York City Chapter of the Bocconi University Alumni Association. He is also a director of the Council for the United States and Italy and a member of the Weill Cornell Medical College Board of Overseers.</p>
			]]></bio>
	</profile>	
	
	<profile>
		<id>97</id>
		<name>Johanna Dee Chua</name>
		<firstname>Johanna</firstname>
		<lastname>Dee Chua</lastname>
		<title1>Managing Director and Head of Asia Pacific</title1>
		<title2>Economic Markets and Analysis</title2>
		<title3>Asia Pacific Citi Investment Research and Analysis</title3>
		<smallImg>deechua.jpg</smallImg>
		<speaker/>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>no</bdc>
		<speakerInfo>
			<highlights>
				<link/>
			</highlights>
			<categories>
				<category>Market Insights</category>
			</categories>
			<topic>
				<topicname/>
			</topic>
			<travels>
				<place/>
			</travels>
		</speakerInfo>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<p>Johanna Chua is Managing Director and Head of Asia-Pacific Economic and Market Analysis at Citi Investment Research and Analysis. Based in Hong Kong, Ms. Chua was formerly the Chief Asia Emerging Market Trading Strategist, responsible for Asian FX, local markets and sovereign credits. Ms. Chua has been ranked No.1 economist for three consecutive years (2006-2008) and No.2 sovereign analyst by Asset magazine. She was ranked No.1 on Sovereign Credit Research by FinanceAsia magazine for eight years (2001-2008), and was part of the team that kept Citi in the No.1 position on fixedincome research in FinanceAsia during the last few years. Prior to working at Citi, Ms. Chua completed her doctorate in economics at Harvard University, and also worked for the Sovereign Strategy group at Lehman Brothers, the Fiscal Policy division at the IMF, as well as conducted academic research with the National Bureau of Economic Research, the Harvard Institute for International Development and the Food Marketing Policy Research Center.</p>
			]]></bio>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>18</id>
		<name>Kenneth T. Derr</name>
		<firstname>Kenneth T.</firstname>
		<lastname>Derr</lastname>
		<title1>Chairman, Retired, Chevron Corporation</title1>
		<title2/>
		<title3/>
		<title4/>
		<boardDir>no</boardDir>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>no</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>no</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>no</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>no</sec16exec>
		<profilelink/>
		<sec16link/>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>85</id>
		<name>Linda Descano</name>
		<firstname>Linda</firstname>
		<lastname>Descano</lastname>
		<title1>Chartered Financial AnalystÂ®</title1>
		<title2>President &amp; CEO, Women &amp; Co., Citi</title2>
		<title3/>
		<title4/>
		<smallImg>descano.jpg</smallImg>
		<speaker>yes</speaker>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>no</bdc>
		<speakerInfo>
			<highlights>
				<link/>
			</highlights>
			<categories>
				<category>Client Trends and Insights</category>
			</categories>
			<topic>
				<topicname>Women's Unique Financial Needs</topicname>
			</topic>
			<travels>
				<place>New York</place>
			</travels>
		</speakerInfo>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<p>Linda is President & CEO of Women & Co., a division of Citi that provides women with financial resources and a community for building their financial knowledge, exchanging financial insights, and accessing tips and tools for creating financial strategies based on the realities of women's financial lives. Linda joined Women & Co. in 2003 as Chief Operating Officer and was appointed as President in 2007 and CEO in 2010.</p>
			<p>Previously, from 1999 through 2002, Linda was a Director and Portfolio Manager in Citi's Private Portfolio Group, where she co-managed customized investment portfolios for individuals and institutions and oversaw the firm's socially responsible investment program. Before that, Linda served as Senior Vice President and Director of Environmental Affairs for Citi predecessor company, Salomon Inc., which she joined in 1994. Prior to embarking on a career in finance, Linda spent several years working in environmental consulting.</p>
			<p>An accomplished speaker, over the course of her career, Linda has spoken at hundreds of conferences on an array of personal finance, investment and leadership topics.  She is a member of several professional associations, including the CFA<SUP>&reg;</SUP> Institute, New York Society of Security Analysts, Financial Women's Association of New York, and New York Women in Communications. Linda also serves as chair of the New York Board of Step Up Women's Network and is a member of Step Up's national board. She is a member of Forbes Executive Women's Board, the Director's Council of the University of Pennsylvania Museum of Archaeology and Anthropology, and the National Organization of Italian American Women.  From 1997 through 1999, Linda chaired the steering committee of the United Nations Financial Institutions Initiative on the Environment. </p>
			<p>Passionate about education and science, Linda has endowed the Nina Anna Scholarship, in honor of her grandmothers, Nina Gaspari Pennachietti and Anna Fortunato Descano. She also supports the Prudy Astrella Legacy Scholarship in honor of her inspirational 5th grade teacher, Ms. Astrella.</p>
			<p>Among her many accomplishments, Linda was the New York recipient of the 2009 Corporate w2wlink Ascendancy Award for her career achievements and her dedication to mentoring women.She was recognized as a Wise Woman by the National Organization of Italian American Women in 2008. She received a Human Rights Leadership Award from Church Women United in 1999 and an Environmental Leadership Award from the United Nations Environment Programme - North America in 1997.</p>
			<p>A native of Philadelphia, Linda attended Temple University and graduated with a bachelor of arts in geology. She holds a Chartered Financial Analyst<SUP>&reg;</SUP> designation.  </p>
			]]></bio>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>19</id>
		<name>John M. Deutch</name>
		<firstname>John M.</firstname>
		<lastname>Deutch</lastname>
		<title1>Institute Professor, Massachusetts Institute of Technology</title1>
		<title2/>
		<title3/>
		<title4/>
		<boardDir>no</boardDir>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>no</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>no</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>no</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>no</sec16exec>
		<profilelink/>
		<sec16link/>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>20</id>
		<name>Terri Dial</name>
		<firstname>Terri</firstname>
		<lastname>Dial</lastname>
		<title1>Citi Senior Advisor</title1>
		<title2/>
		<title3/>
		<title4/>
		<smallImg>dial.jpg</smallImg>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>no</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>no</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>yes</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>no</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>no</sec16exec>
		<profilelink>dial/index.htm</profilelink>
		<sec16link/>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<p>Terri Dial is a senior advisor at Citi. Until January 2010, Terri was Chief Executive Officer of Citi North America Consumer Banking and the Global Head of Consumer Strategy. In her NA Consumer Banking role, she was responsible for consumer and small business banking, Citi branded credit cards, commercial banking, and personal wealth management. In addition, as Global Head of Consumer Strategy, she directed consumer banking strategy worldwide in collaboration with Citi's regional CEOs to ensure consistent application of worldwide standards and best practices in marketing, customer service, innovation, decision analytics, and technology across Citi's Consumer Banking operations. Terri joined Citi in June 2008.</p>
			<p>Prior to joining Citi, Terri served as Group Executive Director of UK Retail Banking and as a member of the Board of Directors at Lloyds TSB Group plc. In this role, she led the business to record customer satisfaction, employee engagement, and sales. Prior to Lloyds TSB, Terri was President and Chief Executive Officer of Wells Fargo Bank, a subsidiary of Wells Fargo & Co. During her nearly 30-year tenure, Terri is credited with building Wells Fargo into one of the most successful banks in the United States. She also has served in various non-executive director roles.</p>
			<p>Terri is a member of the Board of Advisors of the Judge Business School, Cambridge University, England, and the College of Arts and Sciences, Northwestern University, U.S. She is a member of the International Women's Forum and a Director of LookSmart Corp.</p>
			<p>Terri received her B.A. in Political Science from Northwestern University.</p>
			]]></bio>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>103</id>
		<name>Robert DiClemente</name>
		<firstname>Robert</firstname>
		<lastname>DiClemente</lastname>
		<title1>Managing Director</title1>
		<title2>Head, U.S. Economics</title2>
		<title3>Citi Markets and Banking</title3>
		<smallImg>diclemente.jpg</smallImg>
		<speaker/>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>no</bdc>
		<speakerInfo>
			<highlights>
				<link/>
			</highlights>
			<categories>
				<category>The Global Economic Landscape</category>
			</categories>
			<topic>
				<topicname/>
			</topic>
			<travels>
				<place/>
			</travels>
		</speakerInfo>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<p>Robert DiClemente is Managing Director and Chief U.S. Economist for Citigroup, based in New York.</p>
			<p>At Citi and its predecessor firms, Mr. DiClemente has spent three decades analyzing the financial market implications of macroeconomic and policy developments in the United States. His group produces a variety of publications and forecasts for the firm's clients, including Comments on Credit, one of the longest running weekly reports on Wall Street.</p>
			<p>Early in his career, Mr. DiClemente was an assistant to the firm's former chief economist, Henry Kaufman, with a principal focus on monetary and fiscal policies. He was named head of the U.S. Team in 1997.</p>
			<p>Mr. DiClemente received his graduate training in economics at New York University and earned his A.B., magna cum laude, in Economics from Boston University. Among his professional affiliations he is a member, past President and Distinguished Fellow of the Money Marketeers of New York University and member and past Chairman of the Economic Advisory Committee of the Securities Industry and Financial Markets Association.</p>
			]]></bio>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>117</id>
		<name>Brad Dinsmore</name>
		<firstname>Brad</firstname>
		<lastname>Dinsmore</lastname>
		<title1>Group Executive Vice President</title1>
		<title2>Head of Retail Banking, North America Consumer Banking, Citi</title2>
		<title3/>
		<smallImg>dinsmore.jpg</smallImg>
		<speaker/>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>no</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>no</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>no</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>no</sec16exec>
		<speakerInfo>
			<highlights>
				<link/>
			</highlights>
			<categories>
				<category>Future of Banking</category>
				<category>Market Insights</category>
			</categories>
			<topic>
				<topicname>The Future of Retail Banking</topicname>
				<topicname>Maximizing Distribution and Performance</topicname>
				<topicname>Delivering a World Class Customer Experience</topicname>
			</topic>
			<travels>
				<place/>
			</travels>
		</speakerInfo>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<p>Brad Dinsmore is Group Executive Vice President, Head of Retail Banking, North America Consumer Banking, Citi. In this role, he is responsible for Citi's U.S. Regional Banking and Operations, which includes Retail Mortgage Lending, Branch Services and Customer Experience, Distribution Strategy, Sales and Regional Marketing, Performance Management and Citi@Work. </p> 
			<p>Mr. Dinsmore joined Citi in March 2009 and has since grown U.S. branch-based consumer deposits by $12 billion, improved operating efficiency, reduced expenses, and led the national rollout of a $100 million branch and technology enhancement program. He also led a highly successful national initiative to improve customer retention and the customer experience. Mr. Dinsmore works closely with Citi's other consumer businesses, including Personal Banking and Wealth Management, Small Business, Commercial Banking and Citi Cards to deliver comprehensive financial solutions for Citi's retail banking customers.</p> 
			<p>Prior to joining Citi, Mr. Dinsmore spent twenty-one years at Bank of America, where he was responsible for Retail Banking in the Western United States. In this role, he led the turnaround of 2,000 branches, achieving consistent growth and exceeding sales, service, operations and expense objectives. While at Bank of America, Mr. Dinsmore held a number of senior retail bank management positions across Consumer and Small Business Banking, Wealth Management and Marketing, including Head of Consumer and Mortgage Banking Operations in the Southeast from 2001 to 2005. He was also a member of the Management Operating Committee.</p> 
			<p>Mr. Dinsmore is a Member of the Board of the Consumer Bankers Association and a Member of the The Corporate Executive Board.</p> 
			<p>Mr. Dinsmore received his B.S. from California Polytechnic State University and is a graduate of the Pacific Coast Banking School at the University of Washington.</p> 
			]]></bio>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>21</id>
		<name>John L. Donnelly</name>
		<firstname>John L.</firstname>
		<lastname>Donnelly</lastname>
		<title1>Head, Human Resources</title1>
		<title2>Citi</title2>
		<title3/>
		<title4/>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>no</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>no</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>no</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>no</sec16exec>
		<profilelink/>
		<sec16link/>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>90</id>
		<name>Deborah Doyle McWhinney</name>
		<firstname>Deborah</firstname>
		<lastname>Doyle McWhinney</lastname>
		<title1>President</title1>
		<title2>Citi Personal Banking and Wealth Management</title2>
		<smallImg>mcwhinney.jpg</smallImg>
		<speaker>yes</speaker>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>no</bdc>
		<speakerInfo>
			<highlights>
				<link/>
			</highlights>
			<categories>
				<category>Client Trends and Insights</category>
			</categories>
			<topic>
				<topicname>Wealth Management Trends &amp; Insights</topicname>
				<topicname> Changing Face of Retirement</topicname>
			</topic>
			<travels>
				<place>New York</place>
			</travels>
		</speakerInfo>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<p>Deborah McWhinney joined Citi in April 2009 as head of the newly created Citi Personal Wealth Management (CPWM) organization.  The CWPM business provides a broad range of investment services and has the unique ability to serve a variety of customer segments with varying levels of personal assets. </p>
			<p>Prior to joining Citi, she was president of Schwab Institutional, a division of Charles Schwab & Co., Inc., where she helped independent investment advisors grow their businesses more quickly and profitably by building innovative products and services for the fastest growing segment of the financial services industry. She joined Charles Schwab in 2001, and in the following six years served on its management committee, the board of the Charles Schwab Bank, N.A., and the Charles Schwab Foundation board, and was chair of the global risk committee.</p>
			<p>Ms. McWhinney was an executive vice president at Visa International and served as group president for Engage Media Services.  Earlier in her career, McWhinney spent 17 years at Bank of America, where she worked in both corporate and retail banking.</p>
			<p>Ms. McWhinney was appointed by former President George W. Bush to the board of directors of the Securities Investor Protection Corporation (SIPC) in 2002. She also has served on the White House Fellows regional finalist candidate interview panel for the past three years.</p>
 			<p>She serves on the California Institute of Technology's Board of Trustees and is on the Advisory Board of UCSF's Teen and Young Adult Center.</p>
			<p>Ms. McWhinney received her bachelor's degree from the University of Montana and is a graduate of the Pacific Coast Banking School. She currently resides in New York City.</p>
			]]></bio>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>87</id>
		<name>Ana Duarte McCarthy</name>
		<firstname>Ana</firstname>
		<lastname>Duarte McCarthy</lastname>
		<title1>Chief Diversity Officer</title1>
		<title2>Citi</title2>
		<smallImg>duarte.jpg</smallImg>
		<speaker>yes</speaker>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>no</bdc>
		<speakerInfo>
			<highlights>
				<link/>
			</highlights>
			<categories>
				<category>Corporate Citizenship and Governance</category>
			</categories>
			<topic>
				<topicname>Developing Workforce Diversity</topicname>
				<topicname>Women and Global Leadership</topicname>
			</topic>
			<travels>
				<place>New York</place>
			</travels>
		</speakerInfo>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<p>Ana Duarte McCarthy is Chief Diversity Officer, Citi.  Appointed to the role in 2002, Ana is responsible for the development and integration of Citi's workforce diversity strategy for attracting diverse talent, workforce development, fostering an inclusive work environment, and ensuring management accountability.</p>
			<p>Ana joined Citi in 1995.  Her roles at Citi have been within global diversity, including five years as Vice President, Diversity Management, Citibank, Director of Diversity, Global Consumer Group and her current role as head of diversity for the corporation.</p>
			<p>Ana began her career in 1983 within higher education, serving as a bilingual counselor at Passaic Community College.  In 1986 she assumed the role of Director, Higher Education Opportunity Program, New School for Social Research, where she was later appointed Assistant Dean in 1992.  Ana left the New School in 1994 when she joined Kidder, Peabody, Inc. as Assistant Vice President of Compliance and Diversity Programs, where she focused on developing the firm's diversity strategy.</p>
			<p>Ana received her bachelor of arts degree from Lafayette College and a master of education degree from Columbia University.</p>
			<p>Ana serves on the board of directors of the Families and Work Institute and the PhD Project, and the Corporate Advisory Board of the National Council on Research for Women.  She is a member of the National Society of Hispanic MBAs (NSHMBA) and was Chair of the Corporate Advisory Board from 1998-2000.  Among other recognitions, Ana was recently chosen as one of Hispanic Business Magazine's 25 Elite Women for 2009.  In 2007, Ana was recognized as the Ultimate Hispanic Executive by NSHMBA and received Out & Equal Workplace Advocates' Champion Award for her support and advocacy of workplace equality for the gay, lesbian, bisexual and transgender community.  In 2005, she was named to the 2005 YWCA-NYC Academy of Women Leaders.  Ana currently resides in Basking Ridge, New Jersey, with her husband and 13-year-old daughter.</p>
			]]></bio>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>22</id>
		<name>Richard C. S. Evans</name>
		<firstname>Richard C. S.</firstname>
		<lastname>Evans</lastname>
		<title1>Chief Risk Officer</title1>
		<title2>Institutional Clients Group</title2>
		<title3/>
		<title4/>
		<smallImg>evans.jpg</smallImg>
		<speaker>yes</speaker>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>no</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>no</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>no</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>no</sec16exec>
		<profilelink>evans/index.htm</profilelink>
		<sec16link/>
		<speakerInfo>
			<highlights>
				<link/>
			</highlights>
			<categories>
				<category>Market Insights</category>
				<category>Corporate Citizenship and Governance</category>
			</categories>
			<topic>
				<topicname/>
			</topic>
			<travels>
				<place>London</place>
			</travels>
		</speakerInfo>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<p>Richard Evans is Chief Risk Officer for Citi's Institutional Clients Group. Mr. Evans is responsible for managing and tracking the firm's risks across corporate and investment banking, sales and trading, transaction services and alternative investments. He is also responsible for setting strategic risk parameters and managing capital allocation for Citi Institutional Clients Group, as well as ensuring that the firm takes advantage of growth opportunities that meet appropriate risk-return standards.  He is a member of Citi's Senior Leadership Committee.</p>
			<p>Mr. Evans joins Citi from Deutsche Bank AG, where he served most recently as Deputy Chief Risk Officer. That role included running Treasury and Capital Management, Market Risk Management, and Investment Risk Management, including significant involvement in the bank's strategic risk decisions. He was named the "Risk Manager of the Year" in 2004 by Risk Magazine.</p>
			<p>Before joining Deutsche in 2000, Mr. Evans served in a variety of senior roles at JP Morgan over nearly 20 years, his last role being Vice Chairman of JP Morgan's Risk Management Committee and Global Head of Risk Management.</p>
			<p>He was a Board Member of Euroclear SA and Euroclear Plc and Chairman of that Board's Risk Committee. He is also a past Chairman and member of the International Financial Risk Institute (IFRI)'s Executive Committee, a not-for-profit association of Chief Risk Officers from the world's major financial institutions.</p>
			<p>Mr. Evans has an MA in Economics from Gonville and Caius College, Cambridge University.</p>
			]]></bio>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>23</id>
		<name>Pam Flaherty</name>
		<firstname>Pam</firstname>
		<lastname>Flaherty</lastname>
		<title1>President &amp; Chief Executive Officer, Citi Foundation</title1>
		<title2>Director, Corporate Citizenship</title2>
		<title3>Citi</title3>
		<title4/>
		<smallImg>flaherty.jpg</smallImg>
		<speaker>yes</speaker>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>no</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>no</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>no</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>no</sec16exec>
		<profilelink>flaherty/index.htm</profilelink>
		<sec16link/>
		<speakerInfo>
			<highlights>
				<link/>
			</highlights>
			<categories>
				<category>Corporate Citizenship and Governance</category>
			</categories>
			<topic>
				<topicname>Incorporating CSR into Business Strategy</topicname>
				<topicname>Corporate Philanthropy</topicname>
			</topic>
			<travels>
				<place>New York</place>
			</travels>
		</speakerInfo>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<p>Pamela P. Flaherty is President and Chief Executive Officer of the Citi Foundation.  She is also Director of Corporate Citizenship for the company and a member of Citi's Senior Leadership Committee.</p>
			<p>Previously, she managed Citibank's New York branch banking business and served as Citicorp's Senior Human Resources Officer.  She began her career at the company in Citibank's International Banking Group.</p>
			<p>She is Chair of the Board of Trustees of Johns Hopkins University and also participates on the Boards of several non-profit organizations, including the Local Initiatives Support Corporation, Kenyon College, Colonial Williamsburg, and The Nature Conservancy Long Island Chapter.  Pam is also a member of the Council on Foreign Relations.</p>
			<p>She is an honors graduate of Smith College and holds a Masters in International Affairs from Johns Hopkins Nitze School of Advanced International Studies.</p>
			]]></bio>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>107</id>
		<name>Thomas M. Flexner</name>
		<firstname>Thomas M.</firstname>
		<lastname>Flexner</lastname>
		<title1>Global Head of Real Estate</title1>
		<title2>Institutional Clients Group</title2>
		<title4/>
		<smallImg>flexner.jpg</smallImg>
		<speaker>yes</speaker>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>yes</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>no</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>no</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>no</sec16exec>
		<speakerInfo>
			<highlights>
				<link/>
			</highlights>
			<categories>
				<category>Market Insights</category>
			</categories>
			<topic>
				<topicname>Securitization in the Real Estate Market</topicname>
			</topic>
			<travels>
				<place>New York</place>
			</travels>
		</speakerInfo>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<p>Thomas M. Flexner is Citigroup's Global Head of Real Estate and a member of Citi's Institutional Clients Group's Management and Executive Committees. He is responsible for directing worldwide commercial real estate activities across Investment Banking, Commercial Mortgage Finance and Real Estate Private Equity. </p>
			<p>Prior to joining Citi, Tom was Vice Chairman of Bear, Stearns & Co. Inc. and Chairman of its Global Industries Group. He also founded and managed the Commercial Mortgage and the Real Estate, Gaming and Lodging groups at Bear Stearns. </p>
			<p>Tom has worked with various governmental bodies, including the Fed, the U.S. Treasury and the President's Economic Recovery Advisory Board to provide insight and advice on addressing the state of the U.S. commercial real estate economy. Tom is on the board of the Real Estate Roundtable and is actively involved in numerous other industry organizations, and has advised a number of endowments on their real estate investing strategies. He is on the Board of Overseers of the Amos Tuck School of Business, a member of the Directors' Council of Rockefeller University, a Trustee of the Museum of the City of New York and of the Dutchess Land Conservancy, and a member of the Trinity Church Vestry in New York. </p>
			<p>Tom is a graduate of Rhodes College and the Amos Tuck School of Business at Dartmouth College.</p>
			]]></bio>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>24</id>
		<name>James A. Forese</name>
		<firstname>James A.</firstname>
		<lastname>Forese</lastname>
		<title1>Chief Executive Officer</title1>
		<title2>Securities and Banking</title2>
		<title3>Institutional Clients Group</title3>
		<title4/>
		<smallImg>forese.jpg</smallImg>
		<opc>yes</opc>
		<bdc>yes</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>none</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>no</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>no</sec16exec>
		<profilelink>forese/index.htm</profilelink>
		<sec16link/>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<p>James A. Forese is the Chief Executive Officer of Securities and Banking in Citi's Institutional Client Group.</p>
			<p>Mr. Forese is the chair of the Risk Management Committee of the Institutional Clients Group. He is based in New York.</p>
			<p>Prior to his current role, Mr. Forese was the co-head of Global Markets, with responsibility for managing the sales, trading and capital raising activities across Fixed Income, Currencies, Commodities, Equities and Municipal Securities.</p>
			<p>He first joined the firm's Salomon Brothers division in 1985 and was named a Managing Director in 1992.</p>
			<p>Mr. Forese graduated <i>summa cum laude</i> from Princeton University in 1985 with a Bachelor of Science in electrical engineering and computer science. He and his wife, Jennifer, have four sons.</p>
			]]></bio>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>110</id>
		<name>Tina Fordham</name>
		<firstname>Tina</firstname>
		<lastname>Fordham</lastname>
		<title1>Managing Director</title1>
		<title2>Senior Political Analyst</title2>
		<title3>Citi Private Bank</title3>
		<smallImg>fordham.jpg</smallImg>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>no</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>no</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>no</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>no</sec16exec>
		<speaker>yes</speaker>
		<speakerInfo>
			<highlights>
				<link/>
			</highlights>
			<categories>
				<category>The Global Economic Landscape</category>
				<category>Market Insights</category>
			</categories>
			<topic>
				<topicname>Geopolitical Risk</topicname>
				<topicname>Implications of Global Political Developments on Business and Investment</topicname>
			</topic>
			<travels>
				<place>London</place>
			</travels>
		</speakerInfo>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<p>Tina Fordham has over a decade's experience in international policy analysis and political risk assessment. She joined Citi in 2003 and as Senior Political Analyst, focuses on the implications of global political developments for companies and investors.</p>
			<p>Additionally, Ms. Fordham is an Associate Fellow at Chatham House and a member of the World Economic Forum's Global Agenda Council on Strategic Foresight.</p>
			<p>Previously she served as Senior Adviser at the UK Prime Minister's Strategy Unit and was Director of Global Political Risk at the international consultancy Eurasia Group. </p>
			<p>Ms. Fordham has a Master's degree in International Affairs from Columbia University's School for International Public Affairs.</p>
			]]></bio>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>25</id>
		<name>Jane Fraser</name>
		<firstname>Jane</firstname>
		<lastname>Fraser</lastname>
		<title1>Global CEO, Citi Private Bank</title1>
		<title2>Institutional Clients Group</title2>
		<title3/>
		<title4/>
		<smallImg>fraser.jpg</smallImg>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>yes</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>no</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>no</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>no</sec16exec>
		<profilelink>fraser/index.htm</profilelink>
		<sec16link/>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<p>Jane Fraser has been the head of Citi's Global Private Bank since April 2009 and is also responsible for coordinating Citi's Advisory Boards. She was Global Head of Strategy and Mergers & Acquisitions for Citi from October 2007 to May 2009 and also led the firmwide re-engineering effort. She joined Citi in 2004 as the Head of Client Strategy for the Global Banking division. Jane sits on the Management Committee of Citi's Institutional Clients Group.</p>
			<p>Prior to joining Citi, Jane was a Partner at McKinsey & Company where she worked in London and New York for 10 years serving clients in the financial services industry. While at McKinsey she authored a number of articles on globalization and co-authored a book on global strategy, <i>Race for the World</i>, published by HBS Press in 1999. She started her career at Goldman Sachs in the Mergers & Acquisition department in London and then worked for Asesores Bursatiles in Madrid, Spain.</p>
			<p>Jane has an M.B.A. from Harvard Business School and an M.A. in economics from Cambridge University. She is a board member of the Touch Foundation in New York, which runs a medical college and hospital, and works to improve the health care system in Tanzania, Africa.  She is also a member of the Council of Foreign Relations.</p>
			<p>Jane is married with two boys and is based in London.</p>

			]]></bio>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>86</id>
		<name>Alberto Gomez Alcala</name>
		<firstname>Alberto</firstname>
		<lastname>Gomez Alcala</lastname>
		<title1>Economic Research and Communications</title1>
		<title2>Grupo Financiero Banamex-Citigroup</title2>
		<smallImg>alcala.jpg</smallImg>
		<speaker>yes</speaker>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>no</bdc>
		<speakerInfo>
			<highlights>
				<link/>
			</highlights>
			<categories>
				<category>Market Insights</category>
			</categories>
			<topic>
				<topicname>Economic Perspectives on Latin America</topicname>
			</topic>
			<travels>
				<place>Mexico City</place>
			</travels>
		</speakerInfo>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<p>Alberto Gomez is Executive Director of Grupo Financiero Banamex-Citigroup's area of Research and Communications.  His responsibilities include the entire range of economic analysis - macroeconomics, finance, sectors, regional activity - as well as institutional communications for Mexico and Latin America.  He also participates in strategic planning for the region.</p>
			<p>In this role, he serves as Director and Editor for all of Banamex-Citigroup's publications covering economic, political and social studies, including: "<i>Review of the Economic Situation of Mexico</i>" (published monthly in Spanish and English since 1925); the "<i>Daily Economic Report</i>," "<i>Flashnotes</i>," "<i>Regional Indicators of Economic Activity</i>" and "<i>M&#233;xico Social</i>." He is also a published author, most recently of "25 A&#241;os de Desarrollo Social en M&#233;xico" (25 years of Social Development in Mexico) and "Nuestros Valores, Los Mexicanos en M&#233;xico y en Estados Unidos al Inicio del Siglo XXI" (Our Values: Mexicans in Mexico and the United States at the Beginning of the 21st Century).  He is the Secretary of the "<i>Banamex Prize in Economics</i>," and Adviser to subsidiaries of Grupo Financiero Banamex-Citigroup, as well as to the Mutual Funds and the Afore (pension fund). He has worked at Citigroup since 1981.</p>
			<p>Mr. Gomez is a Member of Technical Advisory Committees at the Mexican Institute of Financial Executives (IMEF) and the Center of Private Sector Economic Research (CEESP).  He has also been a member of the Center of Economic Analysis and Research (CAIE - ITAM), and is a member of such international economic organizations as the CBE (Conference of Business Economists) and the ICCBE (International Conference of Commercial Bank Economists).</p>
			<p>He has a Ph.D. in Economics (1986) and a Masters in Economics (1984) from the University of Pennsylvania.</p>
			]]></bio>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>27</id>
		<name>Paul Galant</name>
		<firstname>Paul</firstname>
		<lastname>Galant</lastname>
		<title1>Chief Executive Officer</title1>
		<title2>Citi Global Enterprise Payments</title2>
		<title3/>
		<title4/>
		<smallImg>galant.jpg</smallImg>
		<speaker>yes</speaker>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>no</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>no</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>no</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>no</sec16exec>
		<profilelink>galant/index.htm</profilelink>
		<sec16link/>
		<speakerInfo>
			<highlights>
				<link/>
			</highlights>
			<categories>
				<category>Market Insights</category>
				<category>The Future of Banking</category>
			</categories>
			<topic>
				<topicname/>
			</topic>
			<travels>
				<place>New York</place>
			</travels>
		</speakerInfo>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<p>Paul Galant is CEO of Citi's Global Enterprise Payments business unit which leverages the bank's industry-leading wholesale and retail payment capabilities across regions and organizations globally. In this role, Paul oversees the design, marketing and implementation of comprehensive business-to-consumer and consumer-to-business payments solutions for the world's largest global corporations and financial institutions, as well as governments. He is also a member of Citi's Senior Leadership Committee.</p>
			<p>Prior to this, he served as the CEO of Citi Cards, heading Citi's North American and International Cards business, leading the business through a time of dramatic change in the industry. Citi's global credit card business provides credit for people and businesses the world over. The franchise is a market leader and encompasses card activities in 50 countries across six continents. </p>
			<p>Earlier, Paul served as CEO of Global Transaction Services (GTS) a division of Citi's Institutional Clients Group.  Global Transaction Services is one of Citi's publicly reported product lines, offering award winning and industry leading Treasury and Trade Solutions, and Securities and Fund Services capabilities to corporations, governments, financial institutions and investment advisors worldwide. </p>
			<p>Previously, he was the Global Head of the Cash Management business, -- one of the largest processors of cash flows globally, covering all geographic regions including North America and Latin America, Europe, the Middle East, Africa and Asia Pacific. Under Paul's leadership the Cash Management business experienced strong growth and a significant improvement in its operating performance. It was also recognized for innovation and excellence by many publications including Euromoney, The Banker and Global Finance.</p>
			<p>Before this, Paul was Global Head of eCommerce and Market Data Strategy for Citi Corporate and Investment Banking.  Paul and his team set strategic direction and coordinated execution of eCommerce initiatives, advised on eCommerce alliances, consortia and joint ventures, set market data strategy, managed market data relationships and developed global agreements that generated cost savings, allowed greater distribution and leveraged purchased content and functionality.
			<p>Previous positions before joining Citi were with Donaldson, Lufkin and Jenrette as Global Head of Ecommerce and Financial Engineering within Debt Capital Markets as well as Management Committee member; with both Smith Barney and CSFB heading Financial Engineering Divisions; and as President and Founder of BTP Information Services, Inc.</p> 
			<p>Paul holds a B.A. from Cornell University where he graduated a Phillip Merrill Scholar.  He was featured in Institutional Investors Online 40 (2010, 2008), by Crain's New York Business as a member of its "40 Under 40" (2006), by Global Finance as a member of their "Who's Who in Treasury and Cash Management" (2006) and by CNBC as a "Young Gun" in its "Five under 40" profile (2006).  He serves as an Executive member on the NY Weill Cornell Medical Center Council. </p>
			]]></bio>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>28</id>
		<name>John C. Gerspach</name>
		<firstname>John C.</firstname>
		<lastname>Gerspach</lastname>
		<title1>Chief Financial Officer</title1>
		<title2>Citigroup</title2>
		<title3/>
		<title4/>
		<smallImg>gerspach.jpg</smallImg>
		<opc>yes</opc>
		<bdc>no</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>none</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>no</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>yes</sec16exec>
		<profilelink>gerspach/index.htm</profilelink>
		<sec16link>gerspach/holdings.htm</sec16link>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<p>John Gerspach was named Chief Financial Officer of Citi in July 2009. He is responsible for the financial management of the company. Prior to being named CFO, John was Controller and Chief Accounting Officer of Citi.</p>
			<p>Mr. Gerspach has been with Citi since 1990 and has held various CFO and Chief Administrative Officer positions throughout the company. He has experience in both the Regional Consumer Banking and Institutional Clients Group and has worked closely with all of the regions, including serving as the CFO/CAO of Latin America.</p>
			<p>Before joining Citi in 1990, Mr. Gerspach was CFO at Penn Central Industry Group. Prior to that, he was Comptroller for the Defense Contracting Group at ITT Corporation. His professional career began at Arthur Andersen & Company.</p>
			<p>Mr. Gerspach earned his degree in accounting at the University of Notre Dame and is CPA certified in the State of New York.  He is a member of the Financial Accounting Standards Advisory Council.</p>
			]]></bio>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>102</id>
		<name>Renato de L. Grandmont</name>
		<firstname>Renato de L.</firstname>
		<lastname>Grandmont</lastname>
		<title1>Managing Director</title1>
		<title2>Chief Investment Officer</title2>
		<title3>Citi Wealth Management Latin America</title3>
		<title4>Citi Private Bank Latin America </title4>
		<smallImg>grandmont.jpg</smallImg>
		<speaker>yes</speaker>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>no</bdc>
		<speakerInfo>
			<highlights>
				<link/>
			</highlights>
			<categories>
				<category>Market Insights</category>
			</categories>
			<topic>
				<topicname>Investment Opportunities in Latin America</topicname>
			</topic>
			<travels>
				<place>New York</place>
			</travels>
		</speakerInfo>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<p>Renato is Managing Director and Chief Investment Officer for Citi Wealth Management Latin America and for Citi Private Bank Latin America. He is also the Head of Citi Private Bank's New York Investment Center, covering the regions of Latin America, Asia, Europe, Middle East and Africa. He served as Interim Global Chief Investment Officer for the Citi Private Bank from July 2009 to March 2010. He is a voting member of Citi's Global Investment Committee and Global Portfolio Committee and chairs Citi's Wealth Management Latin America Investment Policy Committee and the Brazil Investment Policy Committee. Renato has been with Citi since 2006, and in the financial industry since 1994.</p>
			<p>Prior to joining Citi, he was Managing Director and Portfolio Manager for Equities at GreenAm Advisors, a Greenwich based multi-strategy hedge fund part of Paloma Partners. Before moving to the buy-side, Renato founded and headed Deutsche Bank's Global Corporate Governance Research group. Renato pioneered corporate governance research by combining governance and financial analysis to identify additional company risk sources and formulate investment recommendations.</p>
			<p>Prior to that assignment, Renato was Director of Latin America Investment Strategy for Deutsche Bank in New York after serving as a Latin America Strategist with Merrill Lynch in New York. Prior to Merrill Lynch, Renato was an Economist with Wharton Econometrics Forecasting Associates - WEFA Group in Philadelphia and also worked in international project finance with Haxar International Consultants in Montreal, Canada.</p>
			<p>Renato has actively participated in the reform of capital markets' laws, regulations and listing standards in countries such as Brazil, Mexico and Argentina. Due to his research on this subject, Deutsche Bank was the only foreign financial institution invited to give testimony before the Brazilian Congress on the importance of corporate law reform. He is a member of the Investor Responsibility Task Force, established by the World Bank/IFC/OECD Global Corporate Governance Forum. He has been a speaker at many domestic and international forums on issues ranging from corporate governance to financial markets to investment strategy and economics.</p>
			<p>He has been a guest speaker to the Yale University School of Management's MBA class of Prof. Ira Millstein. He has been a presenter at major international policy conferences including the Commonwealth Central Bank Governors annual conference and the International Corporate Governance Network annual conference (which represents investors with around US$10 trillion in assets under management). Renato has written articles for the United Nations Environment Program Finance Initiative (UNEP FI), Institutional Investor Magazine, The Financial Times, and the Latin CEO magazine, among others. He frequently comments on the financial markets in the press and on television, including The Financial Times, The Wall Street Journal, Bloomberg, Reuters, Dow Jones Newswires, on network news broadcasts at CNBC, CNN, Bloomberg Television, and CNN en Espa&#241;ol.</p>
			<p>Renato received a Masters of Science in Economics with specialization in International Financial Economics and Econometrics from the University of Montreal. He graduated from Concordia University in Montreal, Canada with a Bachelor of Commerce degree and a double major in International Business and Economics. He is fluent in French, Portuguese, Spanish, and English.</p>
			]]></bio>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>113</id>
		<name>Gary Greenwald</name>
		<firstname>Gary</firstname>
		<lastname>Greenwald</lastname>
		<title1>Chief Innovation Officer</title1>
		<title2>Global Transaction Services, Citi</title2>
		<title3/>
		<smallImg>greenwald.jpg</smallImg>
		<speaker>yes</speaker>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>no</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>no</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>no</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>no</sec16exec>
		<speakerInfo>
			<highlights>
				<link/>
			</highlights>
			<categories>
				<category>The Future of Banking</category>
			</categories>
			<topic>
				<topicname>Making Innovation Profitable</topicname>
				<topicname>Crossing the 2.0 Divide: Consumer to Insitutional Innovation</topicname>
			</topic>
			<travels>
				<place>New York</place>
			</travels>
		</speakerInfo>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<p>Gary Greenwald is the Chief Innovation Officer for Global Transaction Services. Global Transaction Services is one of Citi's publicly reported product lines, offering award winning and industry leading Treasury and Trade Solutions, and Securities and Fund Services capabilities to corporations, governments, financial institutions and investment advisors worldwide. </p>
			<p>Gary is responsible for driving client-focused innovation across market segments, regions and products, with particular focus on the critical role of technology in the transaction services business. At GTS, Gary has developed market leading solutions in such areas as online banking, digital identity management, and analytics. Considered an industry expert on treasury and transaction banking technology trends, Gary is a frequent speaker and author on the subject. </p>
			<p>Gary joined Citi in 1983, and has held a number of diverse positions in both corporate and consumer banking. He holds a BS in Economics from the University of Pennsylvania's Wharton School and an MS in Statistics and Operations Research from New York University's Stern School of Business. In 2006, Gary was recognized by Treasury and Risk Magazine as one of the 100 Most Influential People in Finance. </p>
			]]></bio>
	</profile>
	
	<profile>
		<id>121</id>
		<name>Carlos Gutierrez</name>
		<firstname>Carlos</firstname>
		<lastname>Gutierrez</lastname>
		<title1>Vice Chairman</title1>
		<title2>Institutional Clients Group</title2>
		<title3/>
		<title4/>
		<smallImg>gutierrez.jpg</smallImg>
		<speaker/>
		<boardDir/>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>yes</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>no</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>no</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>no</sec16exec>
		<sec16link/>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<p>Carlos M. Gutierrez is Vice Chairman of the Institutional Clients Group for Citigroup. </p>
			<p>From 2005 to 2009, he was the 35th Secretary of the U.S. Department of Commerce. Before his government service, he was Chairman and CEO of the Kellogg Company, a global manufacturer and marketer of well-known food brands. </p>
			<p>Secretary Gutierrez was born in Havana, Cuba in 1953 and came to the United States with his family in 1960. In 1975, he joined the Kellogg Company as a sales representative in Mexico City, Mexico. After assignments in Latin America, Canada, Asia, and the United States, he became President and CEO in 1999 and Chairman of the Board in April, 2000. </p>
			<p>As the 35th Secretary of the U.S. Department of Commerce, Mr. Gutierrez was responsible for a diverse Cabinet agency with some 38,000 workers and a $6.5 billion budget focused on promoting American business at home and abroad. During his tenure as Secretary, he regularly traveled internationally to visit with foreign government and business leaders to discuss ways to enhance trade and promote U.S. exports. Mr. Gutierrez played a key role in the passage of CAFTA-DR, a landmark agreement that strips away trade barriers, expands export opportunities and boosts hope and opportunity throughout Latin America. In addition, he also served the Bush Administration as Co-Chair for the Commission for Assistance to a Free Cuba and was actively involved in U.S./Cuba policy.</p>
			<p>Secretary Gutierrez studied Business Administration at the Monterrey Institute of Technology in Queretaro, Mexico.</p>
			]]></bio>
	</profile>	
	<profile>
		<id>29</id>
		<name>Yung-Ku Ha</name>
		<firstname>Yung-Ku</firstname>
		<lastname>Ha</lastname>
		<title1>Chief Executive Officer</title1>
		<title2>Citibank Korea Inc.</title2>
		<title3/>
		<title4/>
		<smallImg>ha.jpg</smallImg>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>no</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>no</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>no</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>no</sec16exec>
		<profilelink>ha/index.htm</profilelink>
		<sec16link/>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<p>Yung Ku Ha is the CEO of Citibank Korea Inc. as well as of Citi Korea.   He is responsible for Citi's franchise in Korea and is a member of Citi's Senior Leadership Committee.</p>
			<p>Before taking on his current role, Y.K. had been the CEO of KorAm Bank in May 2001 after 20 years in Citibank.  Through the tender offer process in April 2004, KorAm became a part of Citi and Y.K. returned to the company. In November 2004, KorAm and the Citi Seoul operation were integrated into Citibank Korea Inc.</p>
			<p>Y.K. had originally joined Citibank in 1981.  He had the responsibilities of different country head positions in the company, starting in Korea as Country Treasurer in 1985, Country Business Manager for Investment Banking Group in 1987, Corporate Banking Group Head in 1994, and most recently Country Business Manger for Global Consumer Bank.</p>
			<p>Y.K. was a member of the Financial Industry Development Committee and the Deregulation Committees of various laws and rulings which are hosted by the Ministry of Finance and Economy, from 1998 to 2007. Y.K. is (now) a member of Financial Center Promotion Committee, hosted by FSC (Financial Services Commission). He also chairs Citi Korea's Diversity Committee and business sponsor of Citi Korea Women's Council.</p>
			<p>Y.K. received an MBA from Kellogg School of Northwestern University and a BA in International Economics from Seoul National University in Korea.</p>
			]]></bio>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>106</id>
		<name>Suni Harford</name>
		<firstname>Suni</firstname>
		<lastname>Harford</lastname>
		<title1>Managing Director</title1>
		<title2>Regional Head of Markets</title2>
		<title3>North America Citi</title3>
		<title4/>
		<smallImg>harford.jpg</smallImg>
		<speaker>yes</speaker>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>no</bdc>
		<speakerInfo>
			<highlights>
				<link/>
			</highlights>
			<categories>
				<category>Market Insights</category>
			</categories>
			<topic>
				<topicname>U.S. Market Perspectives</topicname>
			</topic>
			<travels>
				<place>New York</place>
			</travels>
		</speakerInfo>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<p>Suni Harford is a Managing Director and Citigroup's Regional Head of Markets for North America. In this capacity, Suni oversees the North American sales, trading, and origination businesses of Citi's premium securities and banking franchise.  Additionally, Suni chairs the division's Diversity Committee and is the co-chair of the Markets Recruiting Steering Committee.</p>
			<p>Prior to this assignment, Suni was Citi's Global Head of Fixed Income Strategy and Analysis, where she was responsible for Citigroup's credit analytics, Research Strategy and Fixed Income Quantitative Research efforts globally.   She also manages Citi's premier fixed income analytics platform, The Yield Book.  Ms. Harford served as the Head of Citi's FIG Fixed Income Capital Markets Group from 1995-2004, responsible for capital markets origination of financial institutions.</p>
			<p>Ms. Harford joined Salomon Brothers in January 1993, after five years with Merrill Lynch & Co. where she was a Vice President in Investment Banking.  She joined Merrill upon graduation from the Amos Tuck School of Business at Dartmouth College, where she received her MBA in 1988. Prior to business school, Ms. Harford was an actuary at Insurance Services Office, Inc.</p>
			<p>Suni received her Bachelor of Science degree from Denison University, where she majored in physics and math. Suni lives in New York City with her husband and three children: Devon, Jenna and Liam.  She is on the MBA Advisory Board at the Tuck School, and has served on the Board of Trustees of John Cabot University in Rome, Italy.</p>
			]]></bio>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>30</id>
		<name>John Havens</name>
		<firstname>John</firstname>
		<lastname>Havens</lastname>
		<title1>President and Chief Operating Officer</title1>
		<title2>Citigroup</title2>
		<title3>Chief Executive Officer, Institutional Clients Group</title3>
		<title4/>
		<smallImg>havens.jpg</smallImg>
		<opc>yes</opc>
		<bdc>yes</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>none</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>no</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>yes</sec16exec>
		<profilelink>havens/index.htm</profilelink>
		<sec16link>havens/holdings.htm</sec16link>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<p>John Havens is President and Chief Operating Officer of Citigroup, a role he assumed in January 2011. Mr. Havens is also CEO of Citi's Institutional Clients Group (ICG), the institutional division of Citigroup Inc.</p>
			<p>Mr. Havens was previously CEO of Citi Alternative Investments, where he remains Chairman. Prior to joining CAI, he was a founder and Partner of Old Lane, LP, a multi-strategy hedge fund and private equity fund manager that was acquired by Citi in 2007. Upon acquisition, Old Lane's total assets under management and private equity commitments amounted to approximately $4.5 billion.</p>
			<p>Before forming Old Lane in 2005, Mr. Havens was Head of Institutional Equity at Morgan Stanley and a member of the firm's Management Committee. In his 19-year career at Morgan Stanley, Mr. Havens held several positions of increasing authority and served on the new product, risk, and capital allocation committees.</p>
			<p>Mr. Havens has served on many NYSE committees over the years and just ended a term as a Director of the NASDAQ market. He began his career in 1979 as a trader of convertible securities at Kidder Peabody.</p>
			<p>Mr. Havens holds a B.A. degree from Harvard University.</p>
			]]></bio>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>31</id>
		<name>Michael Helfer</name>
		<firstname>Michael</firstname>
		<lastname>Helfer</lastname>
		<title1>General Counsel</title1>
		<title2>Corporate Secretary</title2>
		<title3>Citigroup</title3>
		<title4/>
		<smallImg>helfer.jpg</smallImg>
		<opc>yes</opc>
		<bdc>no</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>none</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>no</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>yes</sec16exec>
		<profilelink>helfer/index.htm</profilelink>
		<sec16link>helfer/holdings.htm</sec16link>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<p>Michael Helfer is the General Counsel and Corporate Secretary of Citigroup.</p>
			<p>Prior to joining Citigroup in 2003, Mr. Helfer was President of Strategic Investments and Chief Strategic Officer at Nationwide Insurance. He had previously been a Partner and Chairman of the Management Committee of Wilmer, Cutler & Pickering, clerked for Chief Judge David Bazelon (D.C. Cir.), and served as Counsel for the Subcommittee on Constitutional Amendments of the U.S. Senate Judiciary Committee. </p>
			<p>Mr. Helfer is a member of the American Law Institute, the Council on Foreign Relations, serves as Chairman of The Clearing House Association and Vice Chairman of the Regulatory Oversight Committee of the Financial Services Roundtable. </p>
			<p>A founding member of the Board of Directors of Lawyers for Children America, Mr. Helfer served as President of the Legal Aid Society in Washington, D.C. and is now a member of the Advisory Board of the Legal Aid Society of New York. </p>
			<p>He received his J.D. from Harvard Law School and a B.A. in economics from Claremont Men's College.</p>
			]]>
		</bio>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>32</id>
		<name>Roberto Hernandez Ramirez</name>
		<firstname>Roberto</firstname>
		<lastname>Hernandez Ramirez</lastname>
		<title1>Chairman, Banco Nacional de Mexico</title1>
		<title2/>
		<title3/>
		<title4/>
		<boardDir>no</boardDir>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>no</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>no</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>no</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>no</sec16exec>
		<profilelink/>
		<sec16link/>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>95</id>
		<name>Deborah Hopkins</name>
		<firstname>Deborah</firstname>
		<lastname>Hopkins</lastname>
		<title1>Chairman of Venture Capital Initiatives</title1>
		<title2>Chief Innovation Officer, Citi</title2>
		<smallImg>hopkins.jpg</smallImg>
		<speaker>yes</speaker>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>no</bdc>
		<speakerInfo>
			<highlights>
				<link/>
			</highlights>
			<categories>
				<category>The Future of Banking</category>
			</categories>
			<topic>
				<topicname>Innovation and Venture Strategies</topicname>
				<topicname>Designing the Future of Money</topicname>
			</topic>
			<travels>
				<place>Palo Alto</place>
			</travels>
		</speakerInfo>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<p>Deborah Hopkins is Citi's Chairman of Venture Capital Initiatives and Chief Innovation Officer.</p>
			<p>In her role as Venture Capital Initiatives Chairman, she oversees the development and enhancement of Citi's relationships with the global venture capital community. Citi created this role in 2010, recognizing that new and emerging business opportunities are increasingly driven through collaboration and engagement with venture capital firms, start-up companies and corporate partners, both in mature and emerging markets.</p>
			<p>As Chief Innovation Officer, Ms. Hopkins is responsible for developing and leading Citi's approach to creative, forward-looking collaboration with external constituencies, including current and prospective clients, venture capital firms, government agencies and academic institutions. She also works to maximize creativity within Citi to ensure operating efficiencies globally, across products, regions and the enterprise as a whole. In addition, she is Co-Chair of Citi's Women's Initiative.</p>
			<p>Since joining Citi in 2003, Ms. Hopkins has held several senior roles at the company. From 2003 to 2005, she was Chief Operations & Technology Officer. Prior to that, she was Head of Corporate Strategy, Mergers & Acquisitions.</p>
			<p>Before coming to Citi, Ms. Hopkins held senior-level positions at several global companies, including Chief Financial Officer for The Boeing Company and for Lucent Technologies. Prior to that, Ms. Hopkins was Vice President of Finance for General Motors Europe.</p>
			<p>In addition to her positions at Citi, Ms. Hopkins serves on the Advisory Board of Riverwood Partners. She was a member of the Board of Directors for DuPont between 2000 and 2005, and in 2000, <i>Fortune</i> magazine named her the second most powerful woman in American business.</p>
			]]></bio>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>33</id>
		<name>Bonnie Howard</name>
		<firstname>Bonnie</firstname>
		<lastname>Howard</lastname>
		<title1>Chief Auditor</title1>
		<title2>Citi</title2>
		<title3/>
		<title4/>
		<smallImg>howard.jpg</smallImg>
		<speaker/>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>no</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>no</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>no</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>no</sec16exec>
		<profilelink>howard/index.htm</profilelink>
		<sec16link/>
		<speakerInfo>
			<highlights>
				<link/>
			</highlights>
			<categories>
				<category>Corporate Citizenship and Governance</category>
			</categories>
			<topic>
				<topicname/>
			</topic>
			<travels>
				<place>New York</place>
			</travels>
		</speakerInfo>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<p>Bonnie Howard was named Chief Auditor of Citi in June 2004.  She manages the Audit and Risk Review function with staff in six U.S. cities and 13 countries.  </p>
			<p>She is a member of the Citi Senior Leadership Committee and business sponsor of the Citi Women's Network - NYC and the Corporate Center Women's Organization.  She also serves on the Board of Directors of the YWCA of the City of New York and the Advisory Council of the YWCA Academy of Women Leaders.</p>
			<p>Bonnie joined Citi in New York in January 2003 as Managing Director of Audit and Risk Review - Markets & Banking.  In this role, she led ARR's worldwide coverage of capital markets, corporate finance, credit and transaction services businesses.</p>
			<p>Prior to joining Citi, from 2000 to 2002 Bonnie was Deputy Auditor of FleetBoston Financial Corporation and from 1988 to 2000 a Managing Director with JP Morgan, where she held leadership roles within global markets operations and internal audit.  Her career began in public accounting with KPMG and Ernst and Young.</p>
			<p>Bonnie graduated from the University of Missouri with a B.S. in Accounting.  She is a Certified Public Accountant and an NASD-registered Finance and Operations Principal (Series 27).</p>
			]]></bio>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>115</id>
		<name>William E. "Bill" Johnson</name>
		<firstname>William</firstname>
		<lastname>Johnson</lastname>
		<title1>CEO</title1>
		<title2>Retail Partner Cards</title2>
		<title3/>
		<smallImg>johnson.jpg</smallImg>
		<speaker>yes</speaker>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>no</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>no</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>no</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>no</sec16exec>
		<speakerInfo>
			<highlights>
				<link/>
			</highlights>
			<categories>
				<category>Market Insights</category>
				<category>Client Trends and Insights</category>
			</categories>
			<topic>
				<topicname>The Changing Credit Landscape</topicname>
				<topicname>Partner Cards: Building Loyalty and Connectivity</topicname>
			</topic>
			<travels>
				<place>Atlanta</place>
			</travels>
		</speakerInfo>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<p>William E. "Bill" Johnson is CEO of Retail Partner Cards within Citi Holdings. Retail Partner Cards provides consumer and commercial credit products and services, including private label credit cards, for national and regional retailers across the U.S. and Canada.   The business services more than 40 million customers and consists of managed assets of approximately $50 billion.  Marquee partners include The Home Depot, Shell, Macy's, Sears, and ExxonMobil.  </p>
			<p>Mr. Johnson joined Citi in 1999 and has been responsible for various aspects of both Citi Cards North America and the Retail Partner Cards business.  Under his leadership, the Retail Partner Cards segment grew from $6B in 2000 to more than $50B at the end of 2009 making Citi the clear leader and preferred provider in this market.  He previously served as an Executive Vice President of both Retail Partnerships and the Retail Sector for Citi Cards.  Mr. Johnson was instrumental in bringing The Home Depot, Sears and Macy's portfolios to Citi.</p>
			<p>Prior to Citi, Mr. Johnson held a number of executive positions at GE Capital.  During his decade-long tenure there, he gained invaluable knowledge about building strong partner relationships, acquiring new portfolios and developing programs specializing in multi-level distribution.  His early career experience includes several positions in business and dealer development.  During this time he was responsible for the acquisition of more than $15B in new business.  He also completed both the MDC and BMC development programs and was a multiple winner of the highly coveted "Pinnacle" award.</p>
			<p>Considered an expert in contract negotiation, Mr. Johnson is recognized throughout the industry as a thought leader in the structure of retail credit programs.  He has been featured in a number of industry publications and is sought out for his business views.   He has also used his negotiation skills to benefit the nonprofit sector.  As a member of the Board of Directors of the Georgia Center for Nonprofits, Mr. Johnson has taught several workshops on "The Art of Negotiation" to train nonprofit executives in negotiation skills.  </p>
			<p>Mr. Johnson is an alumnus of the Citi Chairman's Executive Forum and Business Leadership Program.  In addition to his work with the Georgia Center for Nonprofits, a nationally recognized capacity-building organization, he is engaged in a number of local community activities.  He holds an M.B.A. from Georgia State University. </p>
			]]></bio>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>34</id>
		<name>Charles D. Johnston</name>
		<firstname>Charles D.</firstname>
		<lastname>Johnston</lastname>
		<title1>President</title1>
		<title2>Citi Global Wealth Management</title2>
		<title3/>
		<title4/>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>no</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>no</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>no</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>no</sec16exec>
		<profilelink/>
		<sec16link/>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>81</id>
		<name>Robert L. Joss, Ph.D.</name>
		<firstname>Robert L.</firstname>
		<lastname>Joss, Ph.D.</lastname>
		<title1>Professor of Finance Emeritus and Former Dean, Stanford University Graduate School of Business</title1>
		<title2/>
		<title3/>
		<title4/>
		<smallImg>joss.jpg</smallImg>
		<boardDir>yes</boardDir>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>no</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>no</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>yes</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>no</sec16exec>
		<profilelink/>
		<sec16link>joss/holdings.htm</sec16link>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<ul class="list" style="width: 355px;">
				<li>Professor of Finance Emeritus - 2010 to present</li>
				<li>Dean of Stanford University Graduate School of Business - 1999 to 2009</li>
				<li>CEO and Managing Director, Westpac Banking Corporation - 1993 to 1999</li>
				<li>Vice Chairman, Wells Fargo Bank - 1986 to 1993</li>
				<li>Executive Vice President - 1981 to 1986</li>
				<li>Senior Vice President - 1975 to 1981</li>
				<li>Vice President - 1972 to 1975</li>
				<li>Assistant Vice President - 1971 to 1972</li>
				<li>Deputy to the Assistant Secretary for Economic Policy, U.S. Treasury Department - 1969 to 1971</li>
				<li>White House Fellow - 1968 to 1969</li>
				<li>Director of Citigroup since 2009</li>
				<li>Director of Citibank, N.A. since 2010 </li>
				<li>Other Directorships: Bechtel Group, Inc., Makena Capital Management</li>
				<li>Previous Directorships within the last five years: Agilent Technologies, Inc., Wells Fargo & Co., and Macquarie DDR Management Ltd.</li>
				<li>Other Activities: Committee for Economic Development (Trustee)</li>
			</ul>
			]]></bio>		
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>35</id>
		<name>Lewis B. Kaden</name>
		<firstname>Lewis B.</firstname>
		<lastname>Kaden</lastname>
		<title1>Vice Chairman, Citigroup</title1>
		<title2/>
		<title3/>
		<title4/>
		<smallImg>kaden.jpg</smallImg>
		<speaker/>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>yes</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>none</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>no</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>no</sec16exec>
		<profilelink>kaden/index.htm</profilelink>
		<sec16link/>
		<speakerInfo>
			<highlights>
				<link/>
			</highlights>
			<categories>
				<category>Corporate Citizenship and Governance</category>
			</categories>
			<topic>
				<topicname>Corporate Governance</topicname>
				<topicname>Corporate Social Responsibility</topicname>
			</topic>
			<travels>
				<place>New York</place>
			</travels>
		</speakerInfo>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<p>Lewis B. Kaden is Vice Chairman of Citigroup, Inc. Mr. Kaden is also Chairman of the Institutional Clients Group's Public Sector Group and the Citi Foundation.</p>
			<p>Mr. Kaden joined Citigroup in 2005 from Davis Polk & Wardwell, where he was a partner, whose practice included corporate governance, mergers and acquisitions, and advocacy before appellate courts, including the United States Supreme Court. He regularly advised directors and senior management of major corporations on significant issues.</p>
			<p>Before joining Davis Polk in 1984, Mr. Kaden was a Professor of Law at Columbia University from 1976 to 1984 and Director of Columbia's Center for Law and Economic Studies from 1980 to1984. He has been Adjunct Professor of Law since 1984. In 2005, he was appointed Covington and Burling Distinguished Visitor to the Harvard Law School.</p>
			<p>From 1974 to 1976, Mr. Kaden was Counsel to the Governor of New Jersey. He has served as a moderator for the Public Broadcasting System's Media and Society Seminars, including the "Ethics in America" series, which won a Peabody Award. </p>
			<p>Mr. Kaden is the Lead Independent Director of ArcelorMittal, Chairman of the Board of Trustees of the Markle Foundation and Vice Chairman of the Board of Trustees of Asia Society.  He also serves as a trustee on the boards of Continuum Health Partners and The Century Foundation. He is a member of the Council on Foreign Relations and the Dean's Advisory Board of the Harvard Law School and a former Chairman of the Harvard Law School Fund. He has also served as Chairman of the United States Government Overseas Presence Advisory Panel (1999-2000), the Industrial Cooperation Council of the State of New York, and Governor Mario Cuomo's Commission on Competitiveness (1987-1992). He was the moderator of the Business-Labor Dialogue, a group of chief executive officers and trade union presidents organized by John F. Welch and John Sweeney.</p>
			<p>Mr. Kaden graduated from Harvard College and Harvard Law School, where he was an editor of the Law Review. During 1963-64, he was the John Harvard Scholar at Emmanuel College, Cambridge University. </p>
			]]></bio>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>122</id>
		<name>Leon Kalvaria</name>
		<firstname>Leon</firstname>
		<lastname>Kalvaria</lastname>
		<title1>Vice Chairman</title1>
		<title2>Institutional Clients Group</title2>
		<title3/>
		<title4/>
		<smallImg>kalvaria.jpg</smallImg>
		<speaker/>
		<boardDir/>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>yes</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>no</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>no</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>no</sec16exec>
		<sec16link/>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<p>Leon Kalvaria, Vice Chairman of the Institutional Clients Group, coordinates the Senior Strategic Advisory Group. He is a member of the ICG Management Group and the Global Banking Executive Committee. Previously, he was Global Head of Consumer and Healthcare Investment Banking and a member of Citigroup's Global Investment Banking Operating Committee and Citigroup's Private Equity Investment Committee.</p>
			<p>Leon joined Schroders in 1996 as Global Head of the Consumer Investment Banking, and Citigroup in 2000 following the merger of the two companies. Prior to Schroders, Leon served as Vice Chairman and a Director of Triarc Companies, a firm focused on investments in the consumer industry, and as Managing Director in the Mergers & Acquisitions Group at Credit Suisse First Boston.</p>
			<p>Leon has advised numerous Chief Executive Officers and Boards of Directors in the Consumer and Health Care space, as well as other industries, and has participated in some of the industry's largest, most complex mergers and acquisitions. Leon received his B.A. from Princeton University (Woodrow Wilson School of Public and International Affairs). Mr. Kalvaria is on the Board of Directors and Foundation Board President for Princeton in Africa, a non-profit organization offering opportunities for service through fellowships with a variety of organizations that work across the African continent. He is also a member of the Advisory Council of Princeton's Woodrow Wilson School.</p>
			]]></bio>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>94</id>
		<name>Chris Kay</name>
		<firstname>Chris</firstname>
		<lastname>Kay</lastname>
		<title1>Managing Director</title1>
		<title2>Head of Innovation, Citi</title2>
		<smallImg>kay.jpg</smallImg>
		<speaker>yes</speaker>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>no</bdc>
		<speakerInfo>
			<highlights>
				<link/>
			</highlights>
			<categories>
				<category>The Future of Banking</category>
			</categories>
			<topic>
				<topicname>Corporate Venturing</topicname>
				<topicname>Outside-in Innovation</topicname>
			</topic>
			<travels>
				<place>Palo Alto</place>
			</travels>
		</speakerInfo>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<p>Chris Kay is Managing Director and Head of Innovation for Citi. In this role, reporting to Debby Hopkins, Chris and his team partner with Citi businesses around the world to nurture initiatives from concept to launch and to ensure subsequent scaling across the enterprise. They also help develop new organizational capabilities and individual skills that drive sustainable innovation across business units and geographies. In addition, Chris works with key external corporate partners to develop new Citi capabilities that help drive growth.</p>
			<p>Among the activities that Chris, his colleagues and partners are engaged in currently is "Ubiquity," a multi-phase project focused through the lens of the customer on redefining consumer banking in Japan by providing new retail and mobile experiences. In another project, they are working with the Private Bank to develop a new model for Citi to service the needs of the "next generation" of our most affluent Private Bank customers. Chris and his team are also actively engaged in building innovation capabilities through training programs in markets globally.</p>
			<p>Prior to joining Citi three years ago, Chris was a senior executive at Target, leading several of its most successful growth strategies, initiatives and transformational efforts. Chris started his professional career as a corporate lawyer representing Fortune 100 companies across a variety of areas with a specialty in debt- and equity-based real estate transactions.</p>
			<p>Chris has a JD Magna cum Laude from University of Minnesota and a BA in French and Economics from University of Wisconsin-Madison. He, his wife and five children live in rural Connecticut.</p>
			]]></bio>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>36</id>
		<name>Edward J. Kelly, III</name>
		<firstname>Edward J.</firstname>
		<lastname>Kelly, III</lastname>
		<title1>Chairman</title1>
		<title2>Institutional Clients Group</title2>
		<title3/>
		<title4/>
		<smallImg>kelly.jpg</smallImg>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>yes</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>none</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>no</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>no</sec16exec>
		<profilelink>kelly/index.htm</profilelink>
		<sec16link/>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<p>Edward "Ned" Kelly is Chairman of the Institutional Clients Group. He was Vice Chairman of Citigroup from July 2009 to January 2011 and Chairman of Global Banking from April 2010 to January 2011. Ned also served as Citi's Chief Financial Officer from March through July 2009. Prior to being named CFO, Ned was Head of Global Banking and before that, President and Chief Executive Officer of Citi Alternative Investments.</p>
			<p>Ned joined Citi in February 2008 from The Carlyle Group, a private investment firm, where he was a Managing Director. Prior to joining Carlyle in July 2007, he was a Vice Chairman at The PNC Financial Services Group following PNC's acquisition of Mercantile Bankshares Corporation in March 2007.</p>
			<p>He was Chairman, Chief Executive and President of Mercantile from March 2003 through March 2007 and Chief Executive and President from March 2001 to March 2003. Before Mercantile, Ned was at J.P. Morgan Chase & Co. where he was Managing Director and head of Global Financial Institutions and co-head of Investment Banking Client Management. He joined J.P. Morgan in 1994 as its General Counsel and Secretary. In 1996, he became a Managing Director and subsequently ran various parts of J.P. Morgan's investment banking business, including Global Financial Institutions and Latin America. Prior to joining J.P. Morgan, Ned was a partner at the law firm of Davis Polk & Wardwell, where he specialized in matters related to financial institutions. Early in his career, Ned served as a law clerk to Supreme Court Justice William J. Brennan, Jr. and U.S. Court of Appeals Judge Clement F. Haynsworth, Jr. Prior to law school, he served as a legislative assistant and, later, press secretary to U.S. Senator Richard S. Schweiker. </p>
			<p>He serves on the Board of Directors of CSX Corporation. He also serves on the Board of Trustees of the University of Virginia Law School Foundation. In the past, he has served on the Boards of Directors of The Hartford Financial Services Group, CIT Group, Axis Capital Holdings, Paris Re Holdings, Constellation Energy, the American Stock Exchange and The Hershey Company, among others. </p>
			<p>Ned received his bachelor's degree from Princeton University and his J.D. from the University of Virginia School of Law.</p>
		]]></bio>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>37</id>
		<name>Kevin Kessinger</name>
		<firstname>Kevin</firstname>
		<lastname>Kessinger</lastname>
		<title1>Chief Operations &amp; Technology Officer</title1>
		<title2>Citi</title2>
		<title3/>
		<title4/>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>no</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>no</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>no</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>no</sec16exec>
		<profilelink>kessinger/index.htm</profilelink>
		<sec16link>kessinger/holdings.htm</sec16link>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>38</id>
		<name>Sallie L. Krawcheck</name>
		<firstname>Sallie L.</firstname>
		<lastname>Krawcheck</lastname>
		<title1>Chairman &amp; Chief Executive Officer</title1>
		<title2>Citi Global Wealth Management</title2>
		<title3/>
		<title4/>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>no</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>no</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>no</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>no</sec16exec>
		<profilelink>krawcheck/index.htm</profilelink>
		<sec16link>krawcheck/holdings.htm</sec16link>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>100</id>
		<name>Laura Lane</name>
		<firstname>Laura</firstname>
		<lastname>Lane</lastname>
		<title1>Managing Director</title1>
		<title2>Head, International Government Affairs</title2>
		<smallImg>nophoto.jpg</smallImg>
		<speaker/>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>no</bdc>
		<speakerInfo>
			<highlights>
				<link/>
			</highlights>
			<categories>
				<category>Market Insights</category>
			</categories>
			<topic>
				<topicname>The International Regulatory Landscape</topicname>
				<topicname>Fostering International Growth</topicname>
			</topic>
			<travels>
				<place>Washington, DC</place>
			</travels>
		</speakerInfo>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<p>Laura Lane, as Managing Director and Head of International Government Affairs, directs the day-to-day advocacy efforts of Citi's international government affairs team. She also currently serves as a cleared advisor to the US government on international trade and investment issues.</p>
			<p>Before joining Citi, Ms. Lane was VP for Global Public Policy with Time Warner where she represented the company on the federal and international levels on all issues affecting Time Warner and its divisions.</p>
			<p>In her government career, Ms. Lane was responsible for bilateral trade affairs with the Middle Eastern and Mediterranean countries at the United States Trade Representative (USTR). There, she also negotiated market access commitments on trade in services with China as part of its accession to the World Trade Organization (WTO) and served as U.S. negotiator for the WTO Financial Services negotiations, which resulted in a first-ever global agreement in 1997.</p>
			<p>Ms. Lane served in the U.S. Foreign Service from 1990-1997. She worked in the Trade Policy and Programs office in the Bureau of Economic and Business Affairs at the U.S. Department of State from 1995-1997. She served as the State Department representative on the US Basic Telecommunications negotiating team, which concluded the first-ever global agreement on basic telecommunications in 1996. Ms. Lane also worked in the State Department Operations Center from 1994-1995 as watch officer under Secretary Warren Christopher.</p>
			<p>In her overseas assignments, Ms. Lane was the economic and political-military affairs officer at the American Embassy in Kigali, Rwanda from 1993-1994. She led the evacuation effort of American citizens from Rwanda in April 1994 with the outbreak of the civil war and returned in August as political advisor to U.S. forces providing humanitarian relief to Rwandan refugees. Laura subsequently appeared as a commentator on the Rwandan conflict on Nightline and in the PBS/Frontline documentary "Ghosts of Rwanda." Ms. Lane also served as consular officer in Bogota, Colombia from 1990-1992. In her state department career, she was the recipient of two Superior Honor awards and a Meritorious Honor award.</p>
			<p>Ms. Lane was born in Evanston, Illinois but grew up in Frankfurt, Germany. She graduated summa cum laude from Loyola University with a Bachelors degree in political science and history and summa cum laude from Georgetown University with a Master of Science degree in international economics. Ms. Lane speaks Spanish and French.</p>
			<p>Ms. Lane's husband, Greg, served in the U.S. Marine Corps in Japan, and at the American Embassies in Nicaragua and Colombia and now is an electrical engineer at Cobham Inc. Ms. Lane and her husband have two daughters.</p>
			]]></bio>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>99</id>
		<name>Jonathan Larsen</name>
		<firstname>Jonathan</firstname>
		<lastname>Larsen</lastname>
		<title1>Head of Consumer Banking</title1>
		<title2>Global Cards</title2>
		<title3>Asia Pacific</title3>
		<smallImg>larsen.jpg</smallImg>
		<speaker>yes</speaker>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>no</bdc>
		<speakerInfo>
			<highlights>
				<link/>
			</highlights>
			<categories>
				<category>Client Trends and Insights</category>
			</categories>
			<topic>
				<topicname>Client Excellence</topicname>
				<topicname>Consumer Banking Trends</topicname>
			</topic>
			<travels>
				<place>Hong Kong</place>
			</travels>
		</speakerInfo>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<p>Jonathan Larsen is Citi's Head of Consumer Banking & Global Cards for the Asia Pacific. In this role, Mr Larsen has responsibility for all of Citi's regional consumer products and customer segments under the Citibank branding. He also has joint oversight of Citi's Local Commercial Banking business covering the small and medium enterprises in the Asia Pacific. Mr Larsen was appointed to his current role in October 2009 and is a member Citi's Asia Pacific Executive Committee, which manages Citi's overall business in the region.</p>
			<p>Citibank is the Asia Pacific's pre-eminent retail bank and credit card issuer with 35 million customer accounts and over US$8 billion in revenues in 2008. Among global banks, Citi has the widest distribution network in the region, including more than 600 retail branches and over 2,000 automated teller machines. Citibank is also the top card issuer in the Asia Pacific with about 15 million card accounts. Through its Citigold banking service, Citibank serves more than half a million of the region's most affluent consumers.</p>
			<p>Prior to assuming his current role, Mr Larsen held the position of Country Head and Citi Country Officer for Singapore and CEO of Citibank Singapore Limited. As Country Head and CCO for Citi Singapore, Mr Larsen had oversight of the Institutional Clients Group, Consumer Banking, Global Cards and Global Wealth Management businesses. Mr Larsen assumed this role in September 2008, and concurrently held the position of Product Head for Consumer Banking and Cards in the ASEAN region covering Singapore, Indonesia, Malaysia, Thailand, the Philippines and Guam</p>
			<p>Citi in Singapore provides the most comprehensive range of financial services to retail customers, high net worth individuals, corporate clients, governments and institutional investors. It is consistently ranked in the top tier of providers of M&A advice, equity and debt underwriting, securities trading, cash management, trade services, foreign exchange and treasury in Singapore and across the region. In the consumer banking and wealth management space, it is known for its legacy of consistent innovation, ability to harness technology for groundbreaking consumer products and quality investment advice. As the largest banking employer in Singapore, Citi provides employment to some 8,000 people and is consistently voted as Employer of Choice in the financial sector.</p>
			<p>Under Mr Larsen's leadership, Citi was named the Best Bank in Singapore by Euromoney in 2007 and 2009. During his tenure, Citi in Singapore also won the Best Bank Award from The Asset, the Best Foreign Commercial Bank Award from FinanceAsia and the Best Retail Bank Award from The Asian Banker.</p>
			<p>Mr Larsen joined Citi in 1998 and has held various leadership roles across Citi's franchise in Asia Pacific. In April 2005, he was appointed Country Business Manager and CEO for Citi's consumer banking business in Singapore, which operates under the locally-incorporated Citibank Singapore Ltd.</p>
			<p>Under his leadership, Citibank Singapore has transformed its consumer banking presence through product innovations, expanded distribution and a market-leading service transformation programme. Key milestones included the partnership with Singapore Mass Rapid Transit Corporation Ltd (SMRT) and new customer focused initiatives such as the instant credit card issuance, instant mortgage and unsecured loan approvals, and a landmark service transformation partnership with the Ritz Carlton hotel group. Under his management, Citibank has made significant inroads into the Singapore heartlands, growing branded customer touchpoints from 5 in 2005 to over 800 today.</p>
			<p>From August 2007, Mr Larsen was Head of Citi's Global Consumer Business across South East Asia, a business spanning six countries, fifteen thousand employees and some eight million customer accounts.</p>
			<p>Mr Larsen was previously the Head of Retail Banking for Citibank in Asia Pacific (2003 to 2005) responsible for Citibank's retail business in 12 countries across the region. As Regional Citigold Head (2000 to 2003), he was a key player in building-out Citibank's leading retail Wealth Management franchise across Asia.</p>
			<p>Mr Larsen has also been extensively involved in developing Citi's franchise in the region through acquisition. As Region Head of Business Development (1998 to 2005), he was Citi's principal representative in negotiating and executing the $2.7Bn acquisition of Koram Bank in Korea in 2004. He led Citi's landmark strategic cooperation agreement with, and investment in, the Shanghai Pudong Development Bank, as well as the acquisition of the Diners Club of Japan Inc. He was similarly involved in numerous other corporate and portfolio acquisitions.</p>
			<p>Before joining Citibank, Mr Larsen spent eight years with the global management consultancy firm Booz, Allen & Hamilton where he became a Principal in the firm's Financial Services Group. While at Booz, Allen, he advised major financial institutions across Asia, Europe and the United States on a wide range of large-scale strategic and operational engagements. He was a recipient of the prestigious Booz Allen Professional Excellence Award. Prior to working with Booz, Allen, Mr Larsen spent the first three years of his career with the National Mutual Group in Australia and New Zealand (now part of AXA).</p>
			<p>Mr. Larsen is a Director of Citibank Singapore Limited and Citibank Berhad. He also served as a member of the Advisory Board of the National University of Singapore Business School.</p>
			<p>Mr Larsen holds a Bachelor of Arts with Honours (First Class) from the University of Melbourne where he was awarded the End Derham Prize for 1987.</p>
			]]></bio>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>39</id>
		<name>Brian Leach</name>
		<firstname>Brian</firstname>
		<lastname>Leach</lastname>
		<title1>Chief Risk Officer</title1>
		<title2>Citigroup</title2>
		<title3/>
		<title4/>
		<smallImg>leach.jpg</smallImg>
		<speaker>yes</speaker>
		<opc>yes</opc>
		<bdc>no</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>none</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>no</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>yes</sec16exec>
		<profilelink>leach/index.htm</profilelink>
		<sec16link>leach/holdings.htm</sec16link>
		<speakerInfo>
			<highlights>
				<link/>
			</highlights>
			<categories>
				<category>Corporate Citizenship and Governance</category>
			</categories>
			<topic>
				<topicname/>
			</topic>
			<travels>
				<place>New York</place>
			</travels>
		</speakerInfo>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<p>Brian Leach assumed the role of Chief Risk Officer in March 2008, reporting to Citi's Chief Executive Officer, Vikram Pandit.</p>
			<p>Prior to becoming Citi's Chief Risk Officer, Brian was the co-COO of Old Lane. Brian, along with several former colleagues from Morgan Stanley, founded Old Lane LP in 2005. Earlier, he had worked for his entire financial career at Morgan Stanley, finishing as Risk Manager of the Institutional Securities Business, where he reported directly to its President. As Risk Manager, he oversaw capital allocation, strategic revenue-enhancement opportunities, and all aspects of credit, market, and operational risk management. He was a member of Morgan Stanley's Institutional Securities Division Management Group, Co-Chairman of the Capital Commitment Committee and Chairman of the Board of Trustees of the Morgan Stanley Foundation.</p>
			<p>From October 1998 to December 1999, Brian was seconded to Long-Term Capital Management, the Greenwich, Connecticut-based hedge fund. He was one of six managers selected from a consortium of 14 global financial institutions to manage the liquidation of LTCM and was one of only two present for the duration. Upon his return, he was given the responsibility as the Chief Operating Officer for the Fixed Income Division, where he had broad oversight responsibilities for the division's risk, technology, operations, and legal issues.</p>
			<p>Brian has a B.A. in economics from Brown University and an M.B.A. from Harvard Business School.</p>
			]]></bio>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>108</id>
		<name>Jud Linville</name>
		<firstname>Jud</firstname>
		<lastname>Linville</lastname>
		<title1>Chief Executive Officer</title1>
		<title2>Citi Cards</title2>
		<title3/>
		<smallImg>linville.jpg</smallImg>
		<opc>yes</opc>
		<bdc>no</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>none</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>no</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>no</sec16exec>
		<speaker/>
		<speakerInfo>
			<highlights>
				<link/>
			</highlights>
			<categories>
				<category/>
			</categories>
			<topic>
				<topicname/>
			</topic>
			<travels>
				<place/>
			</travels>
		</speakerInfo>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<p>Jud Linville joined Citigroup in September 2010 as the Chief Executive Officer of Citi Cards. He is responsible for running the North America Cards business and works closely with regional Cards heads across the globe to develop world-class capabilities and facilitate rapid growth and innovation. Citi's global credit card business provides credit for people and businesses the world over, with activities in 50 countries and across six continents. </p><p>Jud serves on the Global Consumer Banking Council and heads the Global Cards Council.</p><p>Prior to joining Citi, Jud was President and Chief Executive Officer of U.S. Consumer Services at American Express Company. During his 20 years with American Express, Jud held a diverse set of roles and led a variety of business assignments. These included a number of marketing and general management positions, as well as responsibility for the consumer cards, membership rewards, consumer travel, digital assets, and global pre-paid businesses.</p><p>Before leading the Consumer Card Services Group, Jud was Executive Vice President of the Service Delivery Network where he was responsible for all U.S. card member and merchant customer service.</p><p>Jud is a member of the Board of Visitors at Duke University's Fuqua School of Business and the Board of Trustees at Lafayette College. He also serves on the Executive Committee of the Board of Directors at Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts.</p><p>Jud earned a bachelor's degree from Lafayette College and a doctorate in psychology from Drexel University College of Medicine.</p>
			]]></bio>
	</profile>
	
	<profile>
		<id>40</id>
		<name>Carl E. Levinson</name>
		<firstname>Carl E.</firstname>
		<lastname>Levinson</lastname>
		<title1>Head, Productivity Improvement &amp; Re-Engineering</title1>
		<title2>Citi</title2>
		<title3/>
		<title4/>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>no</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>no</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>no</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>no</sec16exec>
		<profilelink/>
		<sec16link/>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>072</id>
		<name>Marty Lippert</name>
		<firstname>Marty</firstname>
		<lastname>Lippert</lastname>
		<title1>Chief Operations and Technology Officer</title1>
		<title2>Citi</title2>
		<title3/>
		<title4/>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>no</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>no</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>no</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>no</sec16exec>
		<profilelink/>
		<sec16link/>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>41</id>
		<name>Andrew N. Liveris</name>
		<firstname>Andrew N.</firstname>
		<lastname>Liveris</lastname>
		<title1>Chairman and Chief Executive Officer, The Dow Chemical Company</title1>
		<title2/>
		<title3/>
		<title4/>
		<boardDir>no</boardDir>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>no</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>no</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>no</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>no</sec16exec>
		<profilelink/>
		<sec16link>liveris/holdings.htm</sec16link>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>42</id>
		<name>Gustavo Marin</name>
		<firstname>Gustavo</firstname>
		<lastname>Marin</lastname>
		<title1>Chief Executive Officer</title1>
		<title2>Citi Brazil</title2>
		<title3/>
		<title4/>
		<smallImg>marin.jpg</smallImg>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>no</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>no</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>no</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>no</sec16exec>
		<profilelink>marin/index.htm</profilelink>
		<sec16link/>
		<speaker>yes</speaker>
		<speakerInfo>
			<highlights>
				<link/>
			</highlights>
			<categories>
				<category>Market Insights</category>
			</categories>
			<topic>
				<topicname>Economic Perspectives on Latin America</topicname>
				<topicname>The Brazilian Economy</topicname>
			</topic>
			<travels>
				<place>Sao Paulo</place>
			</travels>
		</speakerInfo>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<p>Gustavo Marin was appointed the CEO of Citi in Brazil in December 2005. As such, he is responsible for all business segments in the country:  Institutional Clients Group (ICG) , Global Consumer Group (GCG), and Citi Private Bank (CPB). He is a member of Citi Latin America's Management Committee and Citi 's Senior Leadership Committee.</p>
			<p>Mr. Marin served as Citi Country Officer (CCO) of Brazil from June 2000 to December 2005. He took additional responsibilities when he was appointed to serve as Chief Executive Officer for the  Institutional Clients Group in Latin America from March 2004 - December 2005.</p>
			<p>Between 1998 and 2004 he was the Country Business Manager (CBM) for the corporate and investment banking segment and, subsequently, also for GCG and Credicard group operations in Brazil.  Earlier, Mr. Marin had assumed the functions of CCO and CBM for the corporate and investment banking segment in Lima, Peru, in 1996.  Before that, in 1993, he had become the CBM and CCO of Citibank in Asuncion, Paraguay.  Mr. Marin commenced his career at Citi in 1981 in Montevideo, Uruguay. Joining as an executive trainee in the Credit Department, he later became Relationship Manager and afterwards Unit Head for Public Sector and Financial Institutions. He became a Division Head in charge of Transaction Banking in 1988.</p>
			<p>Mr. Marin is a member of the Council of Directors of the Brazilian Federation of Banks (Febraban); a member of the Advisory Board of the Securities, Commodities and Futures Exchange  in Brazil (BM&FBovespa); and a member of the Economic Counsel of the Federation of Industries of the State of Sao Paulo (FIESP).</p>
			<p>He graduated in Finance from Universidad de la Republica, Uruguay, in 1981.</p>
			]]></bio>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>123</id>
		<name>Alan S. MacDonald</name>
		<firstname>Alan S.</firstname>
		<lastname>MacDonald</lastname>
		<title1>Chief Client Officer</title1>
		<title2>Citigroup</title2>
		<title3/>
		<title4/>
		<smallImg>macdonald.jpg</smallImg>
		<speaker/>
		<boardDir/>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>yes</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>no</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>no</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>no</sec16exec>
		<sec16link/>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<p>Alan S. MacDonald is Chief Client Officer of Citi. He also is a Vice Chairman of Citibank, Chairman of the Corporate Client Committee, Chair of Citigroup's Pension Fund Committee and Chairman of Citigroup's Private Equity Funds Committee.</p>
			<p>Prior to assuming his current position, Mr. MacDonald was Chief Operating Officer of Global Corporate and Investment Banking. Over the span of his career at Citi, Mr. MacDonald was head of the Global Corporate Bank, co-head of Global Markets,  and head of Markets & Banking in the United States and Canada. He also held several regional leadership roles including head of Citicorp's International Banking and Finance Sector , and head of Citicorp's North American Investment Bank, and  served as CEO of Banco de Investimento Crefisul, Citicorp's 49 percent-owned investment banking subsidiary in Brazil as well as  head of Citicorp's Leasing, Finance and Export Trading subsidiaries in Colombia, and CEO of Banco Internacional de Colombia, Citicorp's 49 percent-owned commercial banking subsidiary in Colombia.</p>
			<p>Prior to joining Citicorp, Mr. MacDonald was an economist with the United Nations Economic Commission for Europe based in Geneva, Switzerland and was a Financial Management Associate with General Motors in Wilmington, Delaware. </p>
			<p>Mr. MacDonald earned a Bachelor of Science degree from Drexel University in 1966, a Master of Science degree from the London School of Economics in 1968, and a Doctorate in economics at Cambridge University, England in 1971. He is a member of The Conference Board; a member of the Economic Club of New York; a Trustee of the American Council in Germany; a Trustee of the Japan Society; a Trustee of the South Fork (Long Island, N.Y.) Chapter of the Nature Conservancy; a Trustee, member of the Executive Committee, and Chair of the Marketing Committee of the New York Philharmonic Orchestra; a Trustee, and Co-Chairman of the Research Committee of the Hospital for Special Surgery in New York and Chairman of the North American Advisory Board of the London School of Economics. He has served as a Director of Liberty Brokerage Company; a Director of the American Bankers Association Securities Association; and a member of New York Partnership's High Tech Committee.</p>
			]]></bio>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>128</id>
		<name>Mark Mason</name>
		<firstname>Mark</firstname>
		<lastname>Mason</lastname>
		<title1>Chief Operating Officer</title1>
		<title2>Citi Holdings</title2>
		<title3/>
		<title4/>
		<smallImg>mason.jpg</smallImg>
		<speaker/>
		<boardDir/>
		<opc>yes</opc>
		<bdc>no</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>no</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>no</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>no</sec16exec>
		<sec16link/>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<p>Mark Mason is COO of Citi Holdings and, beginning January 2012, he will assume a new role as CEO of Citi Holdings
.</p>
			<p>Mr. Mason has been with Citi since 2001 and has held various positions throughout the company. In November 2011, he was named CEO of Citi Holdings, which comprises Brokerage and Asset Management, Global Consumer Finance and Citi's Special Assets Portfolios.</p> 
			<p>Prior to becoming COO, Mr. Mason spent three years as Chief Financial Officer and Head of Strategy and M&A for Citi's Global Wealth Management Unit. He also spent three years as Chief of Staff to Citigroup's Chairman and CEO and was instrumental in the formation of Citigroup Alternative Investments and the development of its client-focused strategy. He held several positions there, including Head of Strategy, Planning and Analysis. In addition, he served as CFO and COO for Citigroup Real Estate Investments, where he was responsible for restructuring the business.</p>
			<p>Prior to joining Citigroup, Mr. Mason spent three years with Lucent Technologies as Director of Strategy and Business Development. He also spent several years as a strategy consultant with Marakon Associates working with a number of Fortune 100 companies to develop strategies to maximize shareholder value. Mark also has experience in investment banking with Goldman, Sachs & Co.</p>
			<p>Mr. Mason holds a Bachelor of Business Administration degree in finance and graduated with honors from Howard University in 1991. He also holds a Master of Business Administration degree from Harvard Business School. Mr. Mason has been recognized by Crain's New York Business "2008 40 Under 40," 2008 YMCA Business Leadership Award, Black Enterprise's "2009 100 Most Powerful Executives in Corporate America" and Howard University as a 2011 Distinguished Alumni in Business.  Mark is a member of the Board of Directors of Primerica Inc. and the United Negro College Fund. He is also a member of Kappa Alpha Psi Fraternity, Incorporated.</p>]]></bio>
	</profile>	
	<profile>
		<id>43</id>
		<name>Mary McDowell</name>
		<firstname>Mary</firstname>
		<lastname>McDowell</lastname>
		<title1>President &amp; Chief Executive Officer</title1>
		<title2>CitiFinancial North America</title2>
		<title3/>
		<title4/>
		<smallImg>mcdowell.jpg</smallImg>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>no</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>no</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>no</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>no</sec16exec>
		<profilelink>mcdowell/index.htm</profilelink>
		<sec16link/>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<p>Mary McDowell is President and Chief Executive Officer for CitiFinancial North America, where she oversees 12,000 employees and manages CitiFinancial's 2,300 branch network with operations in the United States, Canada and Puerto Rico, as well as Citi Assurance. In this role, she is responsible for managing the CitiFinancial franchise and leading key strategic initiatives.  She is a member of Citi's Senior Leadership Committee.</p>
			<p>Mary joined Citi in 1991, serving as Chief Financial Officer for American Health and Life (now CitiAssurance), CitiFinancial, CitiFinancial Mortgage Company, and Citicorp Trust Bank.  In 2003, Mary was named President of CitiFinancial Auto, where she integrated three auto-financing brands - Arcadia, Auto One, and Trans South - into CitiFinancial Auto.  Beginning in July 2006, she served as the President and Chief Operating Officer for CitiFinancial North America, with responsibility for managing the operations of the 2,400-branch network. She was promoted to President and CEO of CitiFinancial in April 2007 and later gained responsibility for CitiFinancial Auto and Citi Assurance.</p>
			<p>Prior to joining Citi, she spent 11 years with Ernst & Young, serving clients in the financial services industry through audit, tax and consulting services including due diligence for acquisitions.</p>
			<p>Mary is the Chairman of CitiFinancial Credit Company and Co-Chairs Citi's Maryland Leadership Council, comprised of Citi business leaders located in Maryland.  She is on the Executive Committee and the Board of Directors of AFSA (American Financial Services Association), and was recently nominated as Chairman-Elect for 2011 for AFSA.   She is also on the Board of Directors of The Living Classrooms Foundation.  She is past Chairwoman of Citi's Texas Leadership Council, and has also served on the vehicle finance advisory boards of AFSA (American Financial Services Association) and CBA (Consumer Bankers Association) and the Board of Directors of TBEC (Texas Business and Education Coalition). She is also business sponsor of Citi's Women's Network - Baltimore/Washington.</p>
			<p>Mary was born in Cameron, Texas and graduated <i>Summa cum Laude</i> from Texas A&M University with a BBA. She is a Certified Public Accountant, Chartered Financial Consultant, and a Chartered Life Underwriter.</p>
			]]></bio>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>44</id>
		<name>Raymond McGuire</name>
		<firstname>Raymond</firstname>
		<lastname>McGuire</lastname>
		<title1>Head, Global Banking</title1>
		<title2>Institutional Clients Group</title2>
		<title3/>
		<title4/>
		<smallImg>mcguire.jpg</smallImg>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>yes</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>no</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>no</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>no</sec16exec>
		<profilelink>mcguire/index.htm</profilelink>
		<sec16link/>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<p>Raymond McGuire is Head of Global Banking at Citi. He is responsible for managing the coverage of Global Industries and clients and executing strategic transactions. Mr. McGuire is a member of the Institutional Clients Group's Executive Committee and Business Practices Committee and has advised on landmark transactions valued at more than $200 billion.</p>
			<p>Prior to joining Citi, Mr. McGuire was the Global Co-Head of Mergers & Acquisitions at Morgan Stanley; Managing Director in the Mergers & Acquisitions Group of Merrill Lynch & Co., Inc.; and one of the original members of Wasserstein Perella & Co. where he became a Partner/Managing Director in 1991. He started his career in 1984 in Mergers & Acquisitions at The First Boston Corporation. </p>
			<p>Presently, Mr. McGuire serves on several boards, including the De La Salle Academy, Foundation for Art and Preservation in Embassies, the Alex Hillman Family Foundation, the International Center of Photography Lincoln Center, New York-Presbyterian Hospital, The New York Public Library, the Studio Museum in Harlem and the Whitney Museum of American Art. He is also a Director of the Wyeth Corporation. In the past, he served on the boards of the Joseph & Claire Flom Foundation, the Howard Gilman Foundation, the Hotchkiss School, and the San Remo Tenants' Corporation and served on various Visiting Committees at Harvard University.</p>
			<p>In 2009, he received the Humanitarian Leadership Award from the Council of Urban Professionals; in 2008 he was presented the Frederick Douglas Award by the New York Urban League and was inducted by Morehouse College as one of the inaugural members of the Martin Luther King, Jr. International Board of Renaissance Leaders. </p>
			<p>He has been featured in <i>Black Enterprise Magazine</i> as one of the 100 Most Powerful Executives in Corporate America and on Wall Street, and by <i>Avenue Magazine</i> one as of New York's 50 Smartest. Mr. McGuire has been honored by the Make-A-Wish Foundation and Art for Life Foundation. Pratt Institute honored him as its inaugural distinguished "Patron of the Arts." He has also been honored with Harvard Business School's African-American Student Union's Professional Achievement Award, has presented at Harvard Law School's Traphagen Distinguished Alumni Speaker Series and emceed the first Harvard College Black Alumni Weekend.</p>
			<p>He received his M.B.A. and J.D. from Harvard Business School and Harvard Law School (1984), and an A.B., <i>cum laude</i>, from Harvard College (1979). He also attended the University of Nice, France while on a Rotary Fellowship (1980). He has had legal experience at the law firms of Skadden, Arps, Slate, Meagher & Flom as well as Patterson, Belknap, Webb & Tyler.</p>
			]]></bio>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>45</id>
		<name>Paul McKinnon</name>
		<firstname>Paul</firstname>
		<lastname>McKinnon</lastname>
		<title1>Head of Human Resources</title1>
		<title2>Citigroup</title2>
		<title3/>
		<title4/>
		<smallImg>mckinnon.jpg</smallImg>
		<speaker>yes</speaker>
		<opc>yes</opc>
		<bdc>no</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>no</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>no</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>no</sec16exec>
		<profilelink>mckinnon/index.htm</profilelink>
		<speakerInfo>
			<highlights>
				<link/>
			</highlights>
			<categories>
				<category>Corporate Citizenship and Governance</category>
			</categories>
			<topic>
				<topicname/>
			</topic>
			<travels>
				<place>New York</place>
			</travels>
		</speakerInfo>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<p>Paul joined Citi on Feb. 1, 2008 with 25 years experience in Human Resources management, consulting and education. He is responsible for all of Human Resources for Citigroup, and for all Talent Management programs. Prior to this assignment, he was Head of Talent Management for Citigroup.</p>
			<p>Until early 2007, Paul was Senior Vice President of the Human Resources Group for Dell, with responsibility for all aspects of the function. During his 10 years with Dell, Paul was instrumental in the company's Winning Culture initiative, which included all Dell's training and development activities, winning external and internal awards, including the coveted EVE award from the U.S. Department of Labor for secretary’s equal opportunity programs. Paul also was Chairman of the Dell Foundation. </p>
			<p>Prior to Dell, he developed a leadership development practice at three separate management consulting firms: McKinnon Consulting, Novations and Harbridge House. Previously, Paul was an assistant professor at the Darden Graduate School of Business at the University of Virginia, where he taught Organizational Behavior. </p>
			<p>Paul currently serves on the Board of Directors of the HR Policy Association and the National Urban League, where he currently serves as Board Secretary. He was inducted as a Fellow into the National Academy of Human Resources in 2002. </p>
			<p>He has a bachelor's degree in history and a master's degree in Organizational Behavior from Brigham Young University, and a Ph.D. in organizational studies from the Sloan School of Management at MIT. </p>
			<p>He is a co-editor of The Chief HR Officer, and in 2011 was named “Human Resources Executive of the Year” by the Academy of Management.  </p>

			]]></bio>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>78</id>
		<name>Gene McQuade</name>
		<firstname>Gene</firstname>
		<lastname>McQuade</lastname>
		<title1>Chief Executive Officer</title1>
		<title2>Citibank, N.A. </title2>
		<title3/>
		<title4/>
		<smallImg>mcquade.jpg</smallImg>
		<speaker>yes</speaker>
		<opc>yes</opc>
		<bdc>yes</bdc>		
		<executivecommittee>none</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>no</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>yes</sec16exec>
		<profilelink>mcquade/index.htm</profilelink>
		<sec16link>mcquade/holdings.htm</sec16link>
		<speakerInfo>
			<highlights>
				<link/>
			</highlights>
			<categories>
				<category>The Global Economic Landscape</category>
				<category>Market Insights</category>
			</categories>
			<topic>
				<topicname/>
			</topic>
			<travels>
				<place>New York</place>
			</travels>
		</speakerInfo>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<p>Eugene M. McQuade is Chief Executive Officer of Citibank N.A., a role he assumed in August 2009. In that role, Mr. McQuade has responsibility for corporate governance and franchise management of Citibank in 101 countries around the globe. McQuade also has oversight responsibility for the Corporate Audit and Corporate Compliance departments of Citigroup. He serves on the Board of Citibank.</p>
			<p>McQuade most recently served as Vice Chairman and President of Merrill Lynch Banks (U.S.). Prior to joining Merrill, McQuade served for three years as President and Chief Operating Officer and a Director of FreddieMac. Previously, he had been President of Bank of America, helping to bring about the 2004 merger between that company and FleetBoston Financial, where he served as President and Chief Operating Officer. McQuade served on the Board of Directors of both Bank of America and FleetBoston.</p>
			<p>Before working at Fleet, McQuade served as Executive Vice President and Controller at Manufacturers Hanover Corp., a predecessor of J.P. Morgan Chase. McQuade began his career at KPMG Peat Marwick in New York.</p>
			<p>Originally from New York City, McQuade is a Certified Public Accountant. He earned a degree in accounting from St. Bonaventure University, of which he was a Trustee. McQuade is also a Director of XL Group plc, an Ireland-based insurance and reinsurance company. He was recently named as a Trustee to The Boys & Girls Club of America.</p>
			]]></bio>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>46</id>
		<name>Manuel Medina-Mora</name>
		<firstname>Manuel</firstname>
		<lastname>Medina-Mora</lastname>
		<title1>Chief Executive Officer</title1>
		<title2>Global Consumer Banking and Chairman of the Global Consumer Council</title2>
		<title3/>
		<title4/>
		<smallImg>medinamora.jpg</smallImg>
		<speaker>yes</speaker>
		<opc>yes</opc>
		<bdc>yes</bdc>			
		<executivecommittee>none</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>no</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>yes</sec16exec>
		<speakerInfo>
			<highlights>
				<link/>
			</highlights>
			<categories>
				<category>Market Insights</category>
				<category>Global Economic Landscape</category>
			</categories>
			<topic>
				<topicname>Global Financial Landscape</topicname>
				<topicname>Economies of Mexico &amp; Latin America</topicname>
			</topic>
			<travels>
				<place>Mexico City</place>
				<place>New York</place>
			</travels>
		</speakerInfo>
		<profilelink>medina/index.htm</profilelink>
		<sec16link>medina/holdings.htm</sec16link>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<p>Manuel Medina-Mora is CEO of Global Consumer Banking, which includes Retail and Commercial Banking, Citi Cards, Citi Mortgage and Citi Retail Partner Cards worldwide. He is also Chairman of Latin America and Mexico. </p>
			<p>His oversight of Citi's Latin America and Mexico businesses include: Markets & Banking, eBanking, Treasury, Consumer Bank, Cards Business, Retail Banking, Insurance, Pension Funds, Securities, Brokerage and Asset Management. </p>
			<p>He started his career with Banamex in 1971 in the area of corporate banking. Later, he assumed responsibilities within the international arena. In 1990 he led Banamex's privatization and, as a result of Grupo Financiero Banamex-Accival's creation in 1991, he became the Deputy President responsible for bank strategy and corporate development. He was appointed CEO of Grupo Financiero Banamex-Accival in 1996, then was CEO of Banamex from 2001 to 2006.</p>
			<p>Mr. Medina-Mora holds a bachelor's degree in business administration from the Universidad Iberoamericana in Mexico and an M.B.A. from the Graduate School of Business of Stanford University.</p>
			]]></bio>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>114</id>
		<name>Rajesh Mehta</name>
		<firstname>Rajesh</firstname>
		<lastname>Mehta</lastname>
		<title1>Managing Director</title1>
		<title2>Regional Head of Treasury and Trade Solutions, Europe Middle East &amp; Africa</title2>
		<title3>Global Transaction Services, Citi</title3>
		<smallImg>mehta.jpg</smallImg>
		<speaker>yes</speaker>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>no</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>no</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>no</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>no</sec16exec>
		<speakerInfo>
			<highlights>
				<link/>
			</highlights>
			<categories>
				<category>The Future of Banking</category>
			</categories>
			<topic>
				<topicname>Innovative Payment Systems</topicname>
			</topic>
			<travels>
				<place>London</place>
			</travels>
		</speakerInfo>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<p>Rajesh Mehta is the Treasury and Trade Solutions Head for Citi Global Transaction Services in Europe Middle East & Africa (EMEA). He is responsible for the provision of cash management, treasury and trade solutions to a broad range of customers including financial institutions, governments, multinational corporations, top local companies, small and medium enterprises.</p>
			<p>GTS's Treasury and Trade Services delivers comprehensive solutions and services to global and domestic corporations, financial institutions and the public sector.</p>
			<p>GTS provides industry leading cash management, treasury and trade services and trade finance solutions to corporations, financial institutions and government entities across the globe through its Treasury and Trade Solutions (TTS) business, and custody and clearing services, fund services, securities finance and issuer services to capital markets participants world-wide through its Securities and Fund Services (SFS) business. </p>
			<p>Rajesh has been with Citi for 26 years and has held numerous roles across the globe throughout his career. He began working for Citi in India and then moved to Singapore, then as Cash Management and Trade Head for Indonesia, Global Transaction Services Head for Mexico and Regional Cash Management and Trade Head for Latin America, based in Buenos Aires. In 2002, he was appointed Global Transaction Services Head for Sub Saharan Africa, based in Johannesburg.  In January 2007, Rajesh moved to London to become the Regional Payments Head for EMEA, assuming responsibility for Cash Management in October 2007 and his current position in March 2008.</p>
			<p>Rajesh holds a bachelors degree in economics from St. Stephen's College, Delhi University and an MBA from the Indian Institute of Management, Ahmedabad.</p>
			]]></bio>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>47</id>
		<name>William J. Mills</name>
		<firstname>William J.</firstname>
		<lastname>Mills</lastname>
		<title1>Chief Executive Officer</title1>
		<title2>Europe, Middle East and Africa</title2>
		<title3/>
		<title4/>
		<smallImg>mills.jpg</smallImg>
		<speaker>yes</speaker>
		<opc>yes</opc>
		<bdc>no</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>none</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>no</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>yes</sec16exec>
		<profilelink>mills/index.htm</profilelink>
		<sec16link>mills/holdings.htm</sec16link>
		<speakerInfo>
			<highlights>
				<link/>
			</highlights>
			<categories>
				<category>The Global Economic Landscape</category>
				<category>Market Insights</category>
			</categories>
			<topic>
				<topicname>Economic Landscape in EMEA</topicname>
				<topicname>The Future of Africa's Capital Markets</topicname>
			</topic>
			<travels>
				<place>London</place>
			</travels>
		</speakerInfo>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<p>Bill Mills is CEO of Europe, Middle East, and Africa (EMEA) for Citi, with a focus on Western Europe and Africa, representing 33 of the region’s 54 countries. Beginning in January 2012, Bill will be CEO of North America for Citi.</p>
			<p>Partnering with Alberto Verme, joint CEO of EMEA with a focus on Central & Eastern Europe and the Middle East, Bill is responsible for the performance of all of Citi’s businesses in EMEA. Citi is engaged in serving a broad range of client segments across the region, including consumers, corporations, institutions and governments. </p>
			<p>Prior to his current role, Bill was Chairman and Chief Executive Officer of Citi Markets & Banking for EMEA.</p>
			<p>Bill has more than 35 years of experience in investment banking, including 29 with Citi. Before relocating to London, he was Chief Executive Officer of Salomon Smith Barney Asia Pacific and a member of the Salomon Smith Barney Management Committee. In that role, Bill was responsible for the Firm's investment banking, equity, fixed income, private client services, and other operations conducted in Asia, Australia, New Zealand and the sub-continent.</p>
			<p>Bill began his Citi career in New York where he formed and headed the debt origination and securitization group at Smith Barney, served as co-head of Smith Barney's Financial Institutions Division, and spent five years as co-head of the Investment Banking Division. Before joining Smith Barney in 1982, he was a Vice President at Standard & Poor's Corporation, where he was a member of the Structured Finance Rating Committee.</p>
			<p>Bill is a Board Member of the Global Financial Markets Association (GFMA), the British Bankers Association (BBA) and Akbank, the Turkish bank in which Citi holds a 20 percent strategic equity stake, and was a Member of the Chancellor of the Exchequer's Financial Services Global Competitiveness Group. He is a Member of the Advisory Council to TheCityUK. Bill is a Member of the Advisory Board of Career Academies UK and serves as the Chair of EMEA's CitiDifference Diversity Steering Committee.</p>
			<p>Bill is Chairman and CEO of Citigroup Global Markets Limited and of Citigroup Global Markets UK Equity Limited. He is a Director of Citibank International plc, Citibank Europe plc, Citibank Investments Limited and Citigroup Global Markets Europe Limited.</p>
			<p>He is a 1977 graduate of Denison University.</p>
			]]></bio>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>124</id>
		<name>Alasdair Morrison</name>
		<firstname>Alasdair</firstname>
		<lastname>Morrison</lastname>
		<title1>Senior Advisor</title1>
		<title2>Citi Asia</title2>
		<title3/>
		<title4/>
		<smallImg>morrison.jpg</smallImg>
		<speaker/>
		<boardDir/>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>yes</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>no</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>no</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>no</sec16exec>
		<sec16link/>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<p>Alasdair Morrison is a British national who has lived and worked in Asia since 1971. He holds a number of non-executive directorships and participates in a number of government and community organizations.</p>
			<p>From 1971 to 2000, Alasdair Morrison worked for the Jardine Matheson Group, a dominant regional multinational enterprise with a portfolio of businesses in over thirty countries employing over 160,000 people. In 1994, Mr. Morrison became Group Managing Director for the Jardine Matheson Group. He was Chairman of Jardine Matheson Ltd and managing director of Hong Kong Land, Dairy Farm, Mandarin Oriental and Jardine Strategic. He also held the position of Chairman of the Supervisory Board of Jardine Fleming.</p>
			<p>Subsequently, and until April 2007, he was a Managing Director of Morgan Stanley and a member of the Firm's Management Committee. From 2000 to 2007, he was Chairman of Morgan Stanley Asia, based in Hong Kong. From 2002 to February 2006, he was concurrently Chairman and Chief Executive Officer of Morgan Stanley Asia.</p>
			<p>Over his many years in Asia, including living and working in Hong Kong, Australia and the Philippines, Mr. Morrison has built extensive regional contacts in the corporate and government community. He has participated in a number of high level government-sponsored working groups and is an active member of the community in Hong Kong.</p>
			<p>He is currently Senior Advisor of Citigroup Asia Pacific, a leading global financial services company. He is an independent non-executive director of Pacific Basin Shipping Limited, MTR Corporation Ltd and the Hong Kong Mercantile Exchange, and a member of the Board of Grosvenor Group Limited in the U.K. He is also a member of the Hong Kong/European Union Business Cooperation Committee, a Director of the Hong Kong Forum, and was a member of the Bloomberg Asia Pacific Advisory Board, a member of the CapitaLand International Advisory Panel in Singapore, a member of the Operations Review Committee of the Independent Commission Against Corruption (ICAC), a Trustee of the Lord Wilson Heritage Trust, a member of the Law Reform Commission, the Construction Industry Review Committee, the Hong Kong/U.S. Business Council, past Chairman of the Supervisory Board of the British Chamber of Commerce, past Vice Chairman of the Harvard Business School Association of Hong Kong, past Chieftain of the Hong Kong St. Andrew's Society, and past Chairman of the Fundraising Committee of the Changing Young Lives Foundation (formerly Save the Children Fund).</p>
			<p>Mr. Morrison was born in Scotland on September 29, 1948, and is a graduate of Eton College and Cambridge University. He attended the Program for Management Development at Harvard Business School in 1983.</p>
			]]></bio>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>48</id>
		<name>Robert Morse</name>
		<firstname>Robert</firstname>
		<lastname>Morse</lastname>
		<title1>Chief Executive Officer, Asia Pacific</title1>
		<title2>Institutional Clients Group</title2>
		<title3/>
		<title4/>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>no</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>no</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>no</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>no</sec16exec>
		<profilelink/>
		<sec16link/>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>49</id>
		<name>Anne Mulcahy</name>
		<firstname>Anne</firstname>
		<lastname>Mulcahy</lastname>
		<title1>Chairman, Xerox Corporation</title1>
		<title2/>
		<title3/>
		<title4/>
		<boardDir>no</boardDir>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>no</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>no</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>no</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>no</sec16exec>
		<profilelink/>
		<sec16link/>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>89</id>
		<name>Anthony J. Nappi</name>
		<firstname>Anthony J.</firstname>
		<lastname>Nappi</lastname>
		<title1>Asia Pacific Region Head</title1>
		<title2>Global Transaction Services Citi</title2>
		<smallImg>nappi.jpg</smallImg>
		<speaker>yes</speaker>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>no</bdc>
		<speakerInfo>
			<highlights>
				<link/>
			</highlights>
			<categories>
				<category>Market Insights</category>
			</categories>
			<topic>
				<topicname>Asia: Catalyst for MNC Growth</topicname>
			</topic>
			<travels>
				<place>Hong Kong</place>
			</travels>
		</speakerInfo>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<p>Anthony Nappi is Managing Director and Asia Pacific Region Head of Global Transaction Services (GTS), a business unit of Citi's Institutional Clients Group. Global Transaction Services offers is one of Citi's publicly reported businesses lines, offering award winning and industry leading Treasury and Trade Solutions and Securities and Fund Services capabilities to corporations, governments, financial institutions and investment advisors worldwide, including eighteen countries in Asia Pacific.</p>
			<p>Citi's Global Transaction Services is consistently recognized as a pre-eminent provider by clients and the industry. In 2009, Citi was honored with multiple awards, including Best Cash Management Bank in Asia by <i>Asiamoney</i>, <i>FinanceAsia</i> and <i>Euromoney</i>, voted Best Trade Bank in Asia for the 5th consecutive year by <i>Trade Finance</i> and named #1 in Asia in <i>Global Custodian's</i> Mutual Fund Administrator survey, as well as Asia <i>Asset Management's</i> Best Local Custodian in Asia in the Securities and Fund Services space.</p>
			<p>Prior to being named Asia Pacific Region Head of Global Transaction Services in 2006, Anthony was the Regional Head of Cash Management as well as the Chief Operating Officer for Global Transaction Services.</p>
			<p>Anthony's banking career spans more than twenty years. He started as a management trainee in Citibank in New York, and has worked a number of roles including business management, financial control, operations, customer service, product management and sales. He has worked in New York, Florida, Chicago, Singapore, and Hong Kong.</p>
			<p>In 2008, Anthony was named <i>The Asset's</i> Transaction Banker of the Year, where he was recognized for "taking care of the cutomers... in a business that puts a preimium on relationship and quick response". In 2009, Anthony was also included in <i>FinanceAsia</i> magazine's inaugural list of 50 masters of Asian finance. This list was formed through a combination of the opinion of readers, website poll and feedback from finance professionals and peers. In naming Anthony, the editors said, "Nappi leads the well-oiled machine that is Citi's transaction banking business in Asia. Despite the bank already being one of the largest cash and trade institutions in the region, he has overseen almost a doubling in annual revenue since taking the helm in 2006. That has helped him maintain Citi's place at the forefront of Asian transaction services."</p>
			<p>Anthony holds a BA in Political Science and a Master's Degree in Business Management from the University of South Florida.</p>
			<p>A native of New York City, Anthony is based in Hong Kong.</p>
			]]></bio>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>50</id>
		<name>Sanjay Nayar</name>
		<firstname>Sanjay</firstname>
		<lastname>Nayar</lastname>
		<title1>Chief Executive Officer, India</title1>
		<title2>Area Head, Bangladesh, Nepal &amp; Sri Lanka, Citi Markets &amp; Banking</title2>
		<title3/>
		<title4/>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>no</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>no</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>no</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>no</sec16exec>
		<profilelink/>
		<sec16link/>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>125</id>
		<name>James O'Donnell</name>
		<firstname>James</firstname>
		<lastname>O'Donnell</lastname>
		<title1>Global Head of Investor Sales and Relationship Management</title1>
		<title2>Institutional Clients Group</title2>
		<title3/>
		<title4/>
		<smallImg>odonnell.jpg</smallImg>
		<speaker/>
		<boardDir/>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>yes</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>no</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>no</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>no</sec16exec>
		<sec16link/>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<p>Jim O'Donnell is a Managing Director and Global Head of Investor Sales and Relationship Management at Citi. Mr. O'Donnell was appointed to this position in August 2008; prior to that, he was Co-Head of Global Investor Sales. Mr. O'Donnell is responsible for the distribution of Global Markets products to Citi's Equities, Fixed Income, Currencies and Commodities clients. </p>
			<p>For the four years prior, Mr. O'Donnell served as Head of U.S. Equities for Citi. He joined the firm in July 1999 as Head of European Equities. Prior to joining Citi, Mr. O'Donnell was President and CEO of HSBC Securities Inc. in New York. He was responsible for all equity, debt, futures and investment banking operations for HSBC in the U.S. and was CEO of HSBC James Capel, HSBC's Global Equity business.</p>
			<p>Prior to HSBC, he was President and CEO of NatWest Securities in the United States. He held various roles at Drexel Burnham Lambert from 1986 to 1990, including Head of Sales and Trading for International Equities and Co-Head of Global Equity Trading. </p>
			<p>Mr. O'Donnell holds a bachelor's degree in comparative religion from Princeton University.</p>
			]]></bio>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>73</id>
		<name>Michael E. O'Neill</name>
		<firstname>Michael E.</firstname>
		<lastname>O'Neill</lastname>
		<title1>Former Chairman and CEO, Bank of Hawaii Corporation</title1>
		<title2/>
		<title3/>
		<title4/>
		<smallImg>oneill.jpg</smallImg>
		<boardDir>yes</boardDir>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>no</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>no</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>yes</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>no</sec16exec>
		<profilelink/>
		<sec16link>oneill/holdings.htm</sec16link>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<ul class="list" style="width: 355px;">
				<li>Chairman, Chief Executive Officer and Director, Bank of Hawaii Corporation - 2000 to 2004</li>
				<li>Elected Chief Executive Officer, Barclay's PLC - 1999</li>
				<li>Vice Chairman and Chief Financial Officer, Bank of America - 1995 to 1998</li>
				<li>Chief Financial Officer, Continental Bank - 1993 to 1995</li>
				<li>Director of Citigroup since 2009</li>
				<li>Director of Citibank, N.A. since 2009 </li>
				<li>Other Directorships: FT Ventures (Advisory Board)</li>
				<li>Previous Directorships within the last five years: N/A</li>
				<li>Other Activities: Hawaii Pacific University (Trustee) and Honolulu Academy of Arts (Trustee)</li>
			</ul>
			]]></bio>		
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>126</id>
		<name>Peter Orszag</name>
		<firstname>Peter</firstname>
		<lastname>Orszag</lastname>
		<title1>Vice Chairman</title1>
		<title2>Global Banking</title2>
		<title3>Institutional Clients Group</title3>
		<title4/>
		<smallImg>orszag.jpg</smallImg>
		<speaker/>
		<boardDir/>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>yes</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>no</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>no</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>no</sec16exec>
		<sec16link/>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<p>Peter R. Orszag is Vice Chairman of Global Banking at Citigroup, Inc. and a member of the Senior Strategic Advisory Group there. He is also an Adjunct Senior Fellow at the Council on Foreign Relations. Prior to joining Citigroup in January 2011, he served as a Distinguished Visiting Fellow at the Council on Foreign Relations and a Contributing Columnist at the <i>New York Times</i>. </p>
			<p>Dr. Orszag previously served as the Director of the Office of Management and Budget in the Obama Administration from January 2009 until July 2010, having been confirmed by the Senate on January 20, 2009. In that Cabinet-level role, he oversaw the Administration's budget policy, coordinated the implementation of major policy initiatives throughout the federal government, and reviewed federal regulatory action, among other responsibilities. From January 2007 to December 2008, Dr. Orszag was the Director of the Congressional Budget Office (CBO), supervising the agency's work in providing objective, nonpartisan and timely analyses of economic and budgetary issues. Under his leadership, the agency significantly expanded its focus on areas such as health care and climate change. </p>
			<p>Prior to CBO, Dr. Orszag was the Joseph A. Pechman Senior Fellow and Deputy Director of Economic Studies at the Brookings Institution. While at Brookings, he also served as Director of The Hamilton Project, Director of the Retirement Security Project and Co-Director of the Tax Policy Center. During the Clinton Administration, he was a Special Assistant to the President for Economic Policy and, before that, a staff economist and then Senior Advisor and Senior Economist at the President's Council of Economic Advisers. Dr. Orszag has also founded and subsequently sold an economics consulting firm.</p>
			<p>Dr. Orszag graduated <i>summa cum laude</i> in economics from Princeton University and obtained a Ph.D. in economics from the London School of Economics, which he attended as a Marshall Scholar. He has coauthored or co-edited a number of books, including <i>Protecting the Homeland</i> (2006), <i>Aging Gracefully: Ideas to Improve Retirement Security in America</i> (2006), <i>Saving Social Security: A Balanced Approach</i> (2004), and <i>American Economic Policy in the 1990s</i> (2002). He is a member of the Institute of Medicine of the National Academies of Sciences, the Council on Foreign Relations, the Hamilton Project Advisory Council, the Marshall Scholarship Alumni Advisory Board, and Phi Beta Kappa. </p>
			<p>Dr. Orszag is married to Bianna Golodryga, an anchor on ABC's <i>Good Morning America</i>.</p>
			]]></bio>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>51</id>
		<name>Vikram Pandit</name>
		<firstname>Vikram</firstname>
		<lastname>Pandit</lastname>
		<title1>Chief Executive Officer</title1>
		<title2>Citigroup Inc</title2>
		<title3/>
		<title4/>
		<smallImg>pandit.jpg</smallImg>
		<highRes>pandit.jpg</highRes>
		<boardDir>yes</boardDir>
		<opc>yes</opc>
		<bdc>yes</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>none</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>yes</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>no</sec16exec>
		<profilelink>pandit/index.htm</profilelink>
		<sec16link>pandit/holdings.htm</sec16link>
		<news><![CDATA[
			<b style="color: #636563; font-size: 1.1em;">Vikram Pandit in the News</b>
			<ul class="list">
				
				<li><a href="http://economictimes.indiatimes.com/opinion/interviews/ceos-dont-run-a-popularity-contest-they-take-tough-calls-vikram-pandit-ceo-citigroup/articleshow/7606806.cms" target="_top">Interview with the Economic Times</a></li>
				<li><a href="http://www.citigroup.com/citi/press/executive.htm" target="_top">Latest speeches</a></li>
				<li><a href="http://online.wsj.com/article/SB10001424052748703727804576011862205476634.html" target="_top"><i>Wall Street Journal</i> profile</a> (requires login)</li>
				<li><a href="http://new.citi.com/2011/02/pandit-on-harvard-us-competitiveness-panel.shtml#more" target="_top">Harvard U.S. competitiveness panel address</a></li>                     
				<li><a href="http://new.citi.com/2011/01/pandit-interviewed-at-davos.shtml" target="_top">Davos interview</a></li>
				<li><a href="http://new.citi.com/2010/12/pandit-on-trends-driving-citis-strategy-investment-and-growth-1.shtml" target="_top">On Citi's strategy for the future</a></li>
			</ul>
			]]></news>
			<social><![CDATA[<a href="http://www.facebook.com/VikramPanditCiti"><img src="/citi/corporategovernance/profiles/images/a_facebook.gif" border="0" alt="Vikram Pandit on Facebook"></a>]]></social>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<p>Vikram Pandit is the Chief Executive Officer of Citigroup, the world's global bank, with approximately 200 million customer accounts and activities in more than 160 countries and jurisdictions.</p>
			<p>Born in India, Pandit moved to the United States at age 16. He enrolled in Columbia University, earning B.S. and M.S. degrees in engineering. Pandit received his Ph.D. in finance from Columbia in 1986. </p>
			<p>He joined Morgan Stanley in 1983 and ultimately rose to the post of President and Chief Operating Officer of the company's institutional securities and investment banking businesses. </p>
			<p>Pandit left Morgan Stanley to become a founding member and chairman of the members committee of Old Lane, LP. When Old Lane was acquired by Citi in 2007, Pandit became Chairman and CEO of Citi Alternative Investments. He later led Citi's Institutional Clients Group, and on Dec. 11, 2007, was named Citi's CEO.</p>
			<p>Upon his appointment, Pandit embarked on a plan to refocus, recapitalize and restructure Citi during the toughest economic climate since the Great Depression. With the goals of long-term profitability and fueling economic recovery and growth at its core, Pandit's strategy for building a new Citi is centered on the company's historic strengths and unique competitive advantages: its global franchise, unique emerging market footprint, innovative spirit and talented and diverse employee base.</p>
			<p>At Citi, Pandit has made Responsible Finance a priority. Citi is committed to providing choice, control and transparency for clients, managing risk responsibly and contributing to economic growth. From innovative foreclosure prevention programs that have kept more than 1,000,000 Americans in their homes to a new, disciplined approach to risk management, Responsible Finance is being engrained throughout Citi's practices and culture. </p>
			<p>Mr. Pandit serves on the boards of Columbia University, Columbia Business School and the Indian School of Business. A naturalized citizen, he lives in New York City with his wife and two children.</p>
			]]></bio>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>52</id>
		<name>Richard D. Parsons</name>
		<firstname>Richard D.</firstname>
		<lastname>Parsons</lastname>
		<title1>Chairman, Citigroup Inc.</title1>
		<title2/>
		<title3/>
		<title4/>
		<smallImg>parsons.jpg</smallImg>
		<boardDir>yes</boardDir>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>no</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>no</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>yes</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>no</sec16exec>
		<profilelink/>
		<sec16link>parsons/holdings.htm</sec16link>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<ul class="list" style="width: 355px;">
				<li>Chairman, Citigroup Inc. - 2009 to present</li>
				<li>Senior Advisor, Providence Equity Partners Inc. - 2009 to present</li>
				<li>Chairman, Time Warner Inc. - 2003 to 2008</li>
				<li>Chief Executive Officer - 2002 to 2007</li>
				<li>Co-Chief Operating Officer - 2001 to 2002</li>
				<li>President - 1995 to 2000</li>
				<li>Director, Time Warner Inc. (or predecessor) - 1991 to 2008</li>
				<li>Chairman and Chief Executive Officer, Dime Savings Bank of New York - 1991 to 1995</li>
				<li>President and Chief Operating Officer - 1988 to 1990</li>
				<li>Associate, Partner and Managing Partner, Patterson, Belknap, Webb & Tyler - 1977 to 1988</li>
				<li>General Counsel and Associate Director, Domestic Council, White House - 1975 to 1977</li>
				<li>Deputy Counsel to the Vice President, Office of the Vice President of the United States - 1975</li>
				<li>Assistant and First Assistant Counsel to the Governor, State of New York - 1971 to 1974</li>
				<li>Director of Citigroup (or predecessor) since 1996</li>
				<li>Citibank, N.A. director - 1996 to 1998</li>
				<li>Other Directorships: The Estee Lauder Companies Inc., and Madison Square Garden, Inc.</li>
				<li>Previous Directorships within the last five years: Time Warner Inc.</li>
				<li>Other Activities: Apollo Theatre Foundation (Chairman), Museum of Modern Art (Trustee), American Museum of Natural History (Trustee), New York City Partnership (Director), Smithsonian Institute of African American History and Culture (Co-Chairman of the Advisory Board), Rockefeller Foundation (Trustee), Jazz Foundation of America (Chairman of the Board), New York City Commission for Economic Opportunity (Co-Chair) and President's Council on Jobs and Competitiveness (member)</li>
			</ul>
			]]></bio>		
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>53</id>
		<name>Douglas L. Peterson</name>
		<firstname>Douglas L.</firstname>
		<lastname>Peterson</lastname>
		<title1>Chief Operating Officer</title1>
		<title2>Citibank, N.A.</title2>
		<title3/>
		<title4/>
		<smallImg>peterson.jpg</smallImg>
		<speaker/>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>no</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>no</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>no</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>no</sec16exec>
		<profilelink>peterson/index.htm</profilelink>
		<sec16link/>
		<speakerInfo>
			<highlights>
				<link/>
			</highlights>
			<categories>
				<category>Market Insights</category>
				<category>Corporate Citizenship and Governance</category>
			</categories>
			<topic>
				<topicname/>
			</topic>
			<travels>
				<place>New York</place>
			</travels>
		</speakerInfo>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<p>Doug Peterson is currently the Chief Operating Officer of Citibank, N.A., Citigroup's principal banking entity that operates in over 100 countries.  Doug has been with Citigroup for 25 years.</p>
			<p>Until the beginning of 2010, Doug was the CEO of Citigroup, Japan where he oversaw the entire franchise covering Capital Markets, Corporate & Investment Banking, Global Transaction Services and Retail Banking, managing over 15,000 employees.  Doug had previously been the Chief Auditor of Citigroup from 2001 to 2004 where he had led the enterprise-wide integration of the Internal Audit teams after the merger of Citicorp and Travelers.  In prior roles, he served as country manager in Costa Rica and Uruguay and as a Corporate Banker in Argentina and New York.</p>
			<p>Doug received his undergraduate degree in Mathematics and History at Claremont McKenna College ('80) and his MBA from the Wharton School at the University of Pennsylvania ('85).  Doug has previously served on the boards of the American Chambers of Commerce (in Costa Rica, Uruguay, and Japan), the Uruguayan American School, and Teaching Matters Inc.  He is currently on the Board of Advisors for the Wharton Financial Institutions Center, the Advisory Board of the Kravis Leadership Institute, and the Board of the US-Japan Business Council.</p>
			]]></bio>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>127</id>
		<name>Michael M. Roberts</name>
		<firstname>Michael M.</firstname>
		<lastname>Roberts</lastname>
		<title1>Managing Director &amp; Global Head</title1>
		<title2>Corporate Banking &amp; Capital Management, Global Banking</title2>
		<title3>Chief Lending Officer, Citibank, N.A.</title3>
		<title4/>
		<smallImg>roberts.jpg</smallImg>
		<speaker/>
		<boardDir/>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>yes</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>no</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>no</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>no</sec16exec>
		<sec16link/>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<p>Michael M. Roberts is the Head of Global Corporate Banking and Capital Management within Citi's Global Banking Group. In this role, Mr. Roberts focuses on several areas, such as further developing Citi's leading Corporate Bank, which provides the highest quality cross-border corporate banking solutions to the world's multinational corporations through Citi's unrivalled global network, and on the end-to-end management of Citi's corporate loan portfolio. </p>
			<p>Mr. Roberts also recently assumed the role of Chief Lending Officer for Citibank, N.A., and is responsible for all loan-related activities for Citibank globally, which includes the ICG, the Private Bank and the Consumer Bank. </p>
			<p>Prior to his present position, he was the Deputy Head and COO of Citi's Global Corporate Bank, a position he held from April 2007 to December 2008. </p>
			<p>Previously, Mr. Roberts was a Managing Director and Head of Global Financial Institutions, a position held between April 2007 and January 2003, and Head of Global Automotive and Industrials (2002) within Citibank's Global Relationship Bank. Prior to these assignments, Mr. Roberts was Chairman and Chief Executive Officer of Citibank Canada, the leading foreign bank operating in Canada from 1998 until 2002. </p>
			<p>He also served in various positions with the bank in France, Belgium and Turkey. </p>
			<p>Mr. Roberts received a B.A. in economics from the University of Texas and an M.A. in international affairs (Banking and Finance) at Columbia University's School of International Affairs.</p>
			<p>Mr. Roberts is married and has two daughters and lives in New York.</p>
			]]></bio>
	</profile>	
	<profile>
		<id>55</id>
		<name>Fernando Quiroz Robles</name>
		<firstname>Fernando</firstname>
		<lastname>Quiroz Robles</lastname>
		<title1>Chief Executive Officer</title1>
		<title2>Institutional Clients Group Mexico &amp; Latin America</title2>
		<title3/>
		<title4/>
		<smallImg>quiroz.jpg</smallImg>
		<speaker>yes</speaker>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>no</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>no</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>no</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>no</sec16exec>
		<profilelink>quiroz/index.htm</profilelink>
		<sec16link/>
		<speakerInfo>
			<highlights>
				<link/>
			</highlights>
			<categories>
				<category>Market Insights</category>
			</categories>
			<topic>
				<topicname>Corporate &amp; Investment Banking in Mexico &amp; Latin America</topicname>
			</topic>
			<travels>
				<place>Mexico City</place>
			</travels>
		</speakerInfo>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<p>Fernando Quiroz is CEO of Institutional Clients Group Mexico & Latin America, Deputy President of Banamex, Head of Specialized Banking in Banamex and President of Accival, Banamex's brokerage house.</p>
			<p>Mr. Quiroz is member of Citi's Senior Leadership Committee, ICG Management Committee; ICG Business Committee, ICG Business Practices Committee and of the Corporate Client Steering Committee.</p>
			<p>Prior to his current position, Mr. Quiroz was head of Strategy and Corporate Development of Banamex and Citi Latin America.</p>
			<p>He began his career at Banamex in 1979, holding various positions in the Consumer, International and Investment Banking Divisions, and Strategic Planning.  He also served as Chief Economist of Banamex.</p>
			]]></bio>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>57</id>
		<name>Bill Rhodes</name>
		<firstname>Bill</firstname>
		<lastname>Rhodes</lastname>
		<title1>Citi Senior Advisor</title1>
		<title2/>
		<title3/>
		<title4/>
		<smallImg>rhodes.jpg</smallImg>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>no</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>no</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>yes</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>no</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>no</sec16exec>
		<profilelink>rhodes/index.htm</profilelink>
		<sec16link/>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<p>Bill Rhodes is a Senior Advisor for Citi. In his most recent role, Mr. Rhodes was the Senior International Officer for Citi. He had specific responsibilities for client relationships worldwide, as well as for relationships with governments and other official institutions.</p>
			<p>Mr. Rhodes gained a reputation for international financial diplomacy in the 1980s as a result of his leadership in helping manage the external-debt crisis that involved developing nations and their creditors worldwide. During that period and in the 1990s, he headed the advisory committees of international banks that negotiated debt-restructuring agreements for Argentina, Brazil, Jamaica, Mexico, Peru, and Uruguay. In 1998, when the Republic of Korea experienced liquidity problems, he chaired the international bank group that negotiated the extension of short-term debt of the Korean banking system. In early 1999, at the request of the government of Brazil, he acted as worldwide coordinator to help implement the maintenance of trade and inter-bank lines by foreign commercial banks to Brazil.</p>
			<p>Mr. Rhodes is a Director of Banamex; a Director of the Private Export Funding Corporation; First Vice Chairman of the Institute of International Finance; Chairman Emeritus of the Americas Society and Council of the Americas; Chairman of the U.S.-Korea Business Council; a Director of the U.S.-Russia Business Council; a Director of the U.S.-Hong Kong Business Council; a Director of the Korea Society; Vice Chairman of the National Committee on U.S. - China Relations; a Director of the U.S.- China Business Council; a member of Korean President Lee's Council of Global Advisors; a Senior Advisor to the Dalian Government in China; a member of the Inter-American Development Bank's Private Sector Advisory Board; a member of the International Policy Committee of the U.S. Chamber of Commerce; a member of the Board at the Foreign Policy Association; Trustee of the Asia Society and a Trustee of the Economic Club of New York. He is also a member of the US-Brazil CEO Forum, a member of the Advisory Council of the Brazilian American Chamber of Commerce, the Council on Foreign Relations, and The Group of Thirty. He also previously served as Chairman of the New York Blood Center and the Bankers Association for Finance and Trade.</p>
			<p>Mr. Rhodes is a Governor and Trustee of The New York-Presbyterian Hospital; a member of the Lincoln Center Consolidated Corporate Fund Leadership Committee; and a member of the Metropolitan Museum of Art Business Committee and Chairman's Committee. He is a member of the Board of Overseers of the Watson Institute for International Studies at Brown University and Chairman Emeritus of the Board of Trustees of the Northfield Mount Hermon School.</p>
			<p>He has received decorations and honors from various governments and institutions, including an Honorary Doctorate in Humane Letters from his alma mater Brown University, Chevalier and Officer of France's Legion of Honor, decorations from Poland, Korea, Brazil, Mexico, Argentina, Venezuela, Colombia, Panama and Jamaica, and multiple awards from not-for-profit organizations such as the Africa-America Institute and the Arab Bankers Association of North America in recognition of his contributions to international banking and finance.</p>
			<p>Mr. Rhodes joined Citibank in 1957 after graduating from Brown University.</p>
			]]></bio>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>54</id>
		<name>Lawrence R. Ricciardi</name>
		<firstname>Lawrence R.</firstname>
		<lastname>Ricciardi</lastname>
		<title1>Senior Advisor, IBM Corporation, Jones Day and Lazard Freres &amp; Co.</title1>
		<title2/>
		<title3/>
		<title4/>
		<smallImg>ricciardi.jpg</smallImg>
		<boardDir>yes</boardDir>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>no</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>no</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>yes</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>no</sec16exec>
		<profilelink/>
		<sec16link>ricciardi/holdings.htm</sec16link>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<ul class="list" style="width: 355px;">
				<li>Senior Advisor, IBM Corporation, Jones Day, Lazard Fr&egrave;res & Co. - 2003 to present</li>
				<li>Senior Vice President and Advisor to Chairman, IBM - 2002</li>
				<li>Senior Vice President and General Counsel, IBM - 1995 to 2001</li>
				<li>Chief Financial Officer, IBM - 1997 to 1998 </li>
				<li>President, RJR Nabisco, Inc. - 1993 to 1995</li>
				<li>Co-Chairman and Chief Executive Officer, RJR Nabisco, Inc. - 1993</li>
				<li>Executive Vice President and General Counsel, RJR Nabisco, Inc. - 1989 to 1995</li>
				<li>Executive Vice President and General Counsel, American Express Travel Related Services - 1983 to 1989 </li>
				<li>Joined American Express - 1973</li>
				<li>Director of Citigroup since 2008 </li>
				<li>Director of Citibank, N.A. since 2009 </li>
				<li>Other Directorships: N/A</li>
				<li>Previous Directorships within the last five years: Reader's Digest Association, Royal Dutch Petroleum and Royal Dutch Shell plc</li>
				<li>Other Activities: The Andrew W. Mellon Foundation (Trustee), National Humanities Center (Trustee) and The Morgan Library & Museum (President)</li>
			</ul>
			]]></bio>		
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>56</id>
		<name>Judith Rodin</name>
		<firstname>Judith</firstname>
		<lastname>Rodin</lastname>
		<title1>President, Rockefeller Foundation</title1>
		<title2/>
		<title3/>
		<title4/>
		<smallImg>rodin.jpg</smallImg>
		<boardDir>yes</boardDir>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>no</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>no</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>yes</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>no</sec16exec>
		<profilelink/>
		<sec16link>rodin/holdings.htm</sec16link>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<ul class="list" style="width: 355px;">
				<li>President, Rockefeller Foundation - 2005 to present</li>
				<li>President Emerita, University of Pennsylvania - 2004 to present</li>
				<li>President, University of Pennsylvania - 1994 to 2004</li>
				<li>Provost, Yale University - 1992 to 1994</li>
				<li>Director of Citigroup since 2004</li>
				<li>Other Directorships: Comcast Corporation and AMR Corporation</li>
				<li>Previous Directorships within the last five years: Aetna Inc.</li>
				<li>Other Activities: World Trade Memorial Foundation (Director), Carnegie Hall (Director), Brookings Institution (Honorary Director), White House Project (member), Council on Foreign Relations (member), Institute of Medicine (member) and New York City Commission for Economic Opportunity (member)</li>
			</ul>
			]]></bio>		
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>101</id>
		<name>Markus Rosgen</name>
		<firstname>Markus</firstname>
		<lastname>Rosgen</lastname>
		<title1>Managing Director</title1>
		<title2>Regional Strategist</title2>
		<title3>Citi Investment Research &amp; Analysis</title3>
		<smallImg>rosgen.jpg</smallImg>
		<speaker/>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>no</bdc>
		<speakerInfo>
			<highlights>
				<link/>
			</highlights>
			<categories>
				<category>Market Insights</category>
			</categories>
			<topic>
				<topicname/>
			</topic>
			<travels>
				<place/>
			</travels>
		</speakerInfo>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<p>Markus RÃ¶sgen is a Managing Director and Head of Regional Strategy, based in Hong Kong.</p>
			<p>Markus joined Citi Investment Research & Analysis in 2004 from Asia ING Financial Markets, where he was the chief strategist covering Asia and Japan. Before that, he worked as a strategist at Morgan Stanley in Hong Kong and London and Warburg Securities in London.</p>
			<p>Markus has been consistently ranked as one of the Best 5 regional strategists by Asiamoney since 2003. In 2007, Markus and his team were a runner-up in Equity Strategy in the Institutional Investor Magazine (All-Asia Research Team survey) and also ranked #3 by Alpha Magazine surveys.</p>
			<p>Markus holds a BA (Hons) in Western European Politics & French from the University of Essex, UK, and an MBA in Banking and Finance from the University of Birmingham Business School in the UK.</p>
			]]></bio>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>58</id>
		<name>Robert E. Rubin</name>
		<firstname>Robert E.</firstname>
		<lastname>Rubin</lastname>
		<title1>Director and Former Senior Counselor, Citi</title1>
		<title2/>
		<title3/>
		<title4/>
		<boardDir>no</boardDir>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>no</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>no</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>no</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>no</sec16exec>
		<profilelink/>
		<sec16link/>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>59</id>
		<name>Mark Rufeh</name>
		<firstname>Mark</firstname>
		<lastname>Rufeh</lastname>
		<title1>Co-Head Global Operations and Technology Division</title1>
		<title2>Global Head of Cost Transformation and Efficiency Improvement</title2>
		<title3/>
		<title4/>
		<smallImg>rufeh.jpg</smallImg>
		<speaker>yes</speaker>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>no</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>no</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>no</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>no</sec16exec>
		<profilelink>rufeh/index.htm</profilelink>
		<sec16link/>
		<speakerInfo>
			<highlights>
				<link/>
			</highlights>
			<categories>
				<category>Market Insights</category>
				<category>The Future of Banking</category>
			</categories>
			<topic>
				<topicname/>
			</topic>
			<travels>
				<place>New York</place>
			</travels>
		</speakerInfo>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<p>Mark Rufeh is a Managing Director and Co-Head of Citigroup's Global Operations and Technology Division.  Mr. Rufeh is also the Global Head of Citigroup's Cost Transformation and Efficiency Improvement Program.  In that capacity, Mr. Rufeh is responsible for leading the Firm's Corporate Services functions, including Real Estate and Facilities, Procurement, Executive Services and Expense Management.</p>
			<p>Mr. Rufeh is a member of the Citigroup Senior Leadership Committee, the Institutional Client Group's Management Committee, and serves as Co-Chair of the Citigroup Expense Advisory Committee.</p>
			<p>Mr. Rufeh joined Citigroup in 2008 as Chief Administrative Officer of the Institutional Client Group.  Prior to joining Citigroup, Mr. Rufeh was a Managing Director and Chief Administrative Officer for the Global Investment Banking and Capital Markets Division of Credit Suisse Group and a member of its Management Committee.</p>
			<p>Mr. Rufeh also served as Chief Executive Officer of The Westchester Capital Group, a private equity firm specializing in real estate-related investments.</p>
			<p>Mr. Rufeh spent fifteen years with Lehman Brothers where he was a member of the Lehman Brothers Operating Committee and held a variety of senior leadership positions, including Chief Operations Officer and Chief Financial Officer of the Lehman Brothers Division.  Mr. Rufeh began his career with The First Boston Corporation.</p>
			<p>Mr. Rufeh received his B.S. from Mercy College in 1983 and an M.B.A. from Manhattan College in 1991.</p>
			<p>Mr. Rufeh is also a Vice Chairman and a member of the Board of Trustees of Graham Windham, one of New York's leading children welfare organizations.</p>
			]]></bio>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>60</id>
		<name>Robert L. Ryan</name>
		<firstname>Robert L.</firstname>
		<lastname>Ryan</lastname>
		<title1>Chief Financial Officer, Retired, Medtronic Inc.</title1>
		<title2/>
		<title3/>
		<title4/>
		<smallImg>ryan.jpg</smallImg>
		<boardDir>yes</boardDir>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>no</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>no</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>yes</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>no</sec16exec>
		<profilelink/>
		<sec16link>ryan/holdings.htm</sec16link>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<ul class="list" style="width: 355px;">
				<li>Senior Vice President and Chief Financial Officer, Medtronic Inc. - 1993 to 2005</li>
				<li>Vice President, Finance and Chief Financial Officer, Union Texas Petroleum Corporation - 1984 to 1993</li>
				<li>Controller - 1983 to 1984</li>
				<li>Treasurer - 1982 to 1983</li>
				<li>Joined Union Texas Petroleum Corporation - 1982 </li>
				<li>Vice President, Citibank, N.A. - 1975 to 1982</li>
				<li>Management Consultant, McKinsey & Co. - 1970 to 1975</li>
				<li>Director of Citigroup since 2007</li>
				<li>Director of Citibank, N.A. since 2009 </li>
				<li>Other Directorships: General Mills, Hewlett-Packard and Stanley Black & Decker </li>
				<li>Previous Directorships within the last five years: United Health Group</li>
				<li>Other Activities: Cornell University (Trustee) and Harvard Business School (member of Visiting Committee)</li>
			</ul>
			]]></bio>		
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>74</id>
		<name>Anthony M. Santomero</name>
		<firstname>Anthony M.</firstname>
		<lastname>Santomero</lastname>
		<title1>Former President, Federal Reserve Bank of Philadelphia</title1>
		<title2/>
		<title3/>
		<title4/>
		<smallImg>santomero.jpg</smallImg>
		<boardDir>yes</boardDir>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>no</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>no</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>yes</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>no</sec16exec>
		<profilelink/>
		<sec16link>santomero/holdings.htm</sec16link>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<ul class="list" style="width: 355px;">
				<li>Senior Advisor, McKinsey & Company - 2006 to 2008</li>
				<li>President, Federal Reserve Bank of Philadelphia - 2000 to 2006</li>
				<li>Richard K. Mellon Professor, Finance, The Wharton School at the University of Pennsylvania - 1984 to 2002</li>
				<li>Director of Citigroup since 2009</li>
				<li>Director of Citibank, N.A. since 2009 </li>
				<li>Other Directorships: RenaissanceRe Holdings, Ltd., Penn Mutual Life Insurance Company, Columbia Funds and B of A Fund Series Trust*</li>
				<li>Previous Directorships within the last five years: N/A</li>
				<li>Other Activities: Drexel University (Trustee), Drexel University College of Medicine (Vice Chair and Trustee) and Ben Franklin Technology Partners of Southeast Pennsylvania (Director)</li>
			</ul>
			<p></p><p>*Mr. Santomero will resign from B of A Fund Series Trust's Board as of June 30, 2011.</p>
			]]></bio>		
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>61</id>
		<name>Deepak Sharma</name>
		<firstname>Deepak</firstname>
		<lastname>Sharma</lastname>
		<title1>Chairman</title1>
		<title2>Citi Private Bank</title2>
		<title3/>
		<title4/>
		<smallImg>sharma.jpg</smallImg>
		<speaker>yes</speaker>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>no</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>no</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>no</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>no</sec16exec>
		<profilelink>sharma/index.htm</profilelink>
		<sec16link/>
		<speakerInfo>
			<highlights>
				<link/>
			</highlights>
			<categories>
				<category>Market Insights</category>
				<category>Client Trends and Insights</category>
			</categories>
			<topic>
				<topicname>Wealth Management: Trends, Opportunities, Challenges</topicname>
				<topicname>The Rise of Asia and the Emerging Economies</topicname>
			</topic>
			<travels>
				<place>Singapore</place>
			</travels>
		</speakerInfo>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<p>Deepak Sharma is Chairman of Citi Private Bank. Before taking on this role in April 2009, Deepak was Chief Executive Officer of Global Wealth Management - International. He is a member of Citi's Senior Leadership Committee.</p>
			<p>Deepak joined Citi in 1976 as a management associate in India. His career has spanned different functional and geographical areas across the Citi global franchise. These include management positions in Operations and Technology, Treasury, Strategic Planning, Electronic Banking, The Citi Private Bank, and Investment Management. He has worked with Citi in India, Korea, Saudi Arabia, the U.S., and Switzerland prior to his current assignment in Asia.</p>
			<p>Deepak is the co-founder and trustee of Indiapore Trust, a fund to benefit children's education across Asia. He is also a trustee of Singapore Indian Development Association (SINDA), a self-help group whose primary focus is to reach out and empower low-income families to stand on their own feet. He is a board member of the Singapore Tyler Print Institute, a non-profit organization that promotes artists in Asia and globally, and a member of the Management Board of the Middle East Institute.</p>
			<p>Deepak received his graduate degree in chemistry and his master's in business administration from the Indian Institute of Management, Ahmedabad.</p>
			]]></bio>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>62</id>
		<name>Zion Shohet</name>
		<firstname>Zion</firstname>
		<lastname>Shohet</lastname>
		<title1>Executive Vice President</title1>
		<title2>Citi Financial Regulation Reform</title2>
		<title3/>
		<title4/>
		<smallImg>shohet.jpg</smallImg>
		<speaker>yes</speaker>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>no</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>no</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>no</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>no</sec16exec>
		<profilelink>shohet/index.htm</profilelink>
		<sec16link/>
		<speakerInfo>
			<highlights>
				<link/>
			</highlights>
			<categories>
				<category>Corporate Citizenship and Governance</category>
			</categories>
			<topic>
				<topicname/>
			</topic>
			<travels>
				<place>New York</place>
			</travels>
		</speakerInfo>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<p>Zion Shohet is Executive Vice President overseeing Citi's firm-wide response to Financial Regulation reform.</p>
			<p>Most recently, Mr. Shohet was Chief Operating Officer of Citi's Institutional Clients Group and a member of Citi's Senior Leadership Committee.</p>
			<p>Before that, Mr. Shohet served as Treasurer and Head of Corporate Finance for Citi. Before that role, he was Citi's Head of Strategy and M&A, helping to shape the direction and strategy of the company and to drive its acquisition program. Prior to assuming that position, Mr. Shohet worked in Citi's International businesses.</p>
			<p>Before joining Citi in April 2001, Mr. Shohet worked in venture capital, where he made investments in financial services companies, and for McKinsey &amp; Company's New York office, where he advised institutional and retail financial services clients on strategy, operations, and corporate finance. Earlier in his career, he worked for Oliver, Wyman and Company in retail banking and insurance.</p>
			<p>Mr. Shohet received his JD from Harvard Law School and his BA in economics from Princeton University, both with high honors.</p>
			]]></bio>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>84</id>
		<name>Edward Skyler</name>
		<firstname>Edward</firstname>
		<lastname>Skyler</lastname>
		<title1>Executive Vice President</title1>
		<title2>Global Public Affairs</title2>
		<title3>Citigroup</title3>
		<title4/>
		<smallImg>skyler.jpg</smallImg>
		<opc>yes</opc>
		<bdc>no</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>none</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>no</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>no</sec16exec>
		<profilelink>skyler/index.htm</profilelink>
		<sec16link/>
		<social><![CDATA[<a href="http://twitter.com/edskyler"><img src="/citi/corporategovernance/profiles/images/a_twitter.gif" border="1" alt="Edward Skyler"></a>]]></social>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<p>Edward Skyler joined Citi as Executive Vice President for Global Public Affairs in May 2010. Mr. Skyler leads all external and internal communications, government affairs, branding and corporate sponsorships, and shares leadership of Investor Relations. He is charged with ensuring that Citi's global dialogues with the public, governments and investors are effective and consistent.</p>
			<p>Prior to joining Citi, Mr. Skyler served as a member of Mayor Michael R. Bloomberg's administration from 2002 to 2010, rising to the position of Deputy Mayor for Operations for the City of New York. In that capacity, he oversaw the performance of the City's main operational agencies and served as a top budget, legislative, and labor negotiator. Mr. Skyler oversaw four consecutive balanced and on-time City budgets; negotiated legislation to reform lobbying and "pay-to-play" practices; and spearheaded critical initiatives such as the overhaul of the City's 911 system and its sustainability agenda.</p>
			<p>Before he was appointed Deputy Mayor for Operations, he served as Press Secretary and Communications Director during Mayor Bloomberg's first term. He managed all communications operations, including media relations and speechwriting. Prior to joining the Bloomberg Administration, he worked in the Corporate Communications group of Bloomberg LP. He also served as Deputy Press Secretary to Mayor Rudolph W. Giuliani and Public Information Director at the Department of Parks & Recreation.</p>
			<p>Mr. Skyler is a graduate of the University of Pennsylvania and earned a law degree from the Fordham University School of Law, which he attended at night. A member of the New York State Bar Association, he has been honored by many civic organizations, including the Association for a Better New York.</p>
			]]></bio>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>118</id>
		<name>Cece Stewart</name>
		<firstname>Cece</firstname>
		<lastname>Stewart</lastname>
		<title1>President, U.S. Consumer and Commercial Banking</title1>
		<title2/>
		<title3/>
		<title4/>
		<smallImg>stewart.jpg</smallImg>
		<speaker/>
		<boardDir/>
		<opc>yes</opc>
		<bdc>no</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>no</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>no</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>no</sec16exec>
		<sec16link/>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<p>Cece Stewart joined Citi in January 2011 as the President of U.S. Consumer and Commercial Banking. She has responsibility for Retail Banking, Commercial Banking, Small Business Banking and Citi Personal Banking and Wealth Management (CPBWM).</p>
			<p>Prior to joining Citi, Cece was the President of the Retail Banking Group and CEO of Morgan Stanley Private Bank N.A., as well as a member of the firm's Management Committee. She joined Morgan Stanley in January 2009 and was responsible for building all aspects of retail banking, including deposits, loans, the credit and debit card business, and mortgages as well as managing Morgan Stanley's trust company. </p>
			<p>Previously, Cece served as Executive Vice President and Head of Retail and Small Business Bank at Wachovia from 2003 to 2008, where she oversaw all retail banking operations for the company. She had been employed by the company since 1978 in a variety of regional banking positions. </p>
			<p>Cece attended the University of South Carolina and graduated from Winthrop University's Executive Master of Business Administration program with honors in 1993. She is on the Foundation Board for Winthrop University and was also the prior Chair of the Consumer Bankers Association.</p>
			<p>Cece's achievements have been recognized by various industry publications. In both 2007 and 2008, she was named by <i>Fortune</i> as one of the "50 Most Powerful Women in Business" and on <i>U.S. Banker</i>'s "Most Powerful Women in Banking" list. Cece is an experienced, dynamic business leader with over 30 years of industry experience. </p>
			]]></bio>
	</profile>	
	<profile>
		<id>93</id>
		<name>Carsten Stendevad</name>
		<firstname>Carsten</firstname>
		<lastname>Stendevad</lastname>
		<title1>Managing Director</title1>
		<title2>Global Head Financial Strategy Group Citi</title2>
		<smallImg>stendevad.jpg</smallImg>
		<speaker>yes</speaker>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>no</bdc>
		<speakerInfo>
			<highlights>
				<link/>
			</highlights>
			<categories>
				<category>Market Insights</category>
			</categories>
			<topic>
				<topicname>Corporate Strategies to Navigate the Crisis</topicname>
				<topicname>Priorities &amp; Challenges for Multinational Organizations</topicname>
			</topic>
			<travels>
				<place>New York</place>
			</travels>
		</speakerInfo>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<p>Carsten is the global head of the Financial Strategy Group (FSG) advising corporates and sovereigns throughout the world on a broad range of corporate finance issues such as valuation, acquisition strategies, capital structure and financing strategies.</p>
			<p>In addition to his client advisory work, Carsten has authored numerous corporate finance articles and reports which have been widely quoted in the Financial Times, Wall Street Journal, The Economist, Euromoney, Newsweek etc.  Carsten has also published in the Journal of Applied Corporate Finance and McKinsey Quarterly.</p>
			<p>Carsten joined Citi in 2002 and spent two years in India as head of the Corporate Advisory Group.  Prior to joining Citi, Carsten worked for McKinsey & Co. based in New York and Copenhagen advising bulge bracket investment banks on growth strategies and operational restructurings. Earlier, Carsten worked in the Central Bank of Denmark. Carsten was born in Denmark and grew up in Belgium. Trained as an economist from the University of Copenhagen (Cand. Polit), Carsten also holds an MPP from Harvard's Kennedy School of Government. Carsten is fluent in English, Danish, French and is conversant in German and basic Hindi. Carsten sits on the board of Neighbors Together, a social service organization in the Bedford-Stuyvesant area of Brooklyn, one of the lowest income communities in the United States.</p>
			]]></bio>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>82</id>
		<name>Diana L. Taylor</name>
		<firstname>Diana L.</firstname>
		<lastname>Taylor</lastname>
		<title1>Managing Director, Wolfensohn Fund Management, L.P.</title1>
		<title2/>
		<title3/>
		<title4/>
		<smallImg>taylor.jpg</smallImg>
		<boardDir>yes</boardDir>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>no</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>no</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>yes</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>no</sec16exec>
		<profilelink/>
		<sec16link>taylor/holdings.htm</sec16link>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<ul class="list" style="width: 355px;">
				<li>Managing Director, Wolfensohn Fund Management, L.P. - 2007 to present</li>
				<li>Superintendent of Banks, State of New York - 2003 to 2007</li>
				<li>Deputy Secretary, Governor Pataki, State of New York - 2002 to 2003</li>
				<li>Chief Financial Officer, Long Island Power Authority - 2001 to 2002</li>
				<li>Vice President, KeySpan Energy - 1999 to 2001</li>
				<li>Assistant Secretary, Governor Pataki, State of New York - 1996 to 1999</li>
				<li>Executive Vice President, Muriel Siebert & Company - 1993 to 1994</li>
				<li>President, M.R. Beal & Company - 1988 to 1993 and 1995 to 1996</li>
				<li>Senior Vice President, Donaldson Lufkin & Jenrette - 1984 to 1988</li>
				<li>Vice President, Lehman Brothers Kuhn Loeb - 1982 to 1984</li>
				<li>Associate, Smith Barney Harris Upham - 1980 to 1982</li>
				<li>Director of Citigroup since 2009</li>
				<li>Other Directorships: Brookfield Properties and Sotheby's</li>
				<li>Previous Directorships within the last five years: Allianz Global Investors and FNMA</li>
				<li>Other Activities: Accion International (Chair), AMFAR (Secretary), Columbia Business School (Board of Overseers), Dartmouth College (Trustee), Hudson River Park Trust (Chair), International Women's Health Coalition (Treasurer), Mailman School of Public Health (Board of Overseers), New York Women's Foundation (Vice Chair), The After School Corporation (member) and YMCA of Greater New York (member)</li>
			</ul>
			]]></bio>		
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>63</id>
		<name>Franklin A. Thomas</name>
		<firstname>Franklin A.</firstname>
		<lastname>Thomas</lastname>
		<title1>Consultant, TFF Study Group</title1>
		<title2/>
		<title3/>
		<title4/>
		<boardDir>no</boardDir>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>no</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>no</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>no</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>no</sec16exec>
		<profilelink/>
		<sec16link/>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>75</id>
		<name>William S. Thompson, Jr.</name>
		<firstname>William S.</firstname>
		<lastname>Thompson, Jr.</lastname>
		<title1>Chief Executive Officer, Retired, Pacific Investment Management Company (PIMCO)</title1>
		<title2/>
		<title3/>
		<title4/>
		<smallImg>thompson.jpg</smallImg>
		<boardDir>yes</boardDir>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>no</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>no</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>yes</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>no</sec16exec>
		<profilelink/>
		<sec16link>thompson/holdings.htm</sec16link>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<ul class="list" style="width: 355px;">
				<li>Chief Executive Officer, PIMCO - 1993 to 2009</li>
				<li>Salomon Brothers Inc. - 1975 to 1993</li>
				<li>Chairman, Salomon Brothers Asia Ltd - 1991 to 1993</li>
				<li>Head of Corporate Finance, Western Region - 1988 to 1991</li>
				<li>Managing Director and Head of Institutional Sales, Western Region - 1981-1988</li>
				<li>Joined Salomon Brothers - 1975</li>
				<li>Director of Citigroup since 2009</li>
				<li>Other Directorships: Pacific Life Corporation</li>
				<li>Previous Directorships within the last five years: N/A</li>
				<li>Other Activities: Pacific Symphony Orchestra (Director), Thompson Foundation for Autism (Chair), Thompson Family Foundation (President) and University of Missouri (President's Financial Advisory Council)</li>
			</ul>
			]]></bio>		
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>77</id>
		<name>Alexander G. van Tienhoven</name>
		<firstname>Alexander G.</firstname>
		<lastname>van Tienhoven</lastname>
		<title1>CEO</title1>
		<title2>Citi Wealth Management Latin America</title2>
		<title3/>
		<title4/>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>no</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>no</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>no</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>no</sec16exec>
		<profilelink/>
		<sec16link/>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>111</id>
		<name>Francesco Vanni d'Archirafi</name>
		<firstname>Francesco</firstname>
		<lastname>Vanni d'Archirafi</lastname>
		<title1>Chief Executive Officer</title1>
		<title2>Global Transaction Services</title2>
		<title3>Institutional Clients Group</title3>
		<smallImg>darchirafi.jpg</smallImg>
		<speaker>yes</speaker>
		<opc>yes</opc>
		<bdc>no</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>no</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>no</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>no</sec16exec>
		<speakerInfo>
			<highlights>
				<link/>
			</highlights>
			<categories>
				<category>Corporate Citizenship and Governance</category>
			</categories>
			<topic>
				<topicname/>
			</topic>
			<travels>
				<place>New York</place>
			</travels>
		</speakerInfo>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<p>Francesco Vanni d'Archirafi is the Chief Executive Officer of Global Transaction Services (GTS), a publicly reported division of Citi's Institutional Clients Group. </p>
			<p>GTS provides industry-leading cash management, treasury and trade services and trade finance solutions to corporations, financial institutions and government entities across the globe through its Treasury and Trade Solutions (TTS) business, and custody and clearing services, fund services, securities finance and issuer services to capital markets participants world-wide through its Securities and Fund Services (SFS) business. </p>
			<p>Prior to his current assignment, Francesco was the Global Head for Treasury and Trade Solutions (TTS). He joined GTS in 2003 as the Region Head for Europe, Middle East and Africa. </p>
			<p>Francesco has served in numerous leadership roles in his extensive career at Citi. He joined Citibank in 1983 as a Management Associate in New York. In 1984, he moved to the Corporate Bank in Lima, Peru, as a Relationship Manager, and later took on the role of Treasury Marketing Manager. In 1986, he was appointed Country Treasurer for Peru. In 1987, Francesco moved to London to launch Citibank's Southern Europe Structured Finance business. In 1993, he was appointed Corporate Finance Head for Italy, based in Milan. In 1996, he returned to London as the Global Co-Head for Mergers and Acquisitions.</p>
			<p>In 1998, Francesco was appointed the Market Manager for Iberia responsible for the Corporate Bank and customer relationships in Spain and Portugal; he was also appointed the Country Corporate Officer of Citigroup for Spain, based in Madrid. In 2001, he was named Chairman and CEO of Citibank International plc and the European Customer Group Executive for Citigroup's Corporate Bank headquartered in London.</p>
			<p>Francesco graduated <i>Magna Cum Laude</i> from the American University in Washington, D.C., with a B.S.B.A. degree in finance. He received the Stanley I. Posner Award given to the graduating senior with the highest overall academic average. In 1983, he obtained an M.B.A. in finance and international business from Columbia University in New York City.</p>
			<p>Francesco is the Chairman of Citibank Holdings Ireland Ltd and Citibank Europe plc. He serves on the boards of Mapfre America S.A., Clearstream International, LCH.Clearnet, and Business in the Community. He is also a board member of Junior Achievement Worldwide, a member of its Board of Governors, and is the Chairman of Junior Achievement - Young Enterprise Europe and the ENGAGE network. He resides in New York City with his wife and their two daughters.</p>
			]]></bio>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>64</id>
		<name>Alberto J. Verme</name>
		<firstname>Alberto J.</firstname>
		<lastname>Verme</lastname>
		<title1>Chief Executive Officer</title1>
		<title2>Europe, Middle East and Africa</title2>
		<title3/>
		<title4/>
		<smallImg>verme.jpg</smallImg>
		<speaker>yes</speaker>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>yes</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>none</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>no</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>yes</sec16exec>
		<profilelink>verme/index.htm</profilelink>
		<sec16link>verme/holdings.htm</sec16link>
		<speakerInfo>
			<highlights>
				<link/>
			</highlights>
			<categories>
				<category>The Global Economic Landscape</category>
				<category>Market Insights</category>
			</categories>
			<topic>
				<topicname>Economic Landscape in EMEA</topicname>
				<topicname>Global Financial Industry Post-Crisis</topicname>
			</topic>
			<travels>
				<place>London</place>
			</travels>
		</speakerInfo>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<p>Alberto Verme is CEO of Europe, Middle East, and Africa (EMEA) for Citi with a focus on Central & Eastern Europe and the Middle East, encompassing 18 countries in the region. Beginning in January 2012, Alberto will be Chairman, Europe, Middle East and Africa Banking. Partnering with Bill Mills, joint CEO of EMEA with a focus on Western Europe and Africa, Alberto is responsible for the performance of all of Citi's businesses in EMEA. Citi serves a broad range of client segments across the region, including consumers, corporations, institutions and governments. </p>
			<p>From 2001 to 2004, Alberto was Head of Global Energy, Power and Chemicals Investment Banking. During his tenure, the franchise achieved world leadership and executed a number of marquee transactions including the Conoco-Phillips merger, the Sibneft-Yukos merger and several key restructurings. </p>
			<p>Alberto joined Salomon Brothers in 1994 and worked as Head and later Chairman of Citi's Latin America Investment Banking Group through May 2001. During that time, he built the leading Latin America banking team, recognized with the IFR 2000 Latin America Bank of the Year award. </p>
			<p>Prior to 1994, he worked for Metallgesellschaft AG as President of MG Global Capital in London. From 1983 to 1992, he worked for The First Boston Corporation, where he served as Director and Head of Spain from 1990 to 1992 and Co-Head of Emerging Markets from 1988 to 1990. He began his career at The World Bank in 1979.</p>
			<p>A Peruvian national, Alberto received a B.A. in economics from Denison University in 1979 and an M.B.A. from Columbia Business School in 1984. </p>
			<p>He is a member of Citi's Global Consumer Council, the Citi Foundation Board of Directors, Bank Handlowy w Warszawie S.A. Board of Directors in Poland, Citibank A.S. Board of Directors in Turkey, the U.S.-Egypt and U.S.-Russia Business Council Boards, Columbia Business School London Advisory Board, and Columbia Business School Board of Overseers in the United States.</p>
			]]></bio>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>65</id>
		<name>Stephen Volk</name>
		<firstname>Stephen</firstname>
		<lastname>Volk</lastname>
		<title1>Vice Chairman</title1>
		<title2>Citigroup</title2>
		<title3/>
		<title4/>
		<smallImg>volk.jpg</smallImg>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>yes</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>none</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>no</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>no</sec16exec>
		<profilelink>volk/index.htm</profilelink>
		<sec16link/>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<p>Stephen R. Volk is Vice Chairman of Citi with a focus both on Citi senior management matters and on Citi Institutional Clients Group.</p>
			<p>Mr. Volk joined Citi in September 2004. Prior to that, he served as Chairman of Credit Suisse First Boston, where he worked closely with the CEO on the strategic management of the firm and on key client matters. He joined Credit Suisse First Boston in August 2001 from Shearman & Sterling, a New York-based law firm, where he had been Senior Partner since 1991. While at Shearman & Sterling, Mr. Volk, a leading mergers and acquisition lawyer, was counsel to a number of corporations, including Citicorp. Among the many issues on which his firm advised Citicorp was the restructuring of its Latin America debt portfolio. Some landmark transactions in which he played a role include the mergers of Glaxo and SmithKlein, Viacom-Paramount, Viacom-CBS, and Vivendi-Universal-NBC. </p>
			<p>He joined Shearman & Sterling in 1960 after graduating from Dartmouth College and Harvard Law School, and became a Partner in 1968.</p>
			<p>Mr. Volk is a Director of Continental Grain. He is also a member of the Council on Foreign Relations, the Dean's Advisory Board of Harvard Law School and a fellow of the American Bar Foundation. </p>
			]]></bio>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>79</id>
		<name>Jeffrey R. Walsh</name>
		<firstname>Jeffrey R.</firstname>
		<lastname>Walsh</lastname>
		<title1>Controller</title1>
		<title2>Chief Accounting Officer</title2>
		<title3>Citi</title3>
		<title4/>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>no</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>no</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>no</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>yes</sec16exec>
		<profilelink/>
		<sec16link>walsh/holdings.htm</sec16link>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>69</id>
		<name>Sanford I. Weill</name>
		<firstname>Sanford I.</firstname>
		<lastname>Weill</lastname>
		<title1>Chairman Emeritus, Citi</title1>
		<title2/>
		<title3/>
		<title4/>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>no</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>no</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>no</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>no</sec16exec>
		<profilelink/>
		<sec16link/>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>105</id>
		<name>Steven Wieting</name>
		<firstname>Steven</firstname>
		<lastname>Wieting</lastname>
		<title1>Managing Director</title1>
		<title2>Citigroup's Economic &amp; Market Analysis team</title2>
		<title4/>
		<smallImg>wieting.jpg</smallImg>
		<speaker/>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>no</bdc>
		<speakerInfo>
			<highlights>
				<link/>
			</highlights>
			<categories>
				<category>The Global Economic Landscape</category>
			</categories>
			<topic>
				<topicname/>
			</topic>
			<travels>
				<place/>
			</travels>
		</speakerInfo>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<p>Steven Wieting is a managing director of Citigroup's Economic & Market Analysis team, responsible for the firm's global economic forecasts and policy analysis. Mr. Wieting, based in New York, serves as the lead economist for the US institutional equities business where he advises the firm's clients globally on macroeconomic issues.</p>
			<p>In addition to forecasting and interpreting economic developments, Mr. Wieting's research focuses heavily on financial markets, investment risks and opportunities. He publishes his research in the weekly Portfolio Economics and also contributes to the firm's Comments on Credit and Portfolio Strategist. His quarterly Inside the S&P 500 provides projections of corporate earnings for the S&P 500 and its industry sectors, a macro-driven check on analysts' earnings expectations, and the first report of its kind on Wall Street.  Mr. Wieting is also a member of the Morgan Stanley Smith Barney Global Investment Committee Advisory Council.</p>
			<p>Prior to joining Smith Barney in 1996, Mr. Wieting was an economics correspondent with Dow Jones, where he followed financial markets, economic forecasts and reported on the views of Federal Reserve policymakers and monetary policy developments.  He also served as a contributor to The Wall Street Journal's "Credit Markets" column.  Previously, Mr. Wieting worked for the US Department of Commerce.</p>
			<p>Mr. Wieting received an M.S. in quantitative economics at Baruch College. He also has acquired credits toward a Ph.D. in economics at the City University Graduate Center</p>
			]]></bio>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>71</id>
		<name>James D. Wolfensohn, K.B.E., AO</name>
		<firstname>James D.</firstname>
		<lastname>Wolfensohn, K.B.E., AO</lastname>
		<title1>Chairman, Wolfensohn &amp; Company LLC</title1>
		<title2>Chairman, Citi International Advisory Board</title2>
		<title3>Senior Advisor, Citi</title3>
		<title4/>
		<smallImg>wolfensohn.jpg</smallImg>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>yes</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>no</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>yes</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>no</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>no</sec16exec>
		<profilelink>wolfensohn/index.htm</profilelink>
		<sec16link/>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<p>James D. Wolfensohn is Chairman of Wolfensohn & Company, LLC, a private investment firm and an advisor to corporations and governments. Mr. Wolfensohn became Chairman of Citigroup International Advisory Board on April 18, 2006. He is also advisor to Citigroup's senior management on global strategy and on international matters. </p>
			<p>Mr. Wolfensohn was the ninth president of the World Bank Group (since 1995). On May 31, 2005, at the end of his second term, he left office and assumed the post of Special Envoy for Gaza Disengagement for the Quartet on the Middle East, a position he served until April 30, 2006. In this role, he helped coordinate Israel's planned withdrawal from the Gaza Strip and spearheaded reconstruction efforts as Palestinians assumed sovereignty over the area. Mr. Wolfensohn is also the Chairman of the advisory group of the Wolfensohn Center, a new research initiative focused on global poverty, at the Brookings Institution.</p>
			<p>Mr. Wolfensohn was the third president in the World Bank's history to be reappointed for a second five-year term by the Board of Executive Directors. As President of the World Bank, he travelled to more than 120 countries in order to pursue the challenges facing the World Bank in regard to poverty and environmental issues. He successfully led initiatives on debt reduction, environmental sustainability, anti corruption programs, AIDS prevention and treatment. He developed activities on religion and culture and decentralized offices overseas linked by the most modern telecommunications system in the international community. </p>
			<p>Prior to joining the Bank, Mr. Wolfensohn was an international investment banker. His last position was as President and Chief Executive Officer of James D. Wolfensohn, Inc., his own investment and corporate advisory firm set up in 1981 to work with major U.S. and international corporations. He relinquished his interests in the firm upon joining the World Bank. </p>
			<p>Before setting up his own company, Mr. Wolfensohn held a series of senior positions in finance. He was Executive Partner of Salomon Brothers in New York and head of its investment banking department. He was Executive Deputy Chairman and Managing Director of Schroders Ltd. in London, President of J. Henry Schroders Banking Corporation in New York, and Managing Director of Darling & Co. of Australia. </p>
			<p>Throughout his career Mr. Wolfensohn has also closely involved himself in a wide range of cultural and voluntary activities, especially in the performing arts. </p>
			<p>He has served as Chairman of the Board of the Institute for Advanced Study at Princeton University for the last 18 years. </p>
			<p>In 1970, Mr. Wolfensohn became involved in New York's Carnegie Hall, first as a board member and later, from 1980 to 1991, as Chairman of the Board, during which time he led its successful effort to restore the landmark New York building. He is now Chairman Emeritus of Carnegie Hall. In 1990, Mr. Wolfensohn became Chairman of the Board of Trustees of the John F. Kennedy Center for the Performing Arts in Washington, D.C. On January 1, 1996, he was elected Chairman Emeritus. </p>
			<p>Mr. Wolfensohn has been President of the International Federation of Multiple Sclerosis Societies, Director of the Business Council for Sustainable Development, and served both as Chairman of the Finance Committee and as Director of the Rockefeller Foundation and of the Population Council, and as member of the Board of Rockefeller University. </p>
			<p>He is an Honorary Trustee of the Brookings Institution, a member of the Council on Foreign Relations and the Century Association in New York. </p>
			<p>Born in Australia in December 1933, Mr. Wolfensohn is a naturalized U.S. citizen. He holds B.A. and LL.B. degrees from the University of Sydney and an M.B.A. from the Harvard Graduate School of Business. </p>
			<p>Before attending Harvard, he was a lawyer in the Australian law firm of Allen, Allen & Hemsley. Mr. Wolfensohn served as an Officer in the Royal Australian Air Force, and was a member of the 1956 Australian Olympic Fencing Team. </p>
			<p>Mr. Wolfensohn is a Fellow of the American Academy of Arts and Sciences and a Fellow of the American Philosophical Society. He has been the recipient of many awards for his volunteer work, including the first David Rockefeller Prize of the Museum of Modern Art in New York for his work for culture and the arts. </p>
			<p>In May 1995, he was awarded an Honorary Knighthood by Queen Elizabeth II for his contribution to the arts. Mr. Wolfensohn has also been decorated by the Governments of Australia, Belgium, Brazil, France, Japan, Germany, Georgia, Mexico, Morocco, The Netherlands, Norway, Peru, Pakistan and Russia.  </p>
			]]></bio>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>66</id>
		<name>Paco Ybarra</name>
		<firstname>Paco</firstname>
		<lastname>Ybarra</lastname>
		<title1>Head, Global Markets</title1>
		<title2>Institutional Clients Group</title2>
		<title3/>
		<title4/>
		<smallImg>ybarra.jpg</smallImg>
		<opc>yes</opc>
		<bdc>no</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>no</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>no</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>no</sec16exec>
		<profilelink>ybarra/index.htm</profilelink>
		<sec16link/>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<p>Paco Ybarra is Head of Global Markets.</p>
			<p>Prior to his current position, Mr. Ybarra was the Global Head of Fixed Income, Currencies & Commodities. He joined the bank in 1987 in Spain as a Management Associate. After holding several positions in the Treasury in Madrid, he became Derivatives Head in 1992. In 1994 he moved to Mexico, where he was appointed Country Treasurer in 1995. In 1997 he moved to New York to become Regional Head of Sales and Trading for Citibank Latin America. In January 2002 he became the Regional Head of EM Sales & Trading for Asia Pacific, based in Singapore. In 2004 he was appointed Global Head of EM Sales and Trading and in November 2006, he became Co-Head of Fixed Income.</p>
			<p>Mr. Ybarra holds a bachelor's degree in economics from the University of Valencia in Spain and an M.B.A. from I.E.S.E. in Barcelona.</p>
			]]></bio>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>83</id>
		<name>Ernesto Zedillo</name>
		<firstname>Ernesto</firstname>
		<lastname>Zedillo</lastname>
		<title1>Director, Center for the Study of Globalization and Professor in the Field of International Economics and Politics, Yale University</title1>
		<title2/>
		<title3/>
		<title4/>
		<smallImg>zedillo.jpg</smallImg>
		<boardDir>yes</boardDir>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>no</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>no</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>yes</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>no</sec16exec>
		<profilelink/>
		<sec16link>zedillo/holdings.htm</sec16link>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<ul class="list" style="width: 355px;">
				<li>Director, Center for the Study of Globalization and Professor in the Field of International Economics and Politics, Yale University - 2002 to present</li>
				<li>President of Mexico - 1994 to 2000</li>
				<li>Secretary of Education, Government of Mexico - 1992 to 1993</li>
				<li>Secretary of Economic Programming and the Budget, Government of Mexico - 1988 to 1992</li>
				<li>Undersecretary of the Budget, Government of Mexico - 1987 to 1988</li>
				<li>Banco de Mexico - Economist, Deputy Manager of Economic Research, Director General of FICORCA, Deputy Director - 1978 to 1987</li>
				<li>Director of Citigroup since 2010</li>
				<li>Director of Citibank, N.A. since 2010</li>
				<li>Other Directorships: Alcoa Inc., Procter & Gamble Company and Grupo Prisa </li>
				<li>Previous Directorships within the last five years: Electronic Data Systems Corporation and Union Pacific Corporation</li>
				<li>Other Activities: ACE Limited (Member of International Advisory Board), Rolls-Royce (Member of International Advisory Board), BP (Member of International Advisory Board), Credit Suisse Research Institute (Advisor), World Economic Forum (Foundation Board), The Global Development Network (Chairman) and The Group of Thirty (Member)</li>
			</ul>
			]]></bio>		
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>67</id>
		<name>Shengman Zhang</name>
		<firstname>Shengman</firstname>
		<lastname>Zhang</lastname>
		<title1>Chairman</title1>
		<title2>Asia Pacific</title2>
		<title3/>
		<title4/>
		<smallImg>zhang.jpg</smallImg>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>yes</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>no</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>no</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>no</sec16exec>
		<profilelink>zhang/index.htm</profilelink>
		<sec16link/>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<p>Shengman Zhang is Chairman of Citi's Asia Pacific region. Before taking on that role in July 2009, he was Vice Chairman of Global Banking and President of Asia Pacific. Mr. Zhang joined Citi in February 2006 as Vice Chairman of Global Banking and Chairman of the Public Sector Group. </p>
			<p>Mr. Zhang, a Chinese national, came to Citi from the World Bank where he was the Managing Director from 2001 to 2005 in charge of the Bank's day-to-day worldwide operations, including all its six geographical regions and six Sector/Thematic Networks. He chaired the Bank's Operations Committee, the Sanctions Committee, and the Corporate Committee on Fraud and Corruption Policy. He was also the Chairman of the Bank Group's Crisis Management Committee.</p>
			<p>Prior to that, from 1997 to 2001, he oversaw the World Bank's Corporate and Support Functions and Sectors and Regions respectively. From 1995 to 1997, Mr. Zhang was Vice President and Corporate Secretary of the World Bank and Executive Director for China between 1994 and 1995. Earlier, Mr. Zhang held a number of senior positions at the Ministry of Finance in China.</p>
			<p>Mr. Zhang is a graduate of Fudan University, China. He also attended McGill University (Canada) as an exchange student. He held an M.P.A. degree from University of Washington, D.C., and finished the Advanced Management Program of Harvard Business School.</p>
			]]></bio>
	</profile>
	<profile>
		<id>68</id>
		<name>Enrique Zorrilla Fullaondo</name>
		<firstname>Enrique</firstname>
		<lastname>Zorrilla Fullaondo</lastname>
		<title1>Chief Executive Officer</title1>
		<title2>Banamex</title2>
		<title3/>
		<title4/>
		<smallImg>zorrilla.jpg</smallImg>
		<speaker>yes</speaker>
		<opc>no</opc>
		<bdc>no</bdc>
		<executivecommittee>no</executivecommittee>
		<senioradvisor>no</senioradvisor>
		<sec16dir>no</sec16dir>
		<sec16exec>no</sec16exec>
		<profilelink>fullaondo/index.htm</profilelink>
		<sec16link/>
		<speakerInfo>
			<highlights>
				<link/>
			</highlights>
			<categories>
				<category>Market Insights</category>
			</categories>
			<topic>
				<topicname>The "Universal Banking" Model</topicname>
				<topicname>Commercial Banking in Mexico</topicname>
			</topic>
			<travels>
				<place>Mexico City</place>
			</travels>
		</speakerInfo>
		<bio><![CDATA[
			<p>Enrique Zorrilla is Chief Executive Officer for Banamex in Mexico. He is also a member of the Senior Leadership Committee of Citi and of the Boards of Directors of Seguros Banamex, Afore Banamex, and Credito Familiar.</p>
			<p>Prior to joining Banco Nacional de Mexico (Banamex) in July 1982, Enrique spent two and a half years with PricewaterhouseCoopers as a Senior Consultant.</p>
			<p>He joined Banamex in Mexico City as an Account Executive in Corporate Banking and, in 1985, he became an Assistant Vice President. In 1988, he opened a new office for the Corporate Banking in Monterrey and, in 1991, was named Senior Vice President responsible for the Corporate and Middle Markets in the North Division.</p>
			<p>From 1993 to 1996, he was the Executive Vice President in charge of the North Division, including the Corporate, Middle Markets, and Retail banking units. He moved back to Mexico City in mid-1996 to design and launch the commercial strategy for Afore Banamex (the pension funds company) and was elected Corporate Director of Commercialization in November of that same year.</p>
			<p>In 2001, after the official announcement of the integration of Citibank Mexico and Banamex, he was put in charge of coordinating the integration process of the retail and the affluent customer segments, an objective that was accomplished in a period of six months. In January 2006, he was appointed Head of Commercial Markets, responsible for 1,388 branches and around 17,386 employees.</p>
			<p>Enrique assumed his current role in December 2006.</p>
			<p>He has a B.A. from the Universidad Iberoamericana, a Certified Public Accounting degree from the Universidad Nacional Autonoma de Mexico, and an MBA from Northwestern University, Chicago. He is the founder of the Diversity Committee, Mexico.</p>
			]]></bio>
	</profile>
</profdata>
